################################################################################
<cache>10800</cache>
<fanart>https://i.pinimg.com/originals/05/6d/cf/056dcffe0f8b622dd72acd921378b875.jpg</fanart>
<content></content>
################################################################################


<plugin>
  <title>Bob Ross</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCxcnsr1R5Ge_fbTu5ajt8DQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAy6GVR9FKfi5C_qKDZkFSCyDIoxrhCeeWf-bQ=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>The official YouTube channel of "The Joy of Painting" and Bob Ross. Watch and paint along with every episode of The Joy of Painting! Happy painting!

You've see Bob Ross before. He is the soft-spoken guy painting happy clouds, mountains, and trees in about 26 television minutes, using big house painting-type brushes and encouraging audiences with his gentle reminder, "you can do it."

The Joy of Painting is an American half-hour instructional television show hosted by painter Bob Ross which ran from January 11, 1983, until May 17, 1994. In each episode, Ross taught techniques for landscape oil painting, completing a painting in each session.</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Draw with Jazza</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCHu2KNu6TtJ0p4hpSW7Yv7Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-HA9hEHM71h0/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/sEmrRics1FE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Join me for new content every week, like tutorials, speedpaintings, streams, competitions and more!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Bobby Duke Arts</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCSC1HqVmTaE4Shn32ihbC7w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-yq6VF3in_D8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/0OQleZH-jHc/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi, I'm Bobby Duke. I live in Texas and when "I want that", I make it. (insert strange scream)
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Doodle Date</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCjU6f8kXosHh7GD-069VWQQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ibhom5eO54I/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/V_MmQuNRTSk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>British art couple that post new ART videos every TUES, FRI & SUNDAY :)
We love doing silly art challenges, drawing in our sketchbooks outside, trying new art supplies and art & craft hauls!
We live in the UK and have two guinea pigs ^__^</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Peter Draws</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCGtGTAa-xarr2HrEKRgRUHQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-TvWQPccDMUo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Ym88dGFYPj0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Here I doodle and you watch and on occasion I do other things</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>markcrilley</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCno-YPZ8BiLrN0Wbl8qICFA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-I0xXTJpmb-8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/TY5czkLoxVM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>How-to-Draw Videos on Every Conceivable Subject!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Heather Rooney</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3MRldbJr8avZpdKlNHmmnw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-oVVu5s2LEjI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/STMHRlCTuGg/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello! I am a 24 year old self-taught illustrator specializing in photorealistic colored pencil and graphite drawings.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Marcello Barenghi</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCcBnT6LsxANZjUWqpjR8Jpw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-788iICJNnbA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/QWFWBhT2s7Q/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>High-level 3D drawing and painting tutorials by "the Italian magician of the 3D Art" specializing in trick art, hyperrealism, mixed media. A new how-to-draw video every Thursday!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing 3D Art</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UChJX37Qpc8U-xQDmm4DcGyA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-CRU851AIOLY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/hzoEa0VLQJk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Drawing and painting is good! Drawing and Painting Channel. 3 Dimensional Art. 3D trick art. Anamorphic Illusions. Optical illusions.
Portrait drawing. How to drawing. How  to painting. Speed drawing. Speed painting. Watercolour painting.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Fine Art-Tips</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCaapxaQKJFJ6XC56CHgeTzw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-bmqD6SlXxJw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/h8Pzggueglo/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Channel by Leonardo Pereznieto

(Para español, ve al canal: ArteDivierte).

To hire Leonardo Pereznieto for workshops or lectures write to the email below this information box. (Business only, not for personal messages, please.)

Leonardo Pereznieto has exhibited his work in many prominent museums and galleries of cities like Florence, London, Paris, Montecarlo, Nice, Frankfurt, Seoul, New York, Los Angeles, Mexico City, etc.

He has delivered over 50 lectures all over the world including at the New York Academy of Art, the Celebrity Centre Florence and the University of Michigan.

Some of the prizes he has been awarded are:

-Gold Medal, Italy Award for Visual Arts.
-Premio Italia, Florence, Italy.
-Awarded by the International Art Festival, NY, NY
-The Mozart Prize for the Arts (sculpture), Nice, France.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Cartooning 4 Kids | How to Draw</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC-biucJWhM8HwjsQ96uoIUw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-T_lL3pmdqTw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/V9c7D6V8hQM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to the Club! Subscribe today and access our HUGE selection of step by step drawing tutorials for young artists and beginners. Draw your favourite characters from movies, Pokemon, Disney, Marvel, Video Games, Cartoon Network and much more. New art lessons posted daily 7 days a week.

If you found value in our lessons then we  ask that you please share this channel with your family, friends and classmates and PLEASE subscribe and continue to watch our videos.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Circle Line Art School</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCVQxmyIOutGT4lmWlDN9pmA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-VPmN-v6x-20/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/39TB0yTWCd0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi, my name is Tom McPherson and I post a new how-to-draw video every Saturday! I specialise in Perspective drawings, Drawing Buildings, Drawing Landscapes, Drawing Optical Illusions, Drawing People and Drawing Objects. Learn to draw with Circle Line Art School. Please subscribe to watch a new how-to-draw art tutorial every week. There are now over 270 of my How-to-Draw art videos on Circle Line Art School. My aim is to inspire people to learn to draw and be more creative.

There are many ways to draw and my aim is to encourage you to try a range of different art techniques and subject matter each week. If you have any comments or suggestions or ideas on what you would like to see next week please leave a comment.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>LethalChris Drawing</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCzM8cfTU666_-aFNulLEx2Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-RtlXl7hUT0Y/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/MZ8_DxzdALA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>How to draw, tutorials, guides, fan art, and vlogging channel.

New artwork video every week. Uploading fan art drawings and paintings, in a time lapse (speed art) video. Also uploading "How to draw" videos.

I focus on uploading speed art regularly, featuring video games, characters, concept art, fine art, movies, celebrities and YouTuber portraits. I'm aiming to also start uploading guides and tutorials, to help teach people how to draw.

Available for Drawing commissions (video games, characters, concept art, movies, celebrities, photos & portraiture), email me: chris_straver@hotmail.co.uk

Aspiring to become a Game Artist, within the Video Game Industry.
I enjoy drawing and painting concept artwork, along with digital artwork in Photoshop. I also enjoy modelling and texturing with 3D software.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing & Painting - The Virtual Instructor</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCULpiAa8nIl_e68y59VYjHQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-HVH-7zJjjnw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/89u9-BVgybE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Learn how to draw and paint! Drawing, painting, and digital art tutorials on a variety of subjects and media by artist and teacher, Matt Fussell. I believe that drawing and painting are skills that can be learned by anyone.  It doesn't require talent - just passion, knowledge, and practice.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>How To Draw tattoo</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCv8MFuhM8eVtfPNyo2j84KA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-nUDGfQ48UX8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/mmgGa3mXzUI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi, this is how to draw channel
I love making friends ! I like to make videos . I upload all types of videos, subscribe and become a friend !
I love fashion and beauty.

I'm an tattooer, oil painter, illustrator, cat romancer, digital artist and animator, :D
I love drawing manga, cars, pets, cartoons, portraits and flowers with watercolor, pen, pencil, ink pen and I am professional with all other colors.

I love making friends …...</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Shoo Rayner</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCaQOnL-tNULRYma5nRDy1QA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-xQSqDOlvBxQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6YhWz0DlU4Y/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Shoo Rayneris the award winning author and illustrator of over 200 children's books published worldwide by major publishers. Shoo is also a publisher, follow his stories and publishing exploits and learn about illustration, how to make books and how to tell stories. Follow Shoo as he visits schools, libraries and festivals around the British Isles and the world.

Learn to draw all sorts of stuff at shoos other channel - www.youtube.com/drawstuffrealeasy

Information about the tools and equipment Shoo uses can be found in the description boxes below the videos.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Art for Kids Hub</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC5XMF3Inoi8R9nSI8ChOsdQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-pwbr7q8g-sM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/sNTyugBGDwo/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey, my name is Rob. We upload new art lessons M-F, every week! Follow along with us and learn how to draw plus other fun art lessons for kids. I have four kids, and we love drawing together! My oldest child is Jack (aka Chuckers), Hadley (aka Hads) is my oldest daughter, Austin (aka Austa-Wasta-Mc-Pasta), and Olivia (Olive) is my youngest. I also have a beautiful wife (Mrs. Hubs)!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Draw So Cute</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3dEvA1is6-0_yuei9iCdEw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-h0W2H_mBTbw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/cXEyEdKCbPw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Have fun learning How To Draw and DIY Craft, anything and everything CUTE with step by step, easy to follow videos.

Hi there! My name is Wennie and I love to draw and craft, CUTE things of course! =) Follow along with me to learn how to draw and make things CUTE and EASY! Watch for fun pop ups too. Hopefully you will learn to draw and create new things while having fun too on my channel. </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DrawKidsDraw</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCH5fi7Ep66Fn2EPvTelvxvQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-gxJECfhnytA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/2-NUaz_7xHg/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Draw Kids Draw is a Drawing Channel For Kids. Learn how to draw popular cartoon characters and other fun things!

100% Kid friendly content! </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Farjana Drawing Academy</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCd3s7BuoOlu4bRJL6RdGWXw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-lsrx5y-A7MQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/vOVGX8McVeQ/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>In this channel tutorials, you can see how to draw step by step perfectly. Alternatively in this tutorial shown coloring techniques. So, all ages people learn how to paint very easily. New drawing video every day</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Fun2draw</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCFf_ebUsE0QHD9AMVTD_npQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-hJyslROYS0g/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/LVs3ig9AWmM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Draw, reimagine, new art challenges, top art videos, & art channel created by popular artist Mei Yu. Watch never-before-seen, hand draw art, new art challenge, fun art video, fun animation, creative art, design, unique painting, illustration, style challenge, amazing art work, new fashion design, re-imagine movie, show, game characters. Learn how to draw, color / colour, easy to advanced Anime / Manga, cartoon art tutorials, people, animal art. Follow my original Animate My Life series, Travel with the Artist, and more. Inform. Entertain. Inspire.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Baylee Jae</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCx-mMlEegnZ-SjWPS73Tgvw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-CR2wTLGh7UY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/jcRkusYyL6U/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I make all kinds of videos related to art, like speedpaints, hauls, product reviews, tutorials, and more. If you like what you see, please subscribe!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Sophie chan</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCPI7Rm8rgXmZnYw12R2SkVw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-0kL9IKINhKA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/sIVv8a28Vd4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I'm a self-taught Manga artist, the author of "The Ocean of Secrets" Manga series. I have always wanted to do this, I was meant to do it, regardless of all the obstacles I've faced. I wanted to show the world that you can achieve your dreams with hard work and determination, I want to inspire you to do the same. </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Alphonso Dunn</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCoBapgfK_m6G7airg1rdn8w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-GniMU84K0Ds/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/HILYttlCUBY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I am passionate about helping others find their passion for drawing and creating art 😊
On my channel you will find lots of videos that provide tips, tricks, and techniques that are based on very basic concepts of drawing

1. be the best you possible
2. help who you can along the way
3. try to make the world a better place
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Jordan Persegati</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCS8dJFs2-_OG-TwxBMUOmiw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-1jSoVWE_js4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/0NWTCRJqsg8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>
I'm an Australian artist who enjoys drawing anime inspired art... with lots of blood! I make Creepypasta videos each week!

Whether I'm narrating creepy horror stories or drawing your favourite manga characters, my goal is to make the most entertaining (and occasionally informative) videos I can!
I'll be making a variety of different content including: art challenges, unboxings, reviews and a whole lot more! Make sure to subscribe to keep up to date with my latest videos :)</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>How to Draw and Paint</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCji4rI3e1-g7Gxjvqih480A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-gTEa_KIEONM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Jq4qzkg8zxY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Art for Kids and Family Fun - How to Draw and Paint! If you’ve ever wanted to learn to draw, paint, sketch, or just have some fun with drawing, then the How to Draw and Paint channel is for you! Featuring hundreds of fun, easy, step-by-step, how-to, super simple video lessons that are perfect for all ages, we’ll show you everything you need to know.

Over the years, How to Draw and Paint has taught millions of aspiring artists how to draw nearly everything you can imagine: from simple hearts and cute kittens, to 3D houses and effects, to cool Minecraft creatures. Our How to Draw and Paint YouTube Channel and companion websites Drawingteachers.com (http://www.drawingteachers.com/) have hundreds of step-by-step articles and online courses to give you the tools you need to become an amazing artist!

So what are you waiting for? Grab some paper and a pencil - How to Draw and Paint will help you become the artist you want to be!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Art of Wei</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCKgkOEqGFUOiXrx1klhlmJQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-jY4SmPCx7LA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/8AjVi804M30/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>
Let me show you how to draw anything the easy way. Full step by step drawing demonstrations with graphite pencils.

And I do 3D modeling as well. But that is not as fun as drawing.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing Hands</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCQ-Ju-faRRBXsSgsR2lH6cw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-vZw5F9MRUe4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Qh8cTSIkEEA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Kasey Golden</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCNwJz8-bLJge72TzJu4ARUA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-lBvCv5PU7mQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/bTg_nk8eCzU/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hiya! My name is Kasey and I mostly focus on watercolor illustrations, but sometimes I like to sew! I upload three times a week! Wowwie!
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Muffalo Potato</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCdmtOFSoI9qIx1BfUOzaU2w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-npZlEje2Tlg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/vwuOxeQ-_34/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Learn to draw in minutes the Muffalo Potato way! Grab your crayons, markers, pencils, or pens and follow along with John as he teaches you how to draw a wide variety of cartoons by using only numbers and letters.
Watch John draw a letter or number in the air, then copy it on your paper. Just keep drawing and turning your paper with John and before you know it, KA-POW! You're making cartoons!
Enjoy a new episode each week and create a whole bunch of fun characters to color and share.
Teachers love Muffalo Potato and parents love to sit down and draw too for a fun family activity.
And remember: "It doesn't have to be perfect. It just has to be fun!"</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DoodleDrawArt</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCbNqUR02W0jCA8v7iV0tAPQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-PoA8LIRGkvk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/LjQ21NVMw10/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>DoodleDrawArt is a drawing channel for kids and beginning artists. My videos will show step-by-step how to draw cute, cartoon pictures. Together we will be drawing animals, holiday themes, and more! The art in this series will use paper, pencils, markers and crayons - No fancy art supplies!

DoodleDrawArt is for artist of all ages, from children to adults. Get out your pencils kids! Let's Draw!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Happy Drawings</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC6h5IetVY4aw1_wJNVFh1Xw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-PFN9GTsCKwc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/7BJNrEvv8GU/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Have fun learning How To Draw anything and everything with my videos ♡</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Facedrawer - How to Draw</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UChXBChGRG95GZGPmLVV39PQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-qdh389A6N9U/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/KDofSJH7_VM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi There! Thanks for visiting our YouTube channel. We post new video every day! We share fun easy step by step drawing lessons, drawing previews and animations and sometime one-one gameplay. Learn how to draw your favorite characters from movies or videogames. We draw everything from Five Nights at Freddy’s (FNaF), Minecraft, Disney, Marvel, Pokemon, Minions, Dragon Ball Z, Anime, Cartoon Network and more.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Draw Their Life</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCKaDRQHf0AELJUcsi64WRtg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-AdmaMWqQMgc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/W-ZifcyrIyc/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I see you stumble upon my channel so let me explain about my channel . Draw My Life is a channel where I draw life story of your favorite fictional character like Batman, Superman life story of Your favorite youtuber and story of Celebrities . By watching my video you can have a pretty good knowledge about all of their lives , cool right, I know . So what are you waiting for hit that SUBSCRIBE button just smash it and join with me for all the fun that we have here .</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>How2DrawAnimals</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCOlX9Ymfc5wKEJR69jSRE1A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-h5MXeGfXtVk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/wBgtxZtNMOM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Learn to draw animals with these videos and the simple step-by-step instructions.

For even easier tutorials, every step is broken down to an individual image at http://www.How2DrawAnimals.com. Check it out!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Paul Priestley</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCMyMtFsqCf0K3Boa1Ig0ApA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-SkNkt-oLqa0/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Y4vdN8H-3Ic/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>This channel has been selected by Feedspot https://blog.feedspot.com/drawing as one of the top 100 Drawing Channels on Youtube. Want to learn to draw and paint, but don't know where to start? This is the channel for you. I have taught art in schools and adult art classes for many years. With this vast amount of experience, I am now creating drawing and painting video tutorials to show students, teachers and children how to draw and paint. Using a step by step approach everything is explained in simple stages to have drawing and painting with confidence in no time at all. The video tutorials are aimed at beginners and those wishing to enhance their drawing and painting techniques and skills. I believe anyone can learn to draw and paint, it just requires two things: to practice and persevere, coupled with great tuition. Between us let's create art. New art tutorial videos will appear here as often as I can produce them. </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing Art Academy</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCc38ZagyazhZa6VQebkEUOQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-JIWEjDjDeDg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/L5izjuc_DDw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Neco Draw</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCnX_mRYLEWREAcaKEBeXGKA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-yRAaMH_r8h4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/zYYa9uCPH5A/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to my channel !
My name is Neco and I am 20 years old. I really like to draw, it's a passion for a long time.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>How to Draw Stuff</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCC8iCB9G6Y5B5BpzDxKDlSg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-KRQESoLMe-U/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/NordxxpERhQ/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to How to Draw Stuff, the channel where you'll learn to draw everyday stuff the easy way.

Our quick drawing tutorials on paper and digital media can get you started drawing very fast.

Drawing doesn't have to be hard, join us on the journey to become a better all-round illustrator!
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>How I Draw</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC7uWciB7Dw0Tnaoqs7H62qA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-aTRQRszNxoY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/uUtdGTjfiL4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Greetings. I'm Robert DeJesus. I'm drawing just about anything; in my own style. From everyday objects, cute animals, trending topics, video game characters, anime characters, portraits, and much more. Make requests in the video comments if you'd like me to try and draw it. Follow, likes and shares are humongously appreciated.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Draw It, Too!</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UClZVDCMYbp_Hogv7MAWVbhg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Uy2aSj380lo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/TRV2ev0vIe0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Do you love to draw, but need a little bit of help?

My name is Ramny and I make YouTube drawing tutorials. On my channel I help young artists develop their drawing skills by showing them how to draw their favorite characters from movies, TV shows, cartoons, comic books, or video games!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Nautica Williams</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCE_P3FFBy76cQkNTqo9aang/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-kU5YqrM8bic/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Fx4dd-xh_u0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>This channel was created to help me, a young artist, to improve along the road (with a little help from my viewers of course).</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DoKiDoKi Drawing</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCY-tGAhulrOzRd6n1mLZwSg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-xuQHUc6Xuus/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Ub36HNHXGwI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Anime/manga/illustration drawing tutorials
Hilarious drawing challenges
Speed drawing</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>KIDS CARTOON DRAWINGS</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCytePDFmydcE-g3pIVR3Rog/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-5xIXu9RnB70/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/2NIeffwxDLc/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi, I'm an Artist,Cartoonist,Illustrator Kids/Children's Fan
In This channel am trying to teach Cartoons,Drawings to Children's</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>zooshii studios</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCc-dOboi5xXo5tNfnu0QT7A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ZDsVaLlzn1M/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/JFeza4Ta2Yw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi zooshettes!

I'm Kitty aka zooshii and I love to draw! Welcome to my drawing channel - if you love cartoons and drawing too, check out the wide range of 'How to Draw' tutorials on this channel.

Happy drawing! With love, Kitty (aka zooshii) x</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DRAW with Chris</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC5kRRap8HrE-R6DJB70rADg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-LP7r-LpuPF8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/G5-C3-4hYOo/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello, my name is Chris :)

I'm a painter, speaker, writer and instructor with over 30 years of experience in drawing and painting. I teach professionally at some of the top art schools in Los Angeles (USA) including New Masters Academy, Art Mentors, Gnomon and Art Center. My work and writing have appeared in books and magazines published worldwide.

My teaching philosophy is grounded in rock solid drawing and painting fundamentals. I am obsessed with learning and spend thousands of hours studying, researching, and applying the best information available to create better art. This channel is a platform for me to share that great information.

Fore more of my work and teaching visit my website: www.drawwithchris.com. Make sure to sign for my free newsletter to get updates on courses, live classes and more great content.

Thanks!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing with Lineke Lijn</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCg_VnlKCBfR7n78FsSx39pw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-pZAxjePYU9U/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/__yCgkbR31I/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>This channel is all about, and only about drawing and it's materials. Most video's are filmed "one on one" and all are explainend to the detail. Should you want to start, or pick up your drawing, because you are allready good at it, this is your channel.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Kirsty Partridge Art</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCSl51TSNCxLQJqLTQp0B6Cg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-SviIVkeEv6A/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/wRtru4G7XfM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>
Welcome to my channel!
I am a 20 year old self taught artist!
I love drawing using coloured pencils, charcoal and markers! I also paint with watercolours. I create both original artwork and fanart :D
I also enjoy helping people improve their art so I am doing a series of tutorial videos explaining all my techniques and tips!
Thank you for visiting my channel!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing 4 Kids | How to Draw</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCwuY5vFq1JrYuJUldW1-kYg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-GpJpN0HcI7w/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/mUICtH-_zhs/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to the DRAWING 4 KIDS channel for beginner artists. We started a second channel for our younger and beginner level artists. To access our Cartooning 4 Kids channel please visit us at https://www.youtube.com/cartooning4kids. We have over 1000 step by step lessons for any level and age. Or you can stay with us right here. :)

We heard our fans so we're responding with more entry level lessons. All our lessons are original artwork. We believe art is the foundation for many things in life. Please visit our website for more information about us at http://www.cartooning4kids.com. We'll continue to add more features and content to our services. Thanks for watching.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Skull Drawings Draw Tattoo</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCLAv_kliH1NdzTWnlFqqUiA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-J2X2Ap6XzHc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/q5z-76ZXKVM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Skull drawings are great. They are fun and very exciting to do. Drawings of skulls are so great. I wanted to go at it from every angle.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Kids Draw TV</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCfyyDmiDqR4g9o28IKJWpwg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-2OFQF6D-5BI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/zorI2bn-X2Y/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi kids here you will learn how to make beautiful drawing and how to paint it with markers and more Enjoy!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Teach Drawing - Coloring for Kids</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCwdViZtK9bNVC6GYcIvbirQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-yPooDvZI5Hs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/WL7F4HvBuoI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi all my friends,
We are Teach Drawing - Coloring for Kids
- BestFriendsForever _

In “Teach Drawing - Coloring for Kids” Channel you can watch the favourite Figures Famous and circumstances like Coloring Page, Coloring book, coloring, coloring page, Coloring for kids, Coloring for children, Coloring babies, Coloring toddlers, drawing, drawing anime, drawing goku, drawing luffy, drawing tutorial, drawing pencil, drawing hand, drawing 3D, drawing spiderman, drawing elsa, drawing flowers, drawing pig, drawing animals, drawing superheroes.
All the world Toys “Coloring Page Club Kids TV”channel. My well as your - We have the same home “Teach Drawing - Coloring for Kids” now!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Sheldene Fine Art Drawing Tutorials</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC_KkCbQ6ZlN0dGnT1GLdz7A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-7XlaPW4clyA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Z9HlhTBYYw4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>My name is Sheldene Visagie and I aim to teach others how to draw realistically.

Weekly Tutorials: www.patreon.com/sheldenefineart

Weekly YouTube Q and A's and weekly YouTube Timelapse videos.

Live drawing via 'Hang with' app

Artist feature every month.

"For the love of being consumed by the definition of my pencil" - Sheldene Visagie</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>WayneTully1</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCHCHxhK4FPeAvOprJWq0DLw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-CatSMetEZDA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/D2h2YpBFvBM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>How to draw fantasy art. Drawing fantasy art videos that inspire you to draw from your own imagination.

Wayne Tully draws some video drawing inspirations and tries to show you how to draw stuff his way but really just to inspire any artist.

I also like to do the odd funny video now and then.

Check out his website - Draw Fantasy Art at the link below and you can also connect with Wayne on his facebook, Google plus and Twitter profile.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Draw With Ian</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCIzyC903-SVeHj0ctn9qH9g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-3OsnUODuZi4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/KLX6EyeYYvY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>This is my drawing channel aimed to teach children how to draw, build their confidence and inspire them :) i love drawing and will draw almost anything such as Disney cartoons, Marvel, Video Games, Cartoon Network and much more.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>IVANOV SEMYON ISP DRAWING</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC-pPKdnHfUhL5UIhwiV52Rg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-sAoy62bztNs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/cyfsImVds34/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Draw Tangles with Dawn</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC4Er38kK1hz5oWyYYO28_ig/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-BfebTBpCxN4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/rDx2NbgIerk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I am NOT a Certified Zentangle Teacher (CZT) and I am NOT teaching the official zentangle method of drawing patterns. What I am doing is helping those who are new to the tangle pattern community figure out the best way to learn to tangle if they are not able to find a CZT in their area. I have started this channel because of so many new people in the facebook group (Tangle It Pattern Club) that feel like the group members are too advanced for them. They feel intimidated by the process and I would like to help them feel less intimidated. Come pick up a pen (any pen will do) and some paper (any paper too) and tangle along with me.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing For Kids and All TV</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCnyUkaFxRa-CA13VnhWOm2A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-yh18b29fEGU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/5zlqIcnJJ1E/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi.. This channel is all about How to Draw different things. Please subscribe if you like to watch and learn drawing.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Easy Drawing</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCMq9QfPrJCmVfUk-pnFTOaw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-vVp2a5d_bvE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Nqata4HNch0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I like drawing:)</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing Tutorials Battu</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC6E6edp2fbNLHC-fr8I3QCw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-5gzJYmFq7qQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/lfWmFz2J2WI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi, i am sudheerbattu, i love sketching, painting , cartoons and illustrations and i like to share my talent with the world. art is my passion.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Scarlet Drawings</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCFgQl-1XbjUZ2U8uiMLqMyg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-qCFd77MQ7so/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/b8J7wTxE8T8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>18 yo
Commissions are open👍
Like,comment and subscribe to my channel :)
Follow and contact me on instagram: scarlet_drawing</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Draw 4 Kids</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCVe0ZdUk-Ud0YSHCOJpuPew/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-vDd8Yrl9BCI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/wmKPEekb7S4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi there! My name is Thuy and I love to draw. I will show you how to draw cartoon people, manga and anime characters,... with pencil, pen and color markers... subscribe for some new videos on every week.

COPYRIGHT NOTICE -Draw 4 Kids didn't own any characters.The Characters which are drawn from movies and shows,all copyrights belong to their respective owners only. All these drawing tutorials are for educational purpose only.

Thank you so much for the all requests. Due to receiving lots of drawing requests, guys please be patient and I will try my best to do ones i can

I hope you will appreciate my videos!   Do not hesitate to comment and subscribe!

Have a GREAT day and see YOU later! :)</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Hello Draw Easy</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCZZmJ0FmknWx1KqHSM0DVEQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-OWlj9bO-Jlc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/eEax4-dGXWg/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey there! Thanks for visiting my YouTube channel. I post new videos every single day!  I draw everything from Marvel, Disney, Minecraft, FNAF, Dragon Ball Z, Anime, Cartoon Network and much more. Follow for the dot and try the same, use pause if you need it. Please subscribe and share the love with your friends.
Thanks for watching!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Gm Drawing</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCF5UaGleM41iEijl0EpTBCA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-L1BtsLR4rRA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/e954W5v_cFc/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey everybody :)

Subscribe to my Channel and follow my journey as an Artist!


 Thank you for the Support!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>NEEYELLOW Drawings</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCRZGubm5YOMmFLi7gWCZR8w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-wFcuGcr7-qg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/xwmDS8P58OA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey!! 🙌 I upload realistic colored pencil and graphite drawings</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Super Simple Draw! - How To Draw for Kids</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC4ltLpkV8sP6nuu8mxcf7Aw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-7yW9xd5q8XE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/8sD-OG6bqoE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to Super Simple Draw where we make drawing and coloring easy and fun! Whether you want to draw a cat, dinosaur or even a robot, we can teach you! Get out your paper, pencils, crayons, or markers and let's draw and color together!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Bo Draw Channel</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCnqPVvQz5pw7zp_TXvq3_OQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-4McbgarqTDU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/dUdZbRMxQpw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey there! Thanks for visiting my YouTube channel.  I draw everything from movies, Disney, Marvel, Video Games, Anime, Cartoon Network and much more. Please subscribe and share the love with your friends.
Thanks for watching! ♥ ♥ ♥</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Kids Drawing Practice</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCrbaMf7Qn4jmi8Mpu-EerVQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-g3cfgAuCTtk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/VQV5LYzKfis/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Kids Drawing practice ( KDP ) is a tutorial for kids to learn drawing. This channel contain simple and easy drawing. Simple drawing is the step to all children's.
Practice simple drawing to improve the skill. Kids Drawing practice YouTube channel updates every week new video.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Mukta easy drawing</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCqdh3prF3MqEZ9opJPlbi1g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-LbQkki-LfQY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/1ZY0ThY43cM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing Class for KIDS</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCrIZhpt_0Uv7TXKwdZVQ1Rg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-hLWxRg0_VM8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/WyFnamKooDk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Subscribe to Learn Basic Drawing. :)</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Jim Bob Drawing Show</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCcXlxUZF3FqiN81WKMsAvLg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Ranjp27FOgQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/O-3p1JXZQaA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey there, and welcome to the JimBob Drawing Show where we draw cartoons and art just for fun. My name is Bobby Chiu and I'm Jim Bryson. We're 2 artists that met in art school and have been great friends ever since. We're always hanging out and doIn art so we figured let's record this stuff and put it on youtube. And that began the start of the Jim-Bob Drawing Show! We'll be posting daily videos for the month of October and if it catches on... who knows so if you'd like to encourage us remember to subscribe and then click the notification button so that you'll know instantly when we have a new video.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>3D Art Drawing</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UClgCXB0bGtC70cRZ5JcBsgw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-A_3vhz1JFKE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/g2b6SI-sQ20/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello, this channel "3D art drawing" (CARTOON ) was created by me, my name is Palash, to teach design for kids, drawing tutorials with cartoon characters etc ...

How to draw,  guides, tutorials, fan art, and blogging channel.
New artwork video every week every day. Uploading fine art drawings and paintings, in a time-lapse (speed art) video. Also uploading "How to draw" videos.

If you want to learn to draw and paint subscribe to my channel...

If you have any requests, I accept advice on the characters to draw, you can make your requests.

by Palash,

Hello, it's canal "3D art drawing" few crudites for me, full 3d art drawing in cartoon characters.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Thays F. Drawing</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCH5zAaw3oA6o_iIeYvG47EQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-qE-pg7KiY1I/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/u2V2iNTzs0A/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Olympia Drawing Attacks</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC1ZvRcRpQkySgXoSRcE-1xQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/--Jy60muDFYY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/KsIJxd5BcYM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>WELCOME and ENJOY MY CHANNEL GUYS
My Name is Tarik i´m 20 ars old Artist in GERMANY
Free Hand Art / Comissions/MyStyle😎👐</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Kids Friendly Drawing</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCLtgH7e_-BD_hKJrnybGKgw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-AUALT3ScySc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/amZ18Q8lvyU/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Kids friendly drawing is the channel for kids, children and adults to learn drawing and coloring step by step. In this channel, you can see variety of drawings like scenery drawing,animals drawing,birds drawing,cartoon drawing,pencil drawing etc.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing Lines for kids Battu</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCfrKuWHbn5j9KAUY-2RfLaw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-kJ4TSBp-QSs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/QjzyOy2v5jI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi, i am sudheerbattu, i love sketching, painting , cartoons and illustrations and i like to share my talent with the world. art is my passion.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Syech Drawing</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCe9BCM4QAxdMbZxCfCudpcQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-HrDyqVT3-Ps/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/3ZAQqf0MnBo/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>All about drawing  cartoon character</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Easy Kids Drawings</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC39j1-_emTMedrUgH-Z7LEA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-vC2r5dhlMjk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/9IonRWOB5MQ/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Learn how to draw and color with these easy step-by-step drawing tutorials made just for kids! Perfect for preschool and kindergarten children, 3 to 6 years old. Educational videos that help kids learn about shapes, colors, letters, and numbers in a fun and easy way! We post daily videos making easy drawings that include animals, plants, food, vehicles, toys, and other fun stuff that kids will love!

Visit our website for more fun drawing resources: www.EasyKidsDrawings.com</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Easy Drawing | Kids Drawing Practice</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCH8Ed7EFEy9AFCGcURBIYZA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-r0SFmXepgEg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/8wLyoWVB2zo/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Easy Drawing | Kids Drawing practice ( KDP ) is a tutorial for kids to learn drawing. This channel contain simple and easy drawing. Simple drawing is the step to all children's.
Practice simple drawing to improve the skill. Easy Drawing | Kids Drawing practice ( KDP ) YouTube channel updates every week new video.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing for Success with Penny Boden</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCT5pUaPmqx03wx1bFP9tfNA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-oVwF_C9EeoM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/jLoK7tMgB3Y/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Penny is a Professional Artist & Certified Teacher whose forte is drawing. Penny loves sharing her knowledge with aspiring artists of all ages. She strives to inspire each student, and to instill in each, a personal repertoire of skills, confidence, and a functional artist’s intuition. Join Penny for a unique, non-traditional learning experience that's student focused and fun! Learn more about Penny & her art at Learn.PennyBoden.ca</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing 101</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCD9MntzKWwxCMZnV9HYdlcg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-1lMID6L53oY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/SUhfCHFpqyY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing for kids BB</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCVVSJbfLqq5Mf-8eZbCP-0w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-GiGq7OmMiFk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/1rGVbT3yNzE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to Drawing for kids BB 💜I draw, paint, draw and artistic artwork for kids and kids on Drawing for kids Channel via Youtube. Sometimes people search for my channel "Drawing for kids BB". Paint the paint, find out the color, color with the colored children's page with color, watercolor and acrylic paint! I feature original paint colors and drawings to inspire creativity!
Please SHARE, COMMENT and LIKE our videos, it's a best you little support that you can give to our channel</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Draw 4 Kids</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC9McCezgDZu_nRyXWHMXzzw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-yQYLFmyRu8o/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Bann38hY57o/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey, my name is A.h. We upload new art lessons M-F, every week! Follow along with us and learn how to draw plus other fun art lessons for kids. I like drawing and coloring.This is my passion and like draw for kids at my free time.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Let's draw kids</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCVPjcRwIQNa-JBKerOWCXWg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-H-pigDlW9bA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/VRKm75KY2eY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>How To Draw with Let's draw kids! Grab a marker or pencil and learn how to draw with us! You will find here lots instructions of how to draw movie characters, funny cartoons, animals, food and much, much more. We hope that you'll enjoy our work and you'll subscribe our channel.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing With James & Austin</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCxrLU5clikZa2D6wcEniL7Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Om3mmmcP6FI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/vpc6rElkjMI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi Guys This Is A Channel For Drawing Making Comic Strips And Fun. Be Sure To Subscribe And Like Our Videos!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Easy Drawing Guides</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCKBY2U1-vwQgs7RFkdyVuLA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-6ZREBjv6QF8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/LPsonqssiW4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Easy to follow, free step-by-step instructions on how to draw animals, plants, and popular cartoon characters. Everyone can create great looking drawings!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Drawing Hours</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC0YRgjdHE3A74bzndp8emEQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-DxOJyCVtpJI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/yqoCUFoO5mI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Learn How to Draw, Sketch, and Paint. Step by Step Drawing Tutorial Videos for Learning Drawing. Videos for Kids, Beginners to Experts. Learn Pencil Drawing, Color Paints, Realistic Drawing Arts.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Maya is drawing</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCHocu2b9zkso9bE-tVaSXJw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-OJUo7uyQyIM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Hv8VtqRSpKw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Drawing tutorial for kids</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Sharjeel Speed Drawings</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCByeSJ1bXf-2NfPsLcfI6Zw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-LxjowwJIbus/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/l-d4jp-95DU/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>hy i am 13 year old  my name is SHARJEEL MUGHAL and this channel is for portraits for cartoon drawing and any other kind of drawings so i hope u will enjoy my channel and please like subscribe and share.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Draw Animals | Kids Drawing Practice</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCf6ajuCkCiwhuC4bEBzZYFQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-jIJoIkzRjpQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/h78uEkkpXhk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Draw Sea Animal | Kids Drawing practice ( KDP ) is a tutorial for kids to learn drawing. This channel contain simple and easy drawing. Simple drawing is the step to all children's.
Practice simple drawing to improve the skill. Draw Sea Animal | Kids Drawing practice ( KDP ) YouTube channel updates every week new video.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Draw With Beektor</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC9vwiOk4p7Sc434xSVy30XA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-eprShKRQgoE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/h31Olp4Ir6E/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Art and music are my passions, my family is what I love. Everything I do, my son is right there. :) For ANY custom work; wildlife portraits, pet portraits, portraits, t-shirt designs, logos, illustrations, tattoo designs, signs, etc contact me at beektor.art@gmail.com or on Instagram at Draw With Beektor. Thank you very much.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>sara animes drawings</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCW1IkfP0flxjrPFJDGjmNfg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-odKiiTV6_9g/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/BcZImX6vT94/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Leila Drawing</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCuFHZhAbxMFeXQtWdtTQwiw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-L9SOR82q5QA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/f9wL9H0p-W8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>
