################################################################################
<cache>10800</cache>
<thumbnail>http://pngimg.com/uploads/youtube/youtube_PNG10.png</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
<fanart>https://a2zwallpaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/2617.jpg</fanart>
################################################################################

<plugin>
  <title>KamuiCosplay</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC79qFuymkVas5dCScbLF9fw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-DfAXuZXn2Oo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/hsggapv1kc0/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Just two Germans making costumes with their dogs! Hope you like what we put out! If you wanna know more, go to kamuicosplay.com or write us a message on Facebook!
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Stereokroma</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCdXCDBx-E4S28GCAypXXHiw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-rDpwEaJWBLY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/XPWgoE3ajMQ/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>We're fascinated about creators and artists of all types. Our videos aim to raise the bar for quality content on Youtube while taking you into the workshops, studios and factories of skilled individuals across the world. Most of our videos feature artisans based in Eastern Canada, but we hope to expand beyond this region once the channel can support itself. 🇨🇦

We have an official website located at: http://tv.stereokroma.com 

Stereokroma is a Montreal based video production company. Our focus is on videography, editing, motion graphics, colour correction and illustration. If you have a project in mind, send us a message and we will work with you to make your vision realized. We're also open to potential collaborations with other Youtubers.
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Mother Daughter Projects</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCdchxe4qrq5DLUCjrM7aVzQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-H80nKE9cEPA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/lP1xHb7hKQI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>We're homeowners sharing our DIY adventures as we learn to maintain, improve, decorate, and use tech in our homes.

You will find videos on home maintenance, improvement, decor and tech on our YouTube channel. For each project, you will also find a link to our blog that will list each step out and what products we used.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Brit Morin</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC8FF-e6Agximt3lyh7AJh_Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-kg9cCfGNhVw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/zyILPo8Bc6Q/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Innovative ideas, apps, and products to help you live more creatively. Learn more: www.brit.co</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Oh Joy!</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UChgrdAdPG6yARuXwhtez1kQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-zP5wRBA7hKQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/S68cUuEHLRM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>The Oh Joy blog covers inspiration and design with a focus on my favorite things: design, fashion and food. The little films you'll find here are an extension of my blog and showcase ideas to inspire your everyday thinking.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>HGTV Handmade</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCesXqJmu3vgiacty8CVlK5g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-hRg0LOUwVXo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/XvLwkfEP0Xg/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to HGTV Handmade, a crafting and DIY collab channel with three new projects every week. Check out our new 2017 schedule below then subscribe and get ready to be inspired!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>DazzleDIY</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC2snD6_rLmxWSUQ-VYXZa4w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-5pINZ4CVpZU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/5mkb_Y_Hr1A/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>SUBSCRIBE if you LOVE DIYS!
Home Decor, Organization, Fashion, School, Art, and Fun!

Hello everyone! Thanks for stopping by my channel.  My name is Aubrey and I am going to college for Graphic Design, while having a love for DIY projects and improving on my video editing skills.
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>IdunnGoddess</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC_FNd7A9b0adbxmpuzIm5ZA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Ytv4dwBU-JM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/S1pTAkGMo9I/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>SUBSCRIBE if you LOVE DIYS!
Home Decor, Organization, Fashion, School, Art, and Fun!

Hello everyone! Thanks for stopping by my channel.  My name is Aubrey and I am going to college for Graphic Design, while having a love for DIY projects and improving on my video editing skills.
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Nim C</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCr8knzz5ua7wvmW-QHyzoIQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-X8rHn7I3il8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/ntQbAG1j7EM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi there! Welcome to my channel ❤️

My name is Nim and I’m 19 years old. I love making clay charms and easy DIY projects. You can expect a new video every Wednesday and Sunday.

I hope you like & enjoy my videos XO</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Maqaroon</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCO7iqpYcqmeRz0my_who9kQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-uGrDLecRa14/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Xe4HpLlTKYM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Maqaroon & Cute Life Hacks is a place where girls can get creative inspiration, DIY ideas and good life advice without the glorification of money, beauty or body image.

Hello! I'm Joanna Zhou, a professional illustrator/designer based in Austria. My dream is to inspire girls to live creatively and develop ambitions for work and business. I believe all girls should build their self-confidence based on their intelligence & creativity instead of defining themselves by their appearance. I like fashion as much as everyone but at the end of the day, our looks are only temporary. Focusing on inner skills that grow with time is what will truly make you happy!

♥ DIY Slime

♥ Budget Gift Ideas

♥ Life Hacks

♥ Fun Games & Apps

♥ Cute Food

♥ ASMR</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Innova Crafts</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC5R0wgIYygsLVRwaKtSSGVA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-vnSqwJQwPN4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/yMdObKZGCe4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>DIY crafts channel: Here you will find very easy diy and crafts. You check out my channel and subscribe free!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>SweetBioDesign ♥ DIY Tutorials</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCXI7TZER-P4juRUe5-3B2aw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-JoAaEj6lnzQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/heAqv0bTpO4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to SweetBioDesign, the handmade channel! Every Wednesday (plus extra days), we'll create fun items, ranging from scrapbooking, the polymer clay and much more! I also provide various templates if necessary to facilitate your work. So what are you waiting? Join me, Subscribe!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Isa's World</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCNkz_Y5S4ssNuFmIThlVqnA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-2mKrdeV6tOY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/x7eJhbkVrq4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello , my name is Isa and I want to make my channel a useful place to find tutorials, tips and tricks of makeup , hair, beauty , personal care and fashion
There are also recipes, original ideas doing arts and crafts with recycled products ... but all in an easy and fun way.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Mad Stuff With Rob</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCT8FGLq9AU1H6U3ePhegxJA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-K-Sq-N21soA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/W_iHBEZUJlY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>You would remember me from POGO on M.A.D. but I have now started my own YouTube channel. So for all those who want to catch up on the new stuff that I've been doing then I suggest you subscribe! We upload a new DIY video every Wednesday and Friday at 5:00 pm!

Happy DIY-ing!

Here is how you can be a part of our DIY family!.
Shoot a fun video of you saying,

'Hi I am _______ and it's time for some DIY. Why? Cause I love it!"

You can shoot this solo or with your friends and then send it to madstuffwithrob@gmail.com. Make sure the video is good quality and do shoot it in horizontal format. The best videos get picked up and get featured on my channel.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Artkala</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCbP0hjFiW9CEnL9HpSPbK_Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-erJx2ct5J8c/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Oa6fTwnstAI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Description
Hey guys, Welcome to the world of innovation Artkala. We are Puja,Pawan & Sneha creators of Artkala. This channel is all about DIY, lifehack, tutorials,  nail art and other awesome ideas that pop on my mind.We always strive to upload the best quality content on our channel.
                                          The best part of our channel is that we transform the old and useless waste materials into a new creative and daily need usefull material and we upload a new video everyday. Every DIY tutorial is very easy and simple to follow, perfect for beginners, explained step by step and achievable at home!
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Arte y Salud en Casa (English)</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCBJp95Ct1QBLUjZq6KJbwRQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-rplI-eQ5Q6Q/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/9B3iGrMatH4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello,my name is Cony and welcome to my channel.

YES! I have another channel but it´s in Spanish( http://www.youtube.com/c/arteysaludencasa1)

Arte y Salud en Casa means art and health from home :)

Please subscribe :) here, you will find easy DIY´s, crafts using easy to find supplies and much more.

Thank you for stopping by.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>StylEnrich</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC1uCxo_EG5y8HN4Wn9jaeag/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-IfG2HGkWtyg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/bbyb9D0TtqI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>StylEnrich is a team of Creative individuals who are extremely passionate about Arts, Crafts and all things DIY. We love to make beautiful crafts and share it with our audience.

We love to explore new techniques of craft making. Creating unique and innovative crafts is what we love. We make all types of crafts including –

• Paper Crafts,
• DIY Home Décor,
• Wall Hangings and Room Decorations
• Clay Craft,
• Ceramic / Plaster of Paris crafts
• Artificial Jewellery,
• Diwali and Christmas Crafts,
• Best out of waste crafts
• Recycled Craft Ideas
• Kids Craft
• Kids school projects

…and the list goes on…

We love it when you appreciate our work. We enjoy every thumbs up we get for our craft videos and we love to read every comment that you leave for us.

We promise to bring new and interesting crafts for you everyday. So please stay tuned and join us on this beautiful journey of creativity.

Happy Crafting!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>[COLORsnowReadyFor DIY]</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCJT_NuyIqx6gOILxLGOog6g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-A--Eb7gtpT8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/9KL8H1Dwi6A/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>DIY ideas for home decor, jewelry,Organization and Wall Art</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>BuzzFeed Nifty</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UChDhriK1Ar625KyY7JdnT7A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ibseYFRSyls/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/vTZgtZ6zBWA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Make it your own.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>SuzelleDIY</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC11YXOTZw0d_GL8iVsRv5iw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-HElTnmmJP0M/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/ati17GvVzus/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>A Bitesize Do-It-Yourself Webseries.

I love braaing, dinner parties and DIY. I also love to go out for a koffie with my best friend Marianne.

Produced by Sketchbook Studios</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Love Yourself</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCkh3K8SLjWbzmL7odQbNFAg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-6WxIXhZr8_0/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/7F9E7th1Mys/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello friends!!

Thank you for your support.
I love to make new things and want to share it with you.
New videos  twice in a week.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DIY Paper Crafts - Giulia's Art</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCD0xaFh0m2cSscYWsqcxedg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-vdTxJ6w4_5U/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/pKKA2OE1r6Y/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>DIY Crafts Tutorials , Crafting Tools Reviews and Vlogs.

I'm trying to upload new video every Saturday and random video on other days!

Learn Amazing Crafts - Paper Crafts, Valentine Crafts, Easter Crafts, Origami, Quilling, Crafts for Kids, Craft Projects, Home Decor Crafts, Paper Flowers, Christmas Crafts, New Year Cards, Valentine's Day Cards, Scrapbooks, Greeting Cards, Mother's Day Cards, Father's Day Cards, Pop-up Cards, Exploding boxes, Handmade Photo Albums, Gift Boxes and Packing, etc.

My name Is Giulia! I'm so glad to have you on my channel! Im from Romania but currenty I live with my husband in Nottingham, UK. Making videos is our passion, We love editing and making content that can help you making the perfect gifts for your loved ones.
I love to make gift ideas, room decor, DIYs, and life hacks videos!
Thank you guys for subscribing and believing in me. I love you all so much!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Parker's Tutorials</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCcCk-KqsBX4KsYt_aJqJI-w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-h-qgm2dSNts/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/l1-VAOEE_H8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey everyone, welcome to the Parker's Tutorials YouTube channel. Since the Summer of 2008 when I was 13, I have made DIY tutorials for movie props. Today, I am 19 years old and currently operate a video production company called PMFilms. After making more tutorials during the Summer of 2013, I will be attending Pratt Institute in Brooklyn New York and majoring in film. Please enjoy my channel!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DIY Crafts TV</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCv7tyVGWpJMiPIQXBHQ308Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-mppavV2FDCA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/PdPTu2orVUc/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Only FRESH OWN DIY Crafts: Room decor, Desk organization, Gifts Tutorials, DIY Bags & Backpacks, Home DIY Crafts, Clothes Recycle Tutorials, School DIYs and other. New video every 5 days. Here you will find really interesting and usefull DIY Ideas.

I try to publish the new DIY Tutorial often. Hope you'll like my DIY Ideas. You can find the following types DIY Crafts on my Channel: Clothes Upcycle, how to make a bag, to make the case for your phone and cosmetics bag, DIY Gifts, DIY School supplies and many another most interesting DIY Ideas for you.
Subscribe to my Channel to keep in new videos. Bye!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Hetal's Art</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCRqEfb8TRJ-WA597UT2kP6w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-mUZNHuKaKSE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/tOBf35dJz5w/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to my channel friends, I am Hetal.
Here you can learn amazing DIY (Do It Yourself) art and craft for home decoration ideas....
Stay tuned with us for more quality videos..</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DIY-Paper Crafts</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCvScO0Q9oYu0A2bLjWwAJXA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-wPdiNbsu0Ac/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/B52fmk-z4NQ/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>DIY-Paper Crafts is channel that show you how make some art and crafts from crepe paper, tissue paper  and origami paper, . We upload videos daily.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Sonali's Creations</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCDxcRZ2QzMDKE7tmc0c6D4Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-aLwMQLsjFd8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/bPF1VJgwuks/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to my channel friends ! I am Sonali and my channel will give you easy and interesting Indian DIY craft that you can try yourself at home.

I also like to spend my time in creative activities such as rangoli drawing,Mehandi, DIY activities, craftmaking etc.DIY crafts and much more creative stuff which you can learn by watching my videos. </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Julia DIY / Easy DIY crafts - How to make</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCcqXzmgHplfMrzqSlOZj95w</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-iK15qYytmyc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/AnwhnmiZI30/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello guys, I'm Julia and I love creativity. I love easy DIY crafts .
On my channel you will find video tutorials .

How to make easy DIY craft ideas :
how to make bag ,
how to make phone case
how to make gift box ,
how to make greeting card ,
how to make paper flower ,
how to make origami ,
how to make piggy bank ,
how to make organizer - diy desk organizer ,
how to make notebook , school supplies , back to school diy ,
decor room diy ,
diy paper craft ideas , - paper diy crafts ,
how to make ribbon flowers ,
how to make ribbon bows .

Easy diy gift ideas - christmas gifts , valentine's day gifts ideas, mothers day craft </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>treshaja</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC4g2yGcc_EdE2nOBcEHWcqQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-CWK_2KeIjLs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/pZwUYDViuYI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to my channel!! I offer inexpensive "do-it-yourself" (DIY) home decor projects that you can easily follow to create or makeover items that will look high-end. I personally love having high-end classy pieces in my home but I don't always want to pay a lot of money for it. I'm sure you can relate to that.

I've dedicated myself to help inspire YOU to believe in YOUR abilities and step out of your comfort zone. Everything you see is done solo while having a full time job.

I am not a professional interior designer or decorator. So, if I can do it, you can too! We all have something special.

A New Video Is Uploaded Every Tuesday at 6:30 AM EST! I hope you enjoy the channel and decide to be apart of the family :-)

Let's keep inspiring each other...XoXo..... Tresha J. A.

Let's Connect!!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Creative DIY Crafts</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC17pSBUglMQLz2v56Li-eTg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ouZudmUNF8o/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/z11t56YgIyI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi, I am Saranya Kuppusamy, homemaker of a beautiful family.
When I was a kid, I used to try doing something with coconut leaves, plantain leaves, and whatever I got there around me in my village. Now, with my kids, I enjoy doing the same thing from whichever I get in my home.

Whatever crafts I try to make, I realize one thing each time, "In Crafting, there are no mistakes, it is your own unique creation".

Do You want to show Your crafts to us, Please send us the pics to the maid id: k.saranya85@gmail.com. We can show up Your crafts with your name in our future videos.
Thanks alot ! And If You find this channel useful, please share with your friends too.
Do something creative everyday !!!
Take Care !</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DIY Ideas - Tutorials - DIY Inspiration</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC7dOWq08N42eEwfnfYMiZ_g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-cU2vqhij09M/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/eMCMBbkuhxs/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi DIY-Fans,

here you can find inspiration and ideas on topics like, diy room décor, diy school supplies, diy phone case, diy clothes, diy crafts, crochet, anti-stress balls, pimp my Playmobil, gift ideas, diy Barbie clothes, Clay, hauls, diy fashion, diy jewelry, diy slime, diy playmobil, handmade stuff, crafting, experiments and much more cool stuff for kids and teens!

You can write a comment, if you have any wishes what you would like to see!
Our channel is kids friendly and we hope to see you soon.

We love creativity! If you also love DIY please SUBSCRIBE for updates throughout the week.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DaNi B. Jade- DIY, Dollar Tree DIY, Home Decor</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCwBT71oHy5W9PYi7tnjWM4g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-BMskhMFjHvA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/QGQYvRLFwsc/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to my channel where I talk Dollar Tree DIY with you all! I will focus on DIY for this channel with Home Decor, as well as fashion, beauty, natural hair, makeup and lifestyle. All of my videos are focused on DIY from the Dollar Tree, Home Decor and anything that is Beauty, Natural hair and makeup related!
I am sure you will love these Home Decor videos, Home Decor projects, Home Decor on a budget, Home Decor ideas, Home Decor hacks, and more! I am just a regular girl who loves to craft! Also, you can find me making videos on life hacks, DIY hacks, and anything else! </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>GreenCrystalRose</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCHSJAub1pBx8UdJSefCegeQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-RWVru6y6t3s/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/ucQb02ijtTo/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi my name is Lissa and Welcome to a little bit of everything: from HOW TO videos to DIYS to decorating and organizing to product reviews. Here you can watch me CREATE NEW and RECREATE INSPIRED LOOKS for LESS. I will also share some plant based recipes. You can visit my instagram to find some meal ideas. My faith in Jesus Christ is extremely important to me and I would like to share that to encourage and motivate others. I hope you enjoy your time here and that I can help inspire you. I would like to keep this channel friendly, uplifting, positive and drama free. Constructive and thoughtful comments are always welcome all others will not be.  Be Blessed!
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Best DIY Ideas</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCaPihf21w4H1480O7YjxoWg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-OzClY1GCHeE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Yjbpw6m04iQ/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>This channel is all about DIY things.
Great ideas for gifts , home decoration, holiday decoration, Christmas ornaments, greeting cards, fashion jewelry, gift boxes and envelopes, personalized origami gifts, flowers with a secret message , origami for mums  and other awesome ideas.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Orchid Place</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCerJ8gfSKGvCasF0juFkXzg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-N_algJ3Y_Xg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/s3URiK05nuM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I am a thrifty DIYer who enjoys making things beautiful.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>FRISHTA - DIY CRAFT</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCrBIWfcuTHs5qugVLa3igXw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-9puBbmmeJLA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/RDuWuR1m96Q/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>my new channel : https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5rgJPtnbtCw
hey , thanks for stopping by my channel i do handmade crafts
such as paper flowers and gift box and IKEA hacks and many
more handmade creative ideas please like comment and
......................................SUBSCRIBE.............................................
ABIT ABOUT ME :
im a 22 year old female from Kurdistan but grew up in the UK
iv always had a passion for diy craft handmade stuff i do a lot of giveaways and free templates.

lets be friends
inst-gram | frishta diy craft
face book page | frishta diy craft
Facebook group | diy on a budget </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>FRISHTA DIY CRAFT</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCt6qK_H3gKf7ZTjaVf7Qv9Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-CBkV4_4ismY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/twAiNaTsM5Q/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary> </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Valena DIY</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCQAa67WLIsrWMQayegNQ3Wg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-8NXDUyYUmfU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/fuxLXzc2tTg/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome in the wonderful world of the loom !

On my channel, you'll find lots of tutorials for learning to knit on a round loom and inspire you for realize beautiful works.
I invite you to subscribe and knit with me !</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DIY WITH JAMMY</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCTWS7tcS-1RHr4qfLBdh3JQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-48NWKynGwno/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/_hHTudLeYck/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Crafts & kitchen</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>ClassyCrafting&Parcels</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCj8-HU4hmw42LZhOwFIFShQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-SX_0IhVFSgU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/72EoEfklQrw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi my name is Vanessa - I am so glad to have you join me. I love planning, DIYs, Pocket Letters and shopping for deals.   I love Dollar Tree and Dollarama, I look forward to sharing my hauls with you and I look forward to seeing your creations on my Facebook Page (ClassyCrafting&Parcels). Chat with you soon. 🤗✨</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Crazy about DIY</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCa0I64m3RkQDTu0Fc3MDn7Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-8DWgC8PMzHo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/179V_cWzzwI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>This channel is dedicated to creativity, How To and How-to :), DIY (Do-It-Yourself), Crafts, Recycling Handmade Stuff, Life Hacks, Tricks and Tips. We film and upload new video every day! Hope our videos will inspire you to create something beautiful with your own hands! #Howto #DIY</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DIY Haunter</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCPuCSbVV05td19gEEv39GlQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-RYhUJYX_PDk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/ud-fNpIUN08/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>DIY tutorials and demonstrations for making Halloween props, decorations and costumes for your own yard haunt, or haunted event.
Check out my new website http://diyhaunter.com</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DIY Paper Crafts Tutorials</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3X5wu4-visIuRrQbJ5g5-w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-EQaFxeR-PRQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/mRxmgEs6Vd0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>DIY Paper Crafts Tutorials in this channel i show you how to learn DIY Crafts Idea from origami paper, color tissue paper, color crepe paper and others paper.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Alexa DIYS & CRAFTS</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCq_bALWoPgbuEK714kE2F-A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Cj-WTjGit0M/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/1xOEMk3ox3k/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>My channel is dedicated to creativity, DIY (Do-It-Yourself), Crafts, Tricks and Tips. Hope my videos will inspire you to create something beautiful with your own hands! #Howto #DIY</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Creative DIY Now</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCj5x-4vX6JcniMoBVc_Nh4g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-jIAmS6knPjs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/wFLxAwjPORk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello Everyone, on my channel you will find lots of creative DIY, Tips, Paper Crafts, Handmade Cards, Origami, Room Decor, Doodles other Art And Crafts. I am not a pro but will tell you what i know. Please feel free to Share your ideas and suggestion. If i use your idea i will mention your name. Be Creative Now !</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>MakeTech</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC_RbkyX5b3Fh4EGI5xYPfVw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-_RIrDuowtos/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/tFQjjm-3aYs/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Making fun stuff with Laser Engravers, 3D Printers, CNC Machines and other tech!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>carverswoodshop</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCcTwSeJXnwxmh9CVVdBfmZw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-H-OoQVjkynk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/8KjEPuBQ8SI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Please ck my online store for dvds, sharpening wheels tools, and my carvings for sale 72 dvds to chose from each 10.00 free shipping in usa only.
https://squareup.com/market/arleen-zomer
always wear a carvers glove and a thumb guard for protection,    email me carverswoodshop@yahoo.com or call or text 484-364-0471  keep carving, arleen</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Lynn O. Doughty</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCsVoj06No2zZR4Uei_nqtLA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-lz3UNgyI1Bg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/2rzOXV0QVzk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Gary McDaniel</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC0c4UIt4p4LjDuvKy3SOhYw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Gy5CZyt_r7A/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/0Oqpt6yqzLo/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>A place to view my woodcarving tutoriald and see my "Carving Video Blog.
You can Purchase the Tutorials on DVD here: http://www.3crosseswoodcarving.com</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>stixandstonescarving</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCiXcrGWJda2lxR0LwSejDig/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-X3WE1aARajk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/3sVqBorD9rU/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I designed this channel to help others learn and enjoy the art of woodcarving. I've been a woodcarver for many years and always have had a love for art of any kind but have had to learn without teachers. So I thought I'd present some tips and help to those who don't have access to carving instruction where they live.  I hope the information is helpful and rewarding to those that view it and maybe in my own way keep this wonderful art alive for the next generation .. thanks for subscribing and your input....Kevin</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>dennis stallings</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCh7KmiL31l-y9-7XDk-YQqA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-jNoVczYI88w/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/7Fu_xt8Ugjc/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>IF YOUR INTERESTED IN WOODCARVING,FISHING INSHORE AND/OR OFFSHORE,AND PHOTOGRAPHING/VIDEO RECORDINGS OF THESE ADVENTURES.THESE ARE MY FAVORITE THINGS TO DO.SO PLEASE SUBSCRIBE AND ENJOY..MORE OFFSHORE VIDEOS IN PLANNING FOR JUNE 2013...THANKS FOR YOUR SUPPORT.....</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Kevin Coates</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCHIwp6WJZdGvySIdpmxq5Yw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-yRSgsIPGi5c/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/592z9haVQ8c/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Gene Messer</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCPWRb0-aQENDroHifzY2UvA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-XzyqqWZgQNE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/DrJWRqTKGq0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Been a woodcarver for 15 years and love it ..
My interest is teaching this wonderful old art to the youth of today and anyone who wants to learn ...

Woodcarving is a art as old as the beginning of time .. Jesus himself was a carpenter and woodcarver ..Today it is more of a hobbby then a profession .. but still loved by those who continue to perserve the art .. My love of style is flat plane carving .. a style originated in Europe ( mostly Sweden)by most of the figure carvers of that time.. it's distinct characteristics are using  basically only a knife and leaving  the cuts in the figure when finished rather then smooth it out ..
Anyone can learn to carve with the right instruction  .. These videos are meant to help the beginner see how knife carving is done with a variety of projects .. And learn the fun of carving a figure out of wood and other projects ..

So put down the joy sticks, turn off the cell phones , put up the video games  and turn off the music and learn to work with your hands ..</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Marloes Wonen</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCRQ71LUR4DMDOymIaDz68gw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-1jTWBQhdxT4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/pNR81oeqLSA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>The Daily DIYer</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC51ehsuNfaIqrzIMAcHF9rw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-GX9pHTS6ThI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/XujrKi0l_tg/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Daily Do It Yourself projects.

Featured tutorials will include:  home décor, holiday projects, art, wood working, party planning, mantel designs, tablescapes, photography, store hauls, favorite products, organizing, toddler activities, homemade beauty products, baking, tips and tricks, before and afters, and MORE!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Do It On A Dime</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCJA8OyDxRY-wm0ya2gtHOsw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-zXuS2_Cxb-Y/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/7rGXHl0SfqU/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi, I'm Kathryn!  I'm on a mission to lead a beautiful, organized lifestyle on a frugal budget.  Let me show you how I live life on a dime!

Follow my blog for budget organizing, money saving finds, free printables, and more from me!: http://www.doitonadimeblog.com/
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>ClutterBug </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC_ldgDzMaFzAEHEnIjSlWoA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-4z-aitMuuHo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Bz6KDruJRvo/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>ClutterBug offers organizing tips, tricks and advice each and every week! Join me as I show you how to get rid of clutter, learn how to organize your home and simplify your life!

Want easy DIY Pinterest worthy tips on a small budget? You're in the right place! Hit that subscribe button now!
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>WhatsUpMom</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCMfXv2enRXepxG92VoxfrEg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-eWC9qtKalw8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/JMREB-fmOVY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Thanks to you, we are the #1 parenting channel on YouTube with over 1.5 million subscribers and 35 million views per month, woo!  Created by moms, we aim to inspire, inform, and hopefully make you laugh-- the kind of relieving "phew, someone else gets it" kind of laugh.  Please subscribe (it's free and appreciated!)  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>The DIY Mommy</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCbnY-O1Pse1lekxYWqVJwgg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-OZ9XVj_DBwA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/CQqyS0FkFhA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Making things for mommy, for baby and for home! New videos every week.

Welcome to my YouTube channel. Here and on my blog, you'll find tutorials on how to make things for mommy, how to make things for baby and how to make things for home.

I'm sharing with you easy and inexpensive DIY ideas that I hope you'll love and find useful and fun.

From home decor ideas, to sewing tutorials, to kids activities to mommy sanity savers - you'll find all of that and more right here on my YouTube channel and TheDIYMommy.com.

I invite you to subscribe to my channel and join The DIY Mommy Community.

Thanks so much for stopping by and I can't wait to hang out with you here!</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Roger Webb</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCVbRweyeFzc6j7_VYQjwxYQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-DtGKT_vE5iU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/b6btAGRJWSw/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to my workshop, all kinds of projects is my interest, woodturning, woodwork, metalwork, CNC Routers and Lasers.
32 Million views over120,000 subscribers is proof that there is something of interest for you here ;-)

 Please send an email to: info@pacifictooling.com  Wood Lathes, CNC routers, 4040, 6060, 6090, 6012, 1212, 1224, 1325 and now CNC 6040, 6090 , 1390,Lasers (linear rail model) and machine tool accessories . 
Australian Inventor Roger Clyde Webb Pacific Tooling

Disclaimer:
These videos are intended for entertainment and inspiration. Woodworking and metalworking is dangerous. Always seek professional advice and training before using any power tools or CNC machine. If you have any uncertainty before performing any DIY procedure, stop and learn a safer method.  Understand that there are years of learning and experimentation by me that are not in the videos. Do not attempt anything simply because you saw it in one of my videos.
Roger Clyde Webb Inventor Australia 2012</summary>
</plugin>
