
<plugin>
  <title>Youtube Documentary Playlist</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/playlist/PLMAWrySkMfZP8lMRveOUhCrZAEwIn_jZM/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/qgAMspKekhapIIu6oDpA1L9jTVqOdGsfRAV0UnNunasrAK7vmHAnF3roDJmcUUxWX0Asbzh1HTuGJIQ1Lws88-nd-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <fanart></fanart>
</plugin>

<plugin>
<title>Youtube Documentary Playlist 2</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/playlist/PLR3SowCQah02FYPAFXOFH2Vy1qcAmIJ_A/</link>
<thumbnail>https://i.pinimg.com/736x/1e/70/a8/1e70a87d45aa800dfa72d08703818ec2--funny-hats-mesh-hats.jpg</thumbnail>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Historia Civilis</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCv_vLHiWVBh_FR9vbeuiY-A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mCOuC84RYcgsPnDdte_mzoVwbAFLs5M2NF1vQ=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Rome Freak.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Kurzgesagt – In a Nutshell</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCsXVk37bltHxD1rDPwtNM8Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mBwm16pirqqYi7Yli1eRKWClJYLV2jNxpsR2w=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Videos explaining things with optimistic nihilism. 

We are a small team who want to make science look beautiful. Because it is beautiful. 

Currently we make one animation video per month. Follow us on Twitter, Facebook to get notified when a new one comes out.

FAQ:
 
- We do the videos with After Effects and Illustrator.</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Techquickie</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC0vBXGSyV14uvJ4hECDOl0Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mDz8L0rfOXq1K3You9ZNzhKq6xqrxsAWtsCxg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Learn about the latest cool technology in only a couple minutes! 

Hosted by Linus Sebastian</summary>
</plugin>




<plugin>
  <title>Primitive Technology</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCAL3JXZSzSm8AlZyD3nQdBA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mDCVv74tHc-NkovY3Kpiqb6HOwcXplX3qDtsw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Primitive technology is a hobby where you build things in the wild completely from scratch using no modern tools or materials. These are the strict rules: If you want a fire, use a fire stick - An axe, pick up a stone and shape it - A hut, build one from trees, mud, rocks etc. The challenge is seeing how far you can go without utilizing modern technology. I do not live in the wild, but enjoy building shelter, tools, and more, only utilizing natural materials. To find specific videos, visit my playlist tab for building videos focused on pyrotechnology, shelter, weapons, food & agriculture, tools & machines, and weaving & fiber.

FAQ
Q.Where is this? 
A.This is in Far North Queensland Australia.
Q.Do you live in the wild?
A.I don't live in the wild but just go into the bush to make these projects. Also I camp out here occasionally.
Q.How did you learn all this?
A.Researching books and internet plus trial and error. I'm not indigenous and have no army training.

Check out my blog below.</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Forgotten Weapons</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCrfKGpvbEQXcbe68dzXgJuA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mC1eAgkglBOz0EvLV6v8NQICgZLm6QktQhrGg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>At Forgotten Weapons I think the most interesting guns out there are the most obscure ones. I try to search out experimental and prototype weapons and show you how they work, in addition to more conventional guns that you may not have heard of before. You're much more likely to find a video on the Cei Rigotti or Webley-Fosbery here than an AR or Glock. So, do you want to learn about something new today? Then stick around!</summary>
</plugin>




<plugin>
  <title>The Great War</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCUcyEsEjhPEDf69RRVhRh4A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mA2mB6MdGDRDeXSkyBpOY0Yt2rDQ2v7vhe-wA=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>The Great War' shows you the history of the First World War in the four years from 1914 to 1918, exactly 100 years ago. Our host Indy takes you back week by week and shows you what was going on in the past. Learn more about the Allies and the Central Powers, emperors, Winston Churchill, Wilhelm II, soldiers, battles and of the life aside the battlefield. Subscribe to our channel to watch a new video every Monday, Thursday & Saturday!

You can support our show on Patreon: http://patreon.com/thegreatwar
</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Sam O'Nella Academy</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC1DTYW241WD64ah5BFWn4JA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mBWEwEo02Tn1ioQlZYd7JPZgVG97H9Hl9Wkjg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>LEMMiNO</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCRcgy6GzDeccI7dkbbBna3Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mAwcgS6sMg0LPCJys_8vf4Zk2GE0qxqmQg6Ww=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Documentaries and list videos narrated by a 20-something Swedish guy.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Barcroft TV</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCfwx98Wty7LhdlkxL5PZyLA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-r5rStE9sVkM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/xug45fuacaM/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Barcroft TV is the home of amazing exclusive video.

We update our YouTube site regularly with incredible real-life stories and footage - so stay tuned for more!
</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Timeline - World History Documentaries</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC88lvyJe7aHZmcvzvubDFRg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAxPMVAumSTrb5TT9OBRjHzXZuc-3GgQMYHotw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to Timeline - the home of world history. Every week we'll be bringing you one-off documentaries and series from the world's top broadcasters, including the BBC, Channel 4, Discovery and PBS. We'll be exploring the mysteries of ancient Egypt, shedding light on the dark ages of medieval Europe and examining the First and Second World Wars. Subscribe so you don't miss out.

Content on our channel is licensed from:

Digital Rights Group
ITV Global Studios
All3Media International
TVF International
Java Films
Off The Fence</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Real Stories</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCu4XcDBdnZkV6-5z2f16M0g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAwBVOWeFxl-QRKIc5FHa4v5YXazOFzWzw5feA=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to Real Stories, the home of award-winning and compelling documentaries you need to see. We will be uploading at least four full length documentaries a week from the best documentary producers on the planet. Subscribe so you don't miss out.

Content on our channel is licensed from:

Digital Rights Group
DCD Rights
ITV Global Studios
All3Media International
TVF International
Java Films
Cargo Film & Releasing
Sideways Film
Truevision Productions
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Only Human</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCkRmoZiR_SOssKA89m1eYJg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAzb8LQjbwMXCIQ3WWWbQsTDYbs-s1gd6siZ8w=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Only Human celebrates and explores the unique and personal qualities we all have. Our channel investigates the individual struggles life can throw at us, and offers a range of human experiences and viewpoints from amazing people from all walks of life.
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Wild Things</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCbq-4OJxnziD3awH-aTezeA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAz5PXK_c3pc8TSV8qC19HqZNYP_YHt8z6d6Yw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>From lush rainforests to sparse deserts, from friendly pets to predatory sharks and lions, Wild Things’ documentaries will take you around the world, exploring the wonders and the dangers nature has to offer. We publish at least one full length documentary a week, subscribe so you don’t miss it!

Content Provided by:

DRG
ITV Global
All3Media
DCD Rights
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>HBODocs </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCbKo3HsaBOPhdRpgzqtRnqA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAxasZmwazld1fImFObboFr9WsJRMZixC-KIhA=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Subscribe to the HBO Documentary Films Channel for the latest news and updates on HBO's inspirational documentaries.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>CBC Docs</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCsEbwT3FHpAey6prlu7tNhw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-z3gbfHi-djE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/9S8fJ4W0ZwM/s100-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Full-length episodes of CBC documentary programming including CBC Docs POV, The Nature of Things with David Suzuki, Short Docs, and more.

Short Docs are available worldwide.

Full length documentaries are available only in Canada.</summary>
</plugin>
