#################################################################################
<cache>10800</cache>
##################################################################################

<plugin>
  <title>Pasta Grannies</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCedsqpl7jaIb8BiaUFuC9KQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-O6JJNvnPPDc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/igDB2e07Tww/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to Pasta Grannies! I find and film real Italian grannies - nonne - making delicious, traditional, handmade pasta. And sometimes soups, breads, dolci, rice dishes, that kind of thing, because that is what the Grannies wanted to cook for me. I'm saving skills and sharing traditions one recipe and Granny at a time! Pasta Grannies posts every Thursday afternoon.

</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>She's In Her Apron </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCLBlAUZM0joZhJlG220iolw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-iEfGk7-Lozg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/NgxlsaxRTuY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I'm a stay at home mom to four amazing kids. I'm a busy wife & mom like most of you! I'm REAL and I love sharing that with you all. I feel as woman we need to be honest and share with one another. We need to be each other's biggest cheerleaders.  I am on a mission to organize my home / life, share a few things from my heart and things I have created. Come and visit with me while I cook, clean, organize and being goofy. I don't have it all together but who really does. :)</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>JunsKitchen</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCRxAgfYexGLlu1WHGIMUDqw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-DjSC7mcMhnw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/m3bOy4p2-kE/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Thank you for visiting my channel! If you have a request, please leave a comment. :)
I am not professional chef. I just like cooking.
If you're also interested, I have an Instagram below, too.
Thank you!
</summary>
</plugin>