#################################################################################
<cache>10800</cache>
##################################################################################
<plugin>
  <title>My Virgin Kitchen</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCAzyupPG4vdo8jd9nJ13LAw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-EEXzm10q6dc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/MeyIBA01MMs/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>A fun food cooking channel. If you are looking for easy how to recipe tutorials mixed with food fun & easy to follow homemade cooking you may have come to the right place! I’m a self-taught cook here on YouTube inspiring you to learn how to cook with me. Recipes on my own, cooking with kids or other friends and family it’s all about trying to get you cooking easy recipes, laughing and learning and hopefully picking up some new cooking ideas.
    There’s also a dose of food fun too, so if you like giant food videos or mini food videos, taste tests, or testing the latest kitchen gadgets you’ll probably like it here!
    I used to be a Virgin in the kitchen (hence the name) and absolutely hated cooking or attempting to make any recipes no matter how simple!
    I am completely self-taught in the hope that I can inspire you guys to attempt the recipes too and get in the kitchen - cooking is all about confidence! I hope you enjoy my mix of fun food recipe videos , subscribe for regular videos
  </summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Kays Seriously Bad Cooking</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCeKWgImK1RAD9IGjWZqxmIw/</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>OnePotChefShow</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCYvqEiyy1pr5Sel8OtEuoeQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-MiUEGcrYzCo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/MlzK3lGqXg8/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Bringing you the best traditional, home-style and old forgotten classic recipes!

NEW COOKING VIDEOS UPLOADED EVERY WEEK!

Support me on Patreon and get exclusive access to my "Coffee Time" podcast:
http://www.patreon.com/onepotchef</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Pasta Grannies</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCedsqpl7jaIb8BiaUFuC9KQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-O6JJNvnPPDc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/igDB2e07Tww/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to Pasta Grannies! I find and film real Italian grannies - nonne - making delicious, traditional, handmade pasta. And sometimes soups, breads, dolci, rice dishes, that kind of thing, because that is what the Grannies wanted to cook for me. I'm saving skills and sharing traditions one recipe and Granny at a time! Pasta Grannies posts every Thursday afternoon.

</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>She's In Her Apron </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCLBlAUZM0joZhJlG220iolw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-iEfGk7-Lozg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/NgxlsaxRTuY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I'm a stay at home mom to four amazing kids. I'm a busy wife & mom like most of you! I'm REAL and I love sharing that with you all. I feel as woman we need to be honest and share with one another. We need to be each other's biggest cheerleaders.  I am on a mission to organize my home / life, share a few things from my heart and things I have created. Come and visit with me while I cook, clean, organize and being goofy. I don't have it all together but who really does. :)</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>JunsKitchen</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCRxAgfYexGLlu1WHGIMUDqw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-DjSC7mcMhnw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/m3bOy4p2-kE/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Thank you for visiting my channel! If you have a request, please leave a comment. :)
I am not professional chef. I just like cooking.
If you're also interested, I have an Instagram below, too.
Thank you!
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Man About Cake</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCcsBpRN1l9YsaLoElmJj2Jg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAx3oUrj7YWt1uABshCrZsxTSJ-UOFnHK1gjbw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Servin' up serious cakes and silly antics in new episodes every Tuesday.

Sink your teeth into current cake decorating trends with Joshua and the men behind Man About Cake! Each week JJR brings you an original cake design - FREE recipes - and step-by-step tutorials to recreate his masterpieces in your own kitchen. Oh yeah, and probably some laughs.</summary>
</plugin>
