#################################################################################
<cache>10800</cache>
<fanart>https://i.pinimg.com/originals/c4/83/cc/c483cc76c1f5dba29c94775116eedffd.png</fanart>
#################################################################################

<plugin>
  <title>Gaming Historian</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCnbvPS_rXp4PC21PG2k1UVg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-8EL8uV2zWuc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6cx197A77Uc/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>The Gaming Historian is a documentary series all about the history of video games. I also like to review books and certain games that I find interesting.

The show is researched, written, edited, and created by Norman Caruso.
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>The 8-Bit Guy</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC8uT9cgJorJPWu7ITLGo9Ww/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-CwfC3-3jalo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/9VXlpqvGSYw/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>A computer video series focusing mainly on retro technology from the 80's, 90's and 2000's. However, once or twice a year I'll create something totally "out there."  My main goal at this point is to make educational content about retro technology that is interesting and engaging.  Some people will be re-living their childhood, while others will be experiencing the technology for the first time.
</summary>
</plugin>


<item>
  <title>Overwatch League</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Johnstonevo/20AP/master/yt/owl.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://pbs.twimg.com/profile_images/798278623027335168/e_aMDar6.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/OFHpK627XkI/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Overwatch League YT channels
  </Summary>
</item>

<plugin>
  <title>PlayOverwatch</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UClOf1XXinvZsy4wKPAkro2A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-M2-DH_DN-Qs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/kczw_wtvMOI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Overwatch™ is a highly stylized team-based shooter set in a future worth fighting for. Every match is an intense multiplayer showdown pitting a diverse cast of soldiers, scientists, adventurers, and oddities against each other in an epic, globe-spanning conflict.

    ESRB rating TEEN for Blood, Violence, and Use of Tobacco. Visit esrb.org for rating information.
  </summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>xQcOW</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCmDTrq0LNgPodDOFZiSbsww/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-2OSf1dzIXF4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/EA83qKpux2g/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>My personnal youtube channel. Guides and highlights from www.twitch.tv/xQcOW
  </summary>
</plugin>




<plugin>
  <title>Curse Entertainment</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCf6J9yokPS0ys456jvjLBGQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-sN4dLBN2imU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/oxgApu53a4g/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Overwatch Moments - SparkTV</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCKNr5GHGYZUKNQAxtHj9ldw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-M_gKG3lfZSQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/wrlKrKJkFSY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Bringing you the best Overwatch moments,montages,best of heroes (like Best of Genji, Best of Tracer), highlights, and all kinds of other interesting Overwatch videos.
    Subscribe if you love to see awesome new Overwatch Moments! i upload one video every 2 days!

    Overwatch Moments - SparkTV
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Overwatch Moments - Gaming Curios</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCAuI-Z03JwnDsVAwB5G2tfw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-HTZHvhdZgjs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/35wr0KD6poA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Overwatch Moments - By Gaming Curios! Covering all kinds of Overwatch Montage and Moments.
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Overwatch Curios</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCv64wapGpUkv-_y2s5aAiWg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-_D0wXorTwl8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/CcIZ3dd9T9M/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to Overwatch Curios! Covering all kinds of Overwatch News, Commentary, and Other Topics.
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>aimbotcalvin</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCdugdXty7WGW1mES30GKgrQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-8aEHZfMQwFg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/scfvvadQJ3w/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>My name is Calvin and I'm beautiful :)
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Overwatch Central </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCZmz0RdI6LvX_rRmrlwx0Eg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-NciZzMBdVq0/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/qpPtUDmRYSw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Overwatch Central is a channel revolving around the game Overwatch by Blizzard Entertainment. We produce guides, analyses, gameplay montages and other videos regarding Overwatch. Welcome to Overwatch Central.

    Overwatch Central is not affiliated with Blizzard Entertainment.
  </summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Rag Tagg</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCaC8IE_uJ9h8s6dIs4ITOwQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-9ua-ntMHhLI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/OJiQkvFbxJE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Angry Scottish Overwatch Guides
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Overwatch Plays </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCebkAwWp6WgOJ9w_T8BpRVA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-UYABj2MWVy8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/iEGZGIhp9ho/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Bringing you the BEST & the BIGGEST Overwatch plays that the Community has to offer!
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Official Overwatch Highlights</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC0qJBJX_ssan9nbmNag804Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-dcFfumRPWSg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/gjWx6-UfiMg/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>ONLY the BEST Overwatch highlights the BEST Tournaments and PRO Players.
    Watch here the most experienced players of the moment doing the best plays and potg.

    Please, Support the Players, Casters and the Tournaments in social media if you like this videos.

    Do you play for any PRO or Competitive team and you have an amazing play to share? Upload it to Mega and send us the link to alregtita@gmail.com and we'll make the video for you!

    We love Overwatch and its community so we try to help them follow their favourites teams and players around the world in the fastest and best possible way with this YouTube Channel. So please, if we have any video that you'd like to see removed, send us a message to alregtita@gmail.com and we will solve it as soon as possible. Thank you very much.
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Overwatch Highlights</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC02vp6CdqGfbJFF5tYc8mOw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-wqOj1wZxVoY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/_juqDax6MB0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to Overwatch Highlights  channel. Here  you can find Overwatch moments and montages of fun, fail,crazy,epic and top plays and WTF videos.  Videos with casual and pro players and many other interesting Overwatch  movies.
    Check our Overwatch WTF Moments Videos. In the future we plan to bring more Overwatch series to the audience.
    Remember to subscribe to be notified when we release new  videos!

    Have any good fun/fail/win Overwatch  moments to submit? Do it here : http://www.heroeswtf.com/overwatch/
    In case you cannot submit replay through this website, send  at: OverwatchWTF@yahoo.com

    Overwatch Highlights TV channel
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Overwatched - Overwatch Funny Moments</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCozax2wW2kvAMm8J2AVaKBw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-dADBo0k6DLQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/fkC4sD1Gf14/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Overwatch Top Plays, Memes, Funny Moments & Spotlights of Blizzard's game "OVERWATCH". The best for you or nothing!

    If u wanna play with me: My battletag Gracen#2570
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Rapida </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCYCwDl5Cu_QnS-Hm76TnU5Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-NpxpultiIB0/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/mQ4ds6871H0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Subscribe, like and share with others!
    Send your moments at: rapidatv@gmail.com

    Enjoy your stay here!

    Top Plays, Top Fails, Funny Moments of Blizzard's game "OVERWATCH". The best for you or nothing!</summary>
  </plugin>


  <plugin>
    <title>SSSniperWolf</title>
    <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCpB959t8iPrxQWj7G6n0ctQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-XlnWO_U5h5o/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/VqHYBQYtrZQ/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
    <summary>Hi I'm SSSniperWolf! You can call me Lia, Sniper Wolf, whatever! Here you'll find awesome gaming videos, vlogs, reacting, and anything else entertaining- plus I upload every single day! If you're interested then subscribe to join the Wolf Pack!</summary>
  </plugin>

  <plugin>
    <title>Blame The Controller - Overwatch</title>
    <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCmSwqv2aPbuOGiuii2TeaLQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-MHIPpVzLK7U/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/XHj6X59K2ko/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
    <summary>Only the best in gaming

      #Overwatch </summary>
    </plugin>


    <plugin>
      <title>Your Overwatch</title>
      <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCEzOHrh9snmHJSGu9wmOvsw/</link>
      <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-oSITWHrc7wU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/CNkaJFS6O40/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
      <summary>Three YouTubers combine efforts to cover Overwatch from top to bottom, new player tips, esports coverage, news and balance discussion. Eddythechump, Weagal & FREEDO.</summary>
    </plugin>


    <plugin>
      <title>VICTORQ - Overwatch Dose</title>
      <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC2akmVDfQuOv60-33qJUmYA/</link>
      <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-WS4uFGTXGSQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/bk89BqTHxKc/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
      <summary>Welcome to the biggest Overwatch library!
        Overwatch Highlights ; Gameplays  ; Guides & Montages

        •Overwatch Gameplays are selected from PRO players, wich can help you to improve your skills.
        Each video is provided for your enjoyment and archive purpose!

        •Twitch.tv VODs copyright belongs to the streamers. Credits can be found in description. If you want one of the gameplays removed contact me at my e-mail address below.

        •I am uploading from Monday to Saturday each week.

        If you need a content editor for your stream feel free to contact me at my e-mail address below.

        Thank you!</summary>
      </plugin>

      <plugin>
        <title>OW Dose - Overwatch Moments</title>
        <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCoHXIA9XaI9KeRcmsv46VjA/</link>
        <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-M_1zF4yg4Qg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/mPlEE6bEnhM/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
        <summary>Get your Daily Dose of Overwatch Moments!

          Moments are selected from the Overwatch Community (streamers, pro players etc.).
          If you want your moment (funny / best) on our channel you can submit it at the following e-mail adress: OwDoseManagement@gmail.com.

          Overwatch Funny Moments, Overwatch OP Moments, Overwatch Bronze Moments, Overwatch Pro Players, Overwatch Fail Plays, Overwatch Epic Moments, Overwatch Best Moments, Overwatch Montage Highlights, Overwatch Moments, Overwatch Plays, Overwatch Highlights, Overwatch Clips, Overwatch Montage Moments,  Overwatch Solo Carry, Overwatch Top Fails, Overwatch Pro Plays, Overwatch Top Plays, Overwatch Best Plays
        </summary>
      </plugin>

      <plugin>
        <title>Akshon Esports</title>
        <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC6dI8msF1_I9HuDSvMtk_nQ/</link>
        <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-vbPR9KAUE4w/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/rFaHAdT8eOc/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
        <summary>Our mission at Akshon Esports is to communicate and share the stories within the esports and gaming community through unique and engaging content.
        </summary>
      </plugin>

      <plugin>
        <title>ryujehong</title>
        <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCtt0Hg9MhraTkzWwNQpplHg/</link>
        <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-CBDM2e64uG4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6nPRef4pbk8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
        <summary>This is the official channel of Seoul Team/Lunatic-Hai ryujehong</summary>
      </plugin>

      <plugin>
        <title>ohnickel</title>
        <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3xbjTJT2pVNR6b94Vaei5g/</link>
        <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Za2ySGH-VDs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/2ZbQP7fKu04/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
        <summary>My name is Nickel. I make commentary videos on Overwatch and gaming in general.

        </summary>
      </plugin>


      <plugin>
        <title>Completed It Mate</title>
        <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC88b1rl5tpgGxK5I-fL7hIw/</link>
        <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-a4EXWALSoXw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/IlDSxVxiUno/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
        <summary>Gaming channel from the idiot from the inbetweeners ... no not that idiot, no ... not the tall one ... not the one with glasses, the one with the blonde bowl hair cut. Yes! That's the one! Watch me talk and play (badly) great video games old and new. Yes if everyone else can start YouTube channels about any old nonsense I want to join in!

          I'm not just a fan of your new fangled current games, in 4D and super graphics and what not. I love playing old games too

          I try to bring out 2 videos a week usually, every Monday will be a brand new episode and then Fridays will be my "Let's Complete" series where i try to complete a game

          Please be kind, have fun and Game On</summary>
        </plugin>


        <plugin>
          <title>CurryShotTV</title>
          <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC86xaj3k3cOFaecL6di4Xfw/</link>
          <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-W6Xwwy-Yn2A/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/pRoKsDz1kf8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
          <summary></summary>
        </plugin>




        <plugin>
          <title>Unit Lost - Great British Gaming</title>
          <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCeJTUiYP64xtfzpL-AagZGA/</link>
          <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-iQlp6VIqX8A/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/iGsL8xUg9To/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
          <summary>Unit Lost GREAT BRITISH GAMING! Overwatch is my thing! Daily videos!

            Join our gaming community forums - http://www.unitlost.com
            We also Live Stream over here http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost
            Make sure you follow us on twitter too! @unitlostgaming
          </summary>
        </plugin>


        <plugin>
          <title>Pine</title>
          <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC0nhCDjyWZ-LZ9Ww0DqpAuA/</link>
          <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Re3FsFXB8-w/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/lKtxqJxiL3g/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
          <summary>#21 on New York Excelsior,  @NYXL: New York's official @OverwatchLeague team.
          </summary>
        </plugin>


        <plugin>
          <title>Kephrii</title>
          <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCUGHabcIVqEiJAoDqcpSqyw/</link>
          <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-4t4W015gZCU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/5TXkBp5KolE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
          <summary>Hey guys! I'm Brian, commonly known as Kephrii! I'm a competitive FPS Player mainly playing Overwatch.
          </summary>
        </plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Project HyperPie</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC5C_OjQLafFMx3uLgXABsSg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-h1b1hJbh6B8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/znDvyqQPQNs/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>This channel is dedicated to some creative individuals in the Project HyperPie Facebook group. It is maintained and updated by those same guys 👍</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>David Marti</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCCdzkEbBKmEPrxOXFsTpEEw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/--KnPEaD9yqo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/N7Baw9JOFug/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Mostly devoted to the base RetroPie image I created called Motion Blue.

The Motion Blue base image is a RetroPie image that has been created and setup with several design goals in mind. Many new scripts and files have been developed to include new features and enhancements.  The base image has been setup and configured for both Emulation Station and Attract Mode will all emulators and romlists/gamelists pre-made.

A design philosophy was adopted for this build to bring RetroPie in line with the current retro gaming community. The most prominent change was to begin using the community standard for filenames for all configuration files and ROM files. This change now has RetroPie matching the EmuMovies/HyperSpin naming convention. With this change, end users are more easily able to download new ROMs and media files that will immediately work, thus saving hours of file renaming.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Simply Austin</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCb4RFFBZEztOW77onViqoDA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-0zGMz83jD_k/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/22X5HQ1q5dY/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>The Simply Austin Channel is a unique blend cutting edge video tutorials on some of the most entertaining systems and programs out there. The channel began in April 2015 on Youtube and exploded in popularity. After realizing that I could make an impact on the industry through entertaining and informative videos, I had finally found my calling.

Bringing YOU everything YOU need!

Unlike many channels out there I do not do this for any money. I do it for the love of the scene and the wanting I have to better it and expand it.  I will always offer my help in any way I can and would like a loyal fanbase who would work with me to make this a better place for us all, not just Pewdy bate!

From what started as a series aimed at the tens of people its now watched by the tens of thousands!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Game Sack</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCT6LaAC9VckZYJUzutUW3PQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-7CPvkI7EVl4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/vePJ5YCuFVA/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>We're Joe and Dave. We talk about video games we find interesting and a few that may not be so great.  Long new episode every other Sunday released at 12:00am mountain time (US). Thanks for checking out Game Sack!
  </summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>MetalJesusRocks</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCEFymXY4eFCo_AchSpxwyrg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ibnBAnZx5hI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/z4xGzX0oFrI/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>The Metal Jesus is a long-haired rocker dude who runs a popular YouTube channel dedicated to Retro Gaming with a Heavy Metal soundtrack. With the help of the Seattle gaming community he covers Hidden Gems, Buying Guides as well as the popular I HATE U series, Gamer Eats and much more. He was also an employee at mega publisher Sierra On-Line in the 90s and he brings his love of big box PC gaming to his channel as well.  New videos on Tuesday & Friday every week!
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Gaming Historian</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCnbvPS_rXp4PC21PG2k1UVg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-8EL8uV2zWuc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6cx197A77Uc/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>The Gaming Historian is a documentary series all about the history of video games. I also like to review books and certain games that I find interesting.

The show is researched, written, edited, and created by Norman Caruso.

If you like what I do and would like to support the show, please consider joining my Patreon. http://www.patreon.com/gaminghistorian</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>TheAngryHoneyBadger</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC7foeIw1ZW7BaqHAUfFgRzg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-UuM8Wa8M6Dw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/d1fW0uYrBgQ/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>PC hardware & Technology reviews and videos!

My Set Up-
Mouse- Sound BlasterX Siege M04
Keyboard - Corsair RGB
Case - Lian Li PC-08
Motherboard  - Sabertooth Z170
CPU - Intel i7-6700k
Memory - 32GB Corsair Vengeance
Video Card - Radeon R9 390X
Power Supply- Corsair RM850W
Hard Drives - 1TB Samsung SDD , 1TB Seagate HDD, 3TB Seagate
Monitors - 2 - 23.6in Asus Monitors
Camera- Logitech C920
Microphone- Audio Technica 2020
Headphones - Sound BlasterX  H5
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Marriland </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCe2yn-ptTl529JPheQgzm_A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-FAJS6B9gjgc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/eCk_GQSe7mk/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>How's it goin' everyone, Marriland here! Welcome to my channel! I hope you enjoy my videos, which consist mostly of Pokémon content, but also other games that I enjoy playing or want to try out.

Also, I do not use Pokémon Showdown. Anyone claiming to be me on that is lying.

</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Dash Star</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC_FoXwVjRM9qgMvNeh92b0g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Az68Q4cWyco/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/iNXVX63CGJA/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Comedy - Gaming - Geek stuff</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>NoobHunter</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCEMHiFr2E9Ekatjhl8mG0xA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-y0euTjnEClY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/v-cEI6NhPVo/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Overwatch Gameplay | Overwatch League Highlights | Overwatch Funny Moments
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Andrew JRT</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCg44vJ8AHcK7GcG6KqGBKag/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-uKYEQXjiM-o/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/qRAEW2DxuYA/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Yo, I make videos</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Lone Hawk</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCKIDf_v3Bj2J4JdJ0kE_6FQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-1mt1oquN5-I/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/P_jay6LWZNA/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I'm a Master rank Overwatch player just trying to improve your game. I make Overwatch Guides, give tips, tricks, and even provide overwatch news. Destiny 2 in the future? Maybe.

I upload as often as I can, but being a college student makes that hard.

If you're an artist or designer and want to help me make some channel art you would be the best!
</summary>
</plugin>
