#################################################################################
<cache>10800</cache>
<fanart>https://i.pinimg.com/originals/c4/83/cc/c483cc76c1f5dba29c94775116eedffd.png</fanart>
#################################################################################

<plugin>
  <title>Gaming Historian</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCnbvPS_rXp4PC21PG2k1UVg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-8EL8uV2zWuc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6cx197A77Uc/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>The Gaming Historian is a documentary series all about the history of video games. I also like to review books and certain games that I find interesting.

The show is researched, written, edited, and created by Norman Caruso.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Nostalgia Nerd</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC7qPftDWPw9XuExpSgfkmJQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAxxw_tRn8J00wlLanXj2gf6XbO7M8SLy-WBlg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>The 8-Bit Guy</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC8uT9cgJorJPWu7ITLGo9Ww/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-CwfC3-3jalo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/9VXlpqvGSYw/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>A computer video series focusing mainly on retro technology from the 80's, 90's and 2000's. However, once or twice a year I'll create something totally "out there."  My main goal at this point is to make educational content about retro technology that is interesting and engaging.  Some people will be re-living their childhood, while others will be experiencing the technology for the first time.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Stop Skeletons From Fighting </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC5Xeb9-FhZXgvw340n7PsCQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mA0FnVNbpnGde53F013-B1Puo4WRTBUUF4jDA=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Stop Skeletons From Fighting: Video Game Documentaries and Reviews

Profile and banner art by http://bit.ly/ClockworkPixel

Wanna send us stuff??

PO Box 30916
Seattle WA 98113

It's a small mail box, so please email before sending!
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>HappyConsoleGamer</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC2vUKoTGIwNYq4LO0YWKPIg/</link>
  <thumbnail>hhttps://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mAGW5YPwxenrR_kcfTaI_9JiqYiD8i21AsoLw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Retro gaming fun!

SUBSCRIBE! 
Please enjoy!
Support us on Patreon!
https://www.patreon.com/happyconsolegamer

I'm your host Johnny Millenium and I review forgotten games that not many people know about but should!

Also I will review some big time releases for fun.
I also just love looking back on the golden days of gaming past.

"Other people review games and bash them.
 I just want to review cool games that I think KICK ASS!"

I'm no fanboy of any one system I have them all, I just like good games on any system.

Background Art by Hanzo!
 https://heavymetalhanzo.deviantart.com/</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Video Game Basement</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCLKskvbbweeNGD9VE-rIgFg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAz42aEwcDiAtATCOVYsfJj1Azfony5FRyKaRg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Luke, Tom and a Basement.. That doesn't sound bad at all does it...  We have no sweeties or signs that say free hugs BUT we do play loads of videos games from various decades.  We'll entertain you and we'll get mad on screen, just what the viewers want or at least that's what we're told.

You can find us posting here (please subscribe, pretty please) but you can also find us on Twitter and Facebook @VGBasementUK.

We are now a member of YawnHub.UK (@YawnHub), this site allows small creators to content share and find more viewers.  Please follow them and help small creators make a difference.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Arcadology</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCL3pKToB6ER8N6TK6ZMueUw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-aVbkbIQPFCk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/TY_KpwsVTbE/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi there, my name is Spoiler Kevin, and I make history and discussion videos about video games and interactive media. Learn about the why's and wherefore's of video game history as I tackle a wide variety of topics, from Dark Souls to SimCity. If that sounds like a good time, then consider subscribing. Feel free to reach out to me on any number of social media channels found above and check out Roguelike Start, the place on the internet all my content calls home.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
<title>Jordan H J</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCenBYEupFr45ztQdv0Q00Gg/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mDLclXZckapQMvY4nmze4TGJ8slqSvPYbu79Q=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>Games and Geekery - If you're into Discord, I set one up - https://discord.gg/us3yXev</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Curse Entertainment</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCf6J9yokPS0ys456jvjLBGQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-sN4dLBN2imU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/oxgApu53a4g/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>




<plugin>
  <title>RETRO GAMING ARTS</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCKUGzrE6_IA6CDGbEdutnnQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAxWHcd8O5e5bT8CRyCmsrr-__eT2vmgtrEkPA=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>We Repair alot of video game consoles, we also modify alot of video game consoles, and we play and collect games, and we make videos about all of it
Lot's of tutorials, how to's and guides on fixing and repairing and modifying your game consoles, with many many more to come!

We also have a website where we sell pre modified game consoles! we're always adding more to the store, feel free to reach out to us and ask us for custom mods or repair jobs

Facebook is the best place to stay up to date with videos and website updates


Thank you to each and every single one of you for all of your support, we cant do what we do without you. Thank you for everything</summary>
</plugin>





      <plugin>
        <title>Completed It Mate</title>
        <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC88b1rl5tpgGxK5I-fL7hIw/</link>
        <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-a4EXWALSoXw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/IlDSxVxiUno/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
        <summary>Gaming channel from the idiot from the inbetweeners ... no not that idiot, no ... not the tall one ... not the one with glasses, the one with the blonde bowl hair cut. Yes! That's the one! Watch me talk and play (badly) great video games old and new. Yes if everyone else can start YouTube channels about any old nonsense I want to join in!

          I'm not just a fan of your new fangled current games, in 4D and super graphics and what not. I love playing old games too

          I try to bring out 2 videos a week usually, every Monday will be a brand new episode and then Fridays will be my "Let's Complete" series where i try to complete a game

          Please be kind, have fun and Game On</summary>
        </plugin>


        <plugin>
          <title>CurryShotTV</title>
          <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC86xaj3k3cOFaecL6di4Xfw/</link>
          <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-W6Xwwy-Yn2A/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/pRoKsDz1kf8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
          <summary></summary>
        </plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Project HyperPie</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC5C_OjQLafFMx3uLgXABsSg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-h1b1hJbh6B8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/znDvyqQPQNs/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>This channel is dedicated to some creative individuals in the Project HyperPie Facebook group. It is maintained and updated by those same guys 👍</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>David Marti</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCCdzkEbBKmEPrxOXFsTpEEw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/--KnPEaD9yqo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/N7Baw9JOFug/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Mostly devoted to the base RetroPie image I created called Motion Blue.

The Motion Blue base image is a RetroPie image that has been created and setup with several design goals in mind. Many new scripts and files have been developed to include new features and enhancements.  The base image has been setup and configured for both Emulation Station and Attract Mode will all emulators and romlists/gamelists pre-made.

A design philosophy was adopted for this build to bring RetroPie in line with the current retro gaming community. The most prominent change was to begin using the community standard for filenames for all configuration files and ROM files. This change now has RetroPie matching the EmuMovies/HyperSpin naming convention. With this change, end users are more easily able to download new ROMs and media files that will immediately work, thus saving hours of file renaming.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Simply Austin</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCb4RFFBZEztOW77onViqoDA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-0zGMz83jD_k/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/22X5HQ1q5dY/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>The Simply Austin Channel is a unique blend cutting edge video tutorials on some of the most entertaining systems and programs out there. The channel began in April 2015 on Youtube and exploded in popularity. After realizing that I could make an impact on the industry through entertaining and informative videos, I had finally found my calling.

Bringing YOU everything YOU need!

Unlike many channels out there I do not do this for any money. I do it for the love of the scene and the wanting I have to better it and expand it.  I will always offer my help in any way I can and would like a loyal fanbase who would work with me to make this a better place for us all, not just Pewdy bate!

From what started as a series aimed at the tens of people its now watched by the tens of thousands!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>ETA Prime</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC_0CVCfC_3iuHqmyClu59Uw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAzgSf30TQgezG7h6axdpSoUM-4nZFPspk-qVg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Tutorials , Retro Emulation and Gameplay On Raspberry pi , Android , PC , Mac And Other Single Board Computers. </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Game Sack</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCT6LaAC9VckZYJUzutUW3PQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-7CPvkI7EVl4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/vePJ5YCuFVA/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>We're Joe and Dave. We talk about video games we find interesting and a few that may not be so great.  Long new episode every other Sunday released at 12:00am mountain time (US). Thanks for checking out Game Sack!
  </summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>MetalJesusRocks</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCEFymXY4eFCo_AchSpxwyrg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ibnBAnZx5hI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/z4xGzX0oFrI/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>The Metal Jesus is a long-haired rocker dude who runs a popular YouTube channel dedicated to Retro Gaming with a Heavy Metal soundtrack. With the help of the Seattle gaming community he covers Hidden Gems, Buying Guides as well as the popular I HATE U series, Gamer Eats and much more. He was also an employee at mega publisher Sierra On-Line in the 90s and he brings his love of big box PC gaming to his channel as well.  New videos on Tuesday & Friday every week!
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Gaming Historian</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCnbvPS_rXp4PC21PG2k1UVg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-8EL8uV2zWuc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6cx197A77Uc/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>The Gaming Historian is a documentary series all about the history of video games. I also like to review books and certain games that I find interesting.

The show is researched, written, edited, and created by Norman Caruso.

If you like what I do and would like to support the show, please consider joining my Patreon. http://www.patreon.com/gaminghistorian</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>TheAngryHoneyBadger</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC7foeIw1ZW7BaqHAUfFgRzg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-UuM8Wa8M6Dw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/d1fW0uYrBgQ/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>PC hardware & Technology reviews and videos!

My Set Up-
Mouse- Sound BlasterX Siege M04
Keyboard - Corsair RGB
Case - Lian Li PC-08
Motherboard  - Sabertooth Z170
CPU - Intel i7-6700k
Memory - 32GB Corsair Vengeance
Video Card - Radeon R9 390X
Power Supply- Corsair RM850W
Hard Drives - 1TB Samsung SDD , 1TB Seagate HDD, 3TB Seagate
Monitors - 2 - 23.6in Asus Monitors
Camera- Logitech C920
Microphone- Audio Technica 2020
Headphones - Sound BlasterX  H5
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Marriland </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCe2yn-ptTl529JPheQgzm_A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-FAJS6B9gjgc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/eCk_GQSe7mk/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>How's it goin' everyone, Marriland here! Welcome to my channel! I hope you enjoy my videos, which consist mostly of Pokémon content, but also other games that I enjoy playing or want to try out.

Also, I do not use Pokémon Showdown. Anyone claiming to be me on that is lying.

</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Dash Star</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC_FoXwVjRM9qgMvNeh92b0g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Az68Q4cWyco/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/iNXVX63CGJA/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Comedy - Gaming - Geek stuff</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Andrew JRT</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCg44vJ8AHcK7GcG6KqGBKag/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-uKYEQXjiM-o/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/qRAEW2DxuYA/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Yo, I make videos</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Linus Tech Tips </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCXuqSBlHAE6Xw-yeJA0Tunw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mAaMpshKryp2hDULwK4Q6yah0alE9E20X0C-w=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>We make entertaining videos about technology, including tech reviews, showcases and other content.

LinusTechTips@gmail.com - Business inquiries only. All others will be ignored.</summary>
</plugin>
