##########################################################################################
<cache>10800</cache>
<fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/tNPYdZhl4rc/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
##########################################################################################

<plugin>
  <title>TalkingBass - Online Bass Lessons</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCDfStxwji-22A_bvY280UIg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-F7O77pcbLF4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/eyuScqKnYWE/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>TalkingBass Video brings you free online video bass lessons from Mark J Smith. All levels are covered from beginner to advanced.</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Fretted Americana</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCFzdwJs_ajtDeimeH6d3e_w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-pEa7EdwusK8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/qC2KGP7Ppgk/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Located in California! call 818 222 4113 for all inquiries.
We are home to the best rare vintage guitars in the world, and one of the most popular guitar shows on the internet featuring the one and only Phil X! We want to inspire and win your trust and confidence.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Andertons</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCSNxIry_FPFcQDFRbi3VOAw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-TNpuBm24H7A/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/aMNpnykWdc0/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to the Andertons Music Co. Youtube channel!

Andertons Music Co. has been a family run business since 1964, so it's fair to say we know a thing or two about guitars!

This channel is dedicated to guitars, effects pedals and amps. Showcasing all of the best gear as well as legendary guest players like John Petrucci, Paul Gilbert and Eric Gales. It doesn't matter if you're interested in a private stock PRS, an entry level acoustic guitar or a full on shred machine - Andertons Music Co. has got you covered!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>The Ukulele Teacher</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC1HlihY-iNtOemAlYQq3GXQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-7PP4UcxiVCc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/rKKKi4-cc6M/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>The best FREE ukulele lessons anywhere on the web - you WILL be able to play a song after your first lesson! Requests for future lesson and video ideas are always welcome. Check out https://www.grabyouruke.com to see what ukes I recommend and how I film my videos!
NEW VIDEO EVERY MONDAY, WEDNESDAY AND SATURDAY!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Justin Guitar Ukulele Lessons: Chords & Strumming</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/playlist/PLlwfspJqZ125opjcbC3f1W9-TQ18wY7K3/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-5lZN4lWqIJ4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/OTjz43hchDk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>CoverSolutions</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCUXTxsU23H02fewbRzHXBgQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-cL14xcH964M/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Mn792k-7rtg/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Play Along Covers (With Tabs In-Video) Of Your Favorite Songs! Post Your Requests!

Cover Solutions is a music project for everyone who wants to learn songs properly and quickly, this project is materialized in a YouTube channel with myself playing different song parts requested by my audience and adding tablatures (notation to learn the song) in the video itself. Band songs, TV songs and videogame covers are being constantly uploaded.
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Josh Fossgreen</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC55WUocY0fvyqiOLCnOPCPg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ne8QQlLIIv0/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/YOCjIbnzf-w/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Learn to play bass guitar and have fun doing it! Lessons range from beginning scales and techniques to advanced slap bass and sweep arpeggios. I'll also post solo bass and other performance videos occasionally, as well as videos about cruise ship gigs for musicians.

If you're a beginner, I can't recommend highly enough my complete 30-hour step-by-step course, Beginner to Badass, check it out here: http://joshfossgreen.com/b2b
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Scott's Bass Lessons</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCWTj3vCqkQIsrTGSm4kM34g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-nwLsfZQhSCA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/jBswImZox9M/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Free online bass lessons in HD, covering bass scales, bass arpeggios and soloing. For beginner, intermediate and advanced bass players.
-----
Hey I'm Scott. I've been a professional bass player for the last 20 years and have been lucky enough to have played with some of the best musicians in the world.

On my channel I'm going to show you exactly how you can become... a bad ass bass player!

I'm going to show you exactly what you need to know to take your bass playing to he next level and beyond.

Whether you're a beginner, intermediate or advanced bass player you will find over 35+ hours of material within this channel to keep you inspired, focused and hungry to be the bass player you know you can be!
</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Low End University - Bass Lessons</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3TqK2sSktlk7CmXGpw7_Cg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-UxCQKEgnOWc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Wrd8RDEsKsw/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Low End University offers hundreds of online bass lessons by educator and bassist Mark Michell, best known for his musical work with Scale the Summit, Tetrafusion, and his educational work as a published author through Hal Leonard. We provide a custom learning experience for every student with our bass guitar lessons online, an ever-growing lesson video library, challenge licks, downloadable PDF transcriptions, bass-less backing tracks, interactive features, community members’ forum and more.

Learn bass guitar online with Low End University today from anywhere. We offer bass lessons for a variety of skill levels. Start your 30-Day FREE Trial subscription and begin learning the bass guitar or continue mastering your skills today!

https://www.LowEndUniversity.com/
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Daric Bennett's Bass Lessons</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCvUGrdDxtUBlxSi4Zl-HkqQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-74EP-eY7cl0/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/2nzAb6ni5ns/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Learn to play bass guitar with these instructions, lessons, techniques and exercises from Daric Bennett! Get your chops up! Check out all the bass lesson videos, subscribe to the channel for free bass lessons and check out the site for full access bass lessons, bass guitar forum, messaging system, member directory and more at daricbennett.com
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Adam Neely</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCnkp4xDOwqqJD7sSM3xdUiQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ps0rJo-2vuA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/O7ExtmPFp3A/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Video essays, lessons and vlogs on new horizons in music and music theory. NYC-based bass player and composer Adam Neely brings you a new video every Monday exploring what music means, and what it means to be a musician.
  </summary>
</plugin>
<plugin>
  <title>Marlon Wörsching Bass Cover</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCjT-aRuS6CtALA-Ghkj_Mtw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-gp_KL37E-HE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/GLvB1z0aHTQ/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey, my name is Marlon Wörsching and I'm a self taught Bassist
from Germany. If you want to collaborate with me in any kind of
video, feel free to contact me via any Social Media or my E-Mail.

Cheers!
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Real Bass Lessons</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCTLM0C5Acp-0xi4ZEb-mSQg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-DygDbW7nuEs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/T6y-rpKawRw/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>My name is Jim Stinnett.  I have been playing bass for 50 years now - Rock, Funk, Country, Jazz, Classical, Pop, etc.  I am a retired Professor from Berklee College Of Music where I taught bass and arranging for the 30 years.  I have been fortunate to teach many great private students, who have made me look good.  ;)   Some of the more notable guys: Mike Gordon (Phish), Brent Rusinow (Allen Stone), Shane Allessio, Ben McKee (Imagine Dragons), Steve Bailey (Berklee Bass Dpt. Chair), Matt O'Donnell, Grant Stinnett, Sunder Panatella, Rob Gourlay, Jim Lambie, Charles Berthoud, et al.

"Real Bass Lessons" features video lessons on a variety of bass related topics in many styles - transcribed bass lines - short lessons on specific topics - some simply grooving bass lines and solos.  Our goal is to educate and entertain.  We have some highly talented and bass loving folks in our community who will be sharing their love for the bass.
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>The Bass Wizard</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCECakqH9ME9aQHLaOvGqXHw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-wfSP8yhSrLk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/xQQ4fpcEm40/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I am a professional bass player in Los Angeles that has toured the world with many different artists such as Olivia Holt, Mitchel Musso (Disney/Hannah Montana), Mark Salling (Glee), Lilian Garcia (WWE), Billy Unger (Disney/Lab Rats), Carly Smithson (American Idol), Steve Rushton and many others.

I am a Berklee College of Music graduate and a Photography, Videography, MMA and Bodybuilding enthusiast.

This channel will have several different types of videos including Gear Reviews, Gig Vlogs, Bass Lessons, Solo Bass Arrangements, Bass Tutorials, etc.

If you want to learn from me, make sure to check out my bass courses at TheBassWizard.com

Much love, Marc - The Bass Wizard.
</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Viaceslav Svedov</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCgCIM3TsDAA5K48X-q7t-pg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-D5cF8gpvFCg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/aXWGQFTQYxg/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>All Bass Songs (covers and my own things as well).</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Fender</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCI7fys0WM62xF2jUlUdq0XQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-WjJObwK738U/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/SJ3lNkgKgNY/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Fender is the world’s foremost manufacturer of electric and acoustic guitars, basses, amplifiers, accessories, apparel and more; known worldwide for Stratocaster, Telecaster, Jazzmaster, Jaguar and Mustang models</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Epiphone</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCEP8b1vx01-zOu9uR9jxdPw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-9_MuRx9HjbM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/XBAljQyRYtw/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>From its humble beginnings in Sparta, Greece in 1873 through its rise to fame on 14th Street in New York City, to its reemergence as a dominant force in musical instruments from its new headquarters today in Nashville, TN, Epiphone instruments can be heard on a century of great recordings.  Epiphone artists includes virtually every major figure in pop music history including Les Paul, The Beatles, The Rolling Stones, John Lee Hooker, Jimi Hendrix, Kurt Cobain, Paul Simon, Jack Casady, Tak Matsumoto, Paul McCartney, Joe Bonamassa, Zakk Wylde, Robb Flynn, Slash, Gary Clark Jr., KISS's Tommy Thayer, Paul Weller, Dwight Yoakam, Oasis, and Radiohead.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Gibson Guitar</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCfPWFpDpmnYO530l9ivmC6Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-f-U5t1b2pWQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/tiiI8B0-kK0/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Gibson is known worldwide for producing classic models in every major style of fretted instrument, including acoustic and electric guitars, mandolins and banjos. Founded in 1894 in Kalamazoo, MI, and headquartered in Nashville since 1984, Gibson Guitar Corp.'s family of brands now includes Epiphone, Dobro, Valley Arts, Kramer, Steinberger, Tobias, Slingerland, Maestro, Baldwin, Hamilton, Chickering and Wurlitzer. www.gibson.com</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Dean Guitars</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCUPWPKDSW3I0C9D5kg00W6g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-VFf7EXbZ56E/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/dY4CbcZpEnU/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>This the official YouTube Channel for Dean Guitars USA.  We appreciate all of our friends out there that also have posted videos of our artists and instruments!  Feel free to share our videos with your friends and make comments and please subscribe. We have a lot of video to share with you this year!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Crimson Custom Guitars</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCdD1Cqxr8aINzWs1agg3tEQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-6_-mFBq0z5Y/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/AbBf2vurBwk/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>How do you build guitars? This channel is an outlet for Crimson Guitars guitar making tutorials and how-to videos with tips and tricks of the guitar makers trade released every week or two and video demos of our completed custom built guitars.  We also shoot video diaries of entire custom guitar builds and post them here, see a guitar come to life in front of your eyes and learn how to make one in the process.

 We are on all the main social media platforms spreading the word and throughout each working day we post photo's of every phase of every build.  You can see each instrument grow from timber to tunes live or at weeks end through the Workshop Diary and the video blog here on YouTube!  Don't forget to share and subscribe to our channel, we really appreciate it :)</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Bass Whisperer TV</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCranFvDA8I4qHg8GweBmDEA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-XPqj9Nb0ucE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/loTJ_ulq_WM/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to the online video outlet for Ed Friedland - "The Bass Whisperer". Here you will find my video product reviews, as well as a few mini lessons. I hope you enjoy them!
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Rob Chapman</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCCOIcdii1bQmfSPHeNNw4Qw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-v_yLFUU8jH8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/EjHnr2dkAoo/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Greetings! I am Rob Chapman, a guitarist from Brighton, UK.

I am the founder & owner of Chapman Guitars, frontman and guitarist for Dorje, and demonstrator for Andertons Music. I love making videos about guitar tuition, demonstration, reviews, and studio things like coffee, pizza and Diablo. Welcome to my world ;-)</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Rocksmith</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCjjgYbxFsIvuF-AUl_xUr0A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-IvUYlP4lnSw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/d8bEoBU_4A0/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Rocksmith is the fastest way to learn guitar and the most innovative and effective guitar learning software on the market. Plug any electric guitar or bass into your PC, Mac, Xbox 360, or PlayStation 3, and join over 1.5 million people who have learned to play guitar with award-winning Rocksmith method. Learn to play guitar in 60 days. Get started, now! </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>The Riff Repeater (Rocksmith)</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCQQ8yAmq2d-zLsqTOV7Uf_g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-NBHhZ4srdJg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/bbAOgXdTq2c/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Rocksmith 2014
BandFuse: Rock Legends</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Reverb.com</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCHP-KQAJgXu4Wo2Xq4-eNow/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-BKoEeDXuO0Q/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/pc1eGfgLrJw/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Reverb.com is the online marketplace to buy, sell, and learn about new, used, and vintage music gear.

Since launching in 2013, Reverb's YouTube channel has grown into one of the world’s most popular music gear channels, connecting millions of people around the world to the gear and inspiration they need to make music.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Thomann Music</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCtvgPVBJ_r1vjN4mRuHCbog/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-HCsoc5fN6fI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/y5KS3jAb12k/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Subscribe to our channel and don't miss out on new videos on bass and guitar every week! We'll have you covered with gear tests, tips, tricks and tutorials as well as interviews and sessions with famous musicians. Plus there will be occasional live streams as well!

Thomann is the World's leading music retailer -- from rare custom shop guitars, drums, keys, dj, brass, strings, pa, lights to everything else you could possibly imagine. With an extremely knowledgeable staff we are able to provide you with funny short films, in-store live performances and much more.

All of our videos feature our employees and are created here, in-house at Thomann.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Dave's World of Fun Stuff</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCOXNPo7CtnzzZ9A4GyQ6Tog/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-u3XTEQQdegk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/r7e1XrusXJk/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Guitar Repairs, Cooking, Comedy and other Fun Stuff !!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>guitarbank</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCh3BbC85YARDmHksD4nnmNA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ryQYFIMboHs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/hV_b9vgRNsA/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello Folks! Guitarbank — is a pretty nice vintage guitars store in Russia
No talking more Rocking!

Reverb shop: reverb.com/shop/guitarbank</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Ben Eller</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCcLsvLJOecfCL6RplXhaO4Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-86HCYyVtlHQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/uQbYMMqw_Ck/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>BigDGuitars -</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCwtoF_Vwd-thTMDufibQ4pA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-zuplftsSU4M/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/iHQ8pdT9mTs/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Close to 20 years in the business, I have been around wood all my life, my grandfather was a furniture builder, my great great grand father built violins back in the old country.  I have worked at a lumber yard handling all types of woods from domestics to exotics, surface sanded hundreds of thousands of board feet from Oak to Cherry to Walnut.  Cut into more wood than you can imagine on a jump saw.

I am self taught with some help from a great friend to teach me the finer details, thank you Doug, and I just keep plugging away.

What was a way for me to make a guitar for myself became an obsession; at one point I had 50 guitars laying around.  Now its time to share my knowledge, ask away I will answer as much as I can.  Be safe and have fun!
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Highline Guitars</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCyQxAUfkTCfJdDO1nyr_a9w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-F70cEActhJw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Rd72V61IMog/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to my youtube channel. Here you will find a collection of videos I have created to help inform and inspire guitar builders regardless of their experience and skill level.
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>stewartmacdonald</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCdr6rJVSSx54ByuY5U2ohTQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-64meSjqQ3J8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/MOIkoNn69Xo/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>For over 40 years we've supplied the world's instrument makers and repair shops from right here in Athens, Ohio. We offer the widest selection of innovative lutherie tools, parts, books and videos available, all backed by our 100% Satisfaction Guarantee!
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Brad Angove</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCl5TLlEtAHzMUsXyEmbmw-w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-H2qOJJT7KKA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/8QHhAXGSSoo/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey guys! I’m Brad, and I make how-to videos. I do custom painting projects, guitar painting, airbrushing, spray can painting, wood working, and a variety of other finishing work, tutorials, and project vlogs. Please subscribe and check out my channel for videos on these topics.
  </summary>
</plugin>
