
<plugin>
  <title>Grumpy Retro Gamers</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UClpniF0RN4YBsafDwFfuOwQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mCC1LzZ8h7I9nZwqobvmm1LwjFLETqDKXtCXw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Reviews, features and let's plays from the Internet's Grumpy Retro Gamers.

Please like, comment, share and subscribe - we look forward to hearing from you!

Love games, still grumpy!

Please note that all donations, snail mail, etc. should be sent to the below address...

Grumpy Retro Gamers
Stage 2 Studios
13 Brassmill Enterprise Centre
Brassmill Lane
Bath
BA1 3JN</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>MAZ Gaming UK</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC7o_4Rc5PdulefBfApGuk6g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mBSu1HnIxbbDyyxy3IVt8Kmn1bG2aPYGGHZTQ=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>MAZ Gaming UK is a YouTube channel and upcoming website, dedicated to all things gaming. From Interviews with some of the biggest names in Gaming, through to News, Reviews and Let's Plays.

Please like and subscribe to keep up to date with our latest content and if you like what you see then why not consider supporting us on Patreon :) www.patreon.com/mazgaminguk</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>EightNineOne</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCVIJ8sdbW3Bl0uFU_xM8Wow/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mBvDErvj1kTVqY2uUBFTb5dHlCR9SvX_Z8NNg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Old school games, reviewed by a British moron. Original right?</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Pixels Ltd</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCgVvzWSSfLuD5LP-I_s8QUg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mAnjYk18j0S4m_hGz7pNh_qgs3EY919uITE4w=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi, I’m Samuel Victor and you’re watching Pixels.Ltd - you must be very excited!

On our shows I talk about all kinds of retro goodness from my childhood growing up in UK in the '80s & ‘90s. I cover movies, TV shows, music, comics, toys, & more, but the primary focus is always going to be retro video games.

We have 3 regular shows, and you’ve just stumbled across the official YouTube Channel, lucky you!

"Pixels.Ltd" is our monthly flagship show, a 45 minute gaming history show with a story-telling vibe and special guests, like Guru Larry, DJ Slopes, Timmy Mallett, and more!

"Pixels Xtra" is a 20 minute show covering extra stuff like channel updates, bloopers, game reviews etc.

"Pixel Plays" is our Let's Play channel, where I play various retro games, with a full commentary, and some very tough challenges to beat!

If you've only just found us, then welcome, & if you decide to stick around? Thank you - you rock!</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>The Gaming Muso</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCjYvO-vGHWZgEWJQBmHESCg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mCa9LjKQ0BrORZfOZBk-fKsiRH0qtzwWGATMg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Music, Videogames and Random comedic Musings :)

Presenter at @gamefaceshow

Incessant Ramblings...
Stuff & Things!</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Trista Bytes</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCSV06jW8k06gHn-ZYQ9qmtg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mCwsosuigVf0EU8--OoPCeR9C7u84rgZcoKQw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Trista Bytes is a source of comic, movie, anime, TV, sci-fi and cyberpunk interest, news & review videos by Bex Trista! Based in the Uk, making short videos on a variety of geek topics.</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>...Since Spacies</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCglptaKA4eqejYu2eTtj1gA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mDxaMoYKJyJO6f9h1g0d5QB-mVDWbQPzN8gKQ=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Some folks are new to gaming... but then some have been playing "Since Spacies". I'm one of those older gamers and this is where I'll be uploading my rants, views and general views on what is happening with gaming.

My name is Brian Costelloe and my username online is "SirBargeArse". I'm a former Sega employee and also use to be a writer for the Megazone magazine and Hyper magazine in the 90's!

I'm new to running a channel so... hang in there as I get use to this!

Twitter: https://twitter.com/sincespacies

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/sincespacies/

Also add me to either Xbox, PSN or Nintendo. My username is "SirBargeArse". Game on!


Find me also now at Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/sincespacies</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Sorax Space</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCeZuazW6czIWpg-bGbU93Pw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mB6KiKSgR7lxeiDUnCLUkcZtEBtM8yRBgRO1Q=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello! I'm Sorax. On Sorax Space you'll find comedic video game reviews, funny app reviews, pickup vids, podcasts, and even more gaming goodness! Subscribe and become a Sorax Spacer today!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>ScaredyMat</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCYVkYO9mIRe5E20HcGKHUHQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mCuAtWdL1vPYUX4KUFXbbk1IGmhKgKmjlHd8Q=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>I'm ScaredyMat, I delve into the deep dark depths of horror gaming and come out with my sanity vanquished, expect a lot of screaming and terror-stricken tears. But its all good fun! I also do reviews!

I Hope you enjoy if you do please don't forget to...

 [̲̅S̲̅][̲̅u̲̅][̲̅b̲̅][̲̅s̲̅][̲̅c̲̅][̲̅r̲̅][̲̅i̲̅][̲̅b̲̅][̲̅e̲̅] 

Until Next Time....☠

I Love You all!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title></title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel//</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>
