################################################################################

<fanart>https://orig00.deviantart.net/917d/f/2014/097/5/5/bring_in_the_nerds____wallpaper_edition_by_blo0p-d7dfks6.png</fanart>
################################################################################



<plugin>
  <title>Dungeons & Dragons</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCi-PULMg2eD_v5AO0PlW4sg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-QxXt2ku_CFo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/da4j2Xy3g2s/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>The Dungeons & Dragons YouTube channel offers an assortment of digital and tabletop game videos, from the popular Acquisitions Incorporated PAX live games to tutorials on how to play D&D and our other product offerings. Enjoy weekly VOD content directly from Wizards of the Coast's livestreams and produced video content like our popular Rage of Demons and Tyranny of Dragons trailers.
  </summary>
</plugin>




<plugin>
  <title>Dungeons & Dragons Online</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCD6EDZQofNgyIkdhLPvuXbw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Mwi285ojRCo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/5-oi1m3gI34/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Fight for power and glory in Dungeons and Dragons Online®, the intense action MMO that's completely Free to Play! Build your hero from classic D&D races and classes and battle through hundreds of hours of exciting adventure based game play.
  </summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Matthew Colville</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCkVdb9Yr8fc05_VbAVfskCA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-7_SDOsdEWIw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/zIW1p-xRGkg/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>My name's Matt Colville, I'm a writer and designer in video games and this is my channel where we talk about nerd stuff! Mostly D&D (how to run it), my weekly game (stream archive) and occasionally movies.
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>[B]Geek & Sundry[/B]</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCaBf1a-dpIsw8OxqH4ki2Kg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-cyEhEXnn2BI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Ek4fD_9iVxM/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>We bring you the best of indie geek culture with daily video uploads from the Internet's foremost geek voices and content creators including Felicia Day, Wil Wheaton, Adam de la Pena, Amy Berg, Bryan Singer, Canadians, NASA scientists, and much much more!
  </summary>
</plugin>
