################################################################################
<cache>10800</cache>
<fanart>https://images.fastcompany.net/image/upload/fc/3060718-poster-p-1-10-ways-to-make-slack-simpler-safer-and-less-annoying.jpg</fanart>
<thumbnail>http://pngimg.com/uploads/youtube/youtube_PNG10.png</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
###################################################################################


<plugin>
  <title>The Samurai Carpenter</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC06fO6LNH_AUgjbmqaZRV5Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-2qkQEgD8w7w/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/XKyG633UjTM/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Showing the world that there are still passionate craftsmen around who love what they do and find joy in enriching peoples lives with relationship and art.  My videos are for inspiration purposes only and I do not consider myself an expert.  Using power tools can be dangerous so be safe and work at your own risk.

Check Out The Samurai Woodworking School: http://samuraiskills.com/
</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Alec Steele</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCWizIdwZdmr43zfxlCktmNw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-V_jCF9fW3Bc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/nMWJKdlFdTU/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>My name's Alec Steele and here you'll find near-daily videos documenting the process of building some awesome projects here in the shop. As a blacksmith, most of the projects start as lumps of steel, or stacks of different alloys for making damascus, that I forge out into blades, sculpture, art or tools before taking the project to the machining equipment or into the grinding room for finishing. Each project teaches me a lot and stretches the bounds of my knowledge. I make a lot of mistakes but they serve as an excellent teacher. There's always something important for me to learn in the shop! 

I want my work to be the spark that ignites the desire for you to get into your shop (or kitchen/basement/garage) and make something too! Whether it's stitching a leather wallet or forging a giant sword, you'll love the creative process.

Be sure to follow me on instagram @alecsteele for behind the scenes and grab some awesome t-shirts at https://alecsteeleshop.com/

Thanks! 
Alec</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>ThisWoodwork</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCZXRKRLIJalPdM9tAANuyUg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-DCBAdZ6WJws/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/8Q1LlvBrwTQ/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Woodworking and woodturning project and how to videos! 

I am Alex Harris, a 22 year old woodworker. Here at my channel I post how-to videos of all kinds of woodworking and woodturning projects, demonstrating that just about anyone can get involved in the hobby. 
Interested in making things yourself? You can learn more about woodwork, or just have fun watching me make something right here!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Highland Woodworking</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UChYK4HS3hVQmsr6OEHZDDzQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-4ukKM33G3O4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/_6kooSIHqx8/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Woodworking videos from a leading source of fine tools. Learn woodworking skills online from Highland Woodworking. 

Educating woodworkers since 1978</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>YouCanMakeThisToo</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC_mcFH_r7Aq6SyQ0HrGaenQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-C3v3fE1c87k/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Ba1Xol0MzPQ/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>My goal is to make videos that break the barriers that prevent people from embracing their creativity by showing that making is within their ability and reach. If you are inspired by my videos, please subscribe and leave me comment or send a message. Happy making!
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>The Cutting Bored</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCg88X__cwd6NJH82-3svvlA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-viXFqVBjtcs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/ckSm-0AjMIE/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I like to design, create, film, edit, and write. This channel is a result of that ongoing collective passion as I continue to build things - big and small - that bring me joy everyday. 

I hope I can inspire at least one person to be a creator in their own right. 

You should subscribe if you're interested :-)

Cheers, 
Zach
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>3x3Custom - Tamar</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC39z4_U8Kls0llAij3RRZAQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-3xJEHNc_bp8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/r2VnZQValto/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>3x3 Custom is about trying something new and learning as you do. Follow along as I design, build and create custom projects that you can make on your own!

If you enjoy watching the building process from start to finish, head on over to my Instagram, where I post in real time as I build. https://www.instagram.com/3x3custom/</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Fix This Build That</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCHYSw4XKO_q1GaChw5pxa-w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-cP8WhWr2hsY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/5XDEiK5S3yY/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Woodworking & DIY Projects, Plans and Tools in easy understand detailed content.  Let's build something awesome!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>EvanAndKatelyn</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCUuMYw2l2UeWyTGYixYfRCA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-poIhH2w02l8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/UPhxau3FzCA/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey guys, we're Evan and Katelyn and we make stuff together: woodworking, 3D printing, welding, props, CNC, home projects, sometimes practical stuff, sometimes totally unnecessary but fun stuff.

The reason we started this channel is partly for y'all, but partly for us too. We want to show that making stuff is fun and accessible, even if you're figuring it out as you go (like we often are). But also, we wanna work together. We're basically each others favorite person, and being able to do stuff we love with the person we love is pretty much the dream.

So if you like making things, enjoy a heavy dose of goofiness and expertly aimed high fives, and want to see a random stream of cool things we make in a new video each week, please consider subscribing and sharing our channel. Thanks! Bye!
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Crafted Workshop</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC-hTi9atsD6wAl2s46LpAVw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Gn54PAf6sJc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/mMfteLZUg5w/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Weekly how-to project videos about woodworking, metalworking, and more. Created by Johnny Brooke.
    <summary>
</plugin>
<plugin>
  <title>Wood By Wright</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCbMtJOly6TpO5MQQnNwkCHg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-V_DH2XKmnOI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/meZT27EC9DA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I have been working with wood since I could stumble into the shop with my dad. A few years ago I moved into a house with no space for a full shop so I decided to take up all hand tool wood working. That started a whole new passion for wood. Now I feel as though I am learning the art all over again.

My Joy and desire is to share this passion for hand tool woodworking with everyone I can. So come along for the fun of learning the ancient and new art of Hand tool woodworking!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Michaelcthulhu</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCGca03sbLq7OUnXMdvRHyBQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-M80n2s-9j2o/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/fmMfJHYsnos/s176-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I make Giant Swords. I sell them to people. People like you. Check out my Facebook page. Don't follow me on Twitter.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Shop Time</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3CrzXzBFVqEopj5T1jiRtA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-XEL_2E2Ni3Y/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/QkojIu83a0U/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Just a geek with a full set of power tools!

I do woodworking, woodturning or whatever piques my interest at the time. My hope is to have one part woodworking and one part crazy. I 'll try my best to make something interesting. This is just for fun, please don't do what I do in the shop.

All of the content shown is for the sole purpose of entertainment and is not intended for educational purposes in any format. Anyone choosing of their own free will to reenact or recreate any of this content assumes all personal liability and or responsibility by doing so. Woodworking especially with power tools is very dangerous and can cause serious bodily harm,  therefore proper education and training is advised.  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Mr. Volt</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCvOOv9tfBMSzcXnDkgzMufA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-5wuVSn5-omQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/S8DPHvbSzik/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Props - Gadgets - DIY Technology</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>3D Central</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCeYZg5Ynx0gGdeKQ-v7N8nQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-GE-hlFp7W0s/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/fXBlJTnXzl8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi, we're 3D Central! We've been 3D Printing since 2011, and we've turned our passion into Virginia's first 3D Printing shop!

Want to send us something? Want to visit the shop? Here's our address, check out our hours on our page!
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Tempest Rings</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCfdCFlodE6Lphcy9Gr6_1BQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-5fSU-WnvTyw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/wwx4_bhUKoE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Just making rings.Just making rings.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Wood Working for Mere Mortals</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCBB7sYb14uBtk8UqSQYc9-w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-60UeHmwKfZg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/vKU1lfJfd1A/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Ever think about making something out of wood? You can! Woodworking for Mere Mortals is dedicated to making woodworking easy, fun and accessible. New woodworking video every Friday!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Richard Morley</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCwX4xJMViZkXcoYeZ9naNJw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-myQRDp9qUJc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/p-mcLHv_DGU/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Useful & interesting woodworking & maker projects as well as techniques that are designed to be not just cost effective but also interesting, fun and achievable.
Weather you're a "time-served master craftsman" or "weekend hobbyist" - I hope you are entertained and inspired to get out there and build - whilst having fun and feeling proud of your endeavours.
Some videos could be a 'how-to" style, some might just be a "sit back and enjoy the build". Wood, plastic, maybe a bit of metal working.  There could also be some paper or leathercraft. I just like to build, make, create and have fun. You might even enjoy a bit of soldering and some electronics, CNC or 3D printing. I enjoy making so you can enjoy watching - Hopefully  :-)
Watch, like, subscribe, share, watch again! Comments welcomed, questions answered, If you take the time to engage, the least I can do is respond or reply in some way, if only to say thanks for the comment!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Modustrial Maker</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC9aRTgvFLqnK1S0RsWZzlMw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-lYhUFQiE-D4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/UgZSlv2UFX8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>DIY Build Videos for my modern industrial creations.   If you like what you see, subscribe to get notifications about future videos.

To see what I'm working on before build videos are posted, follow me on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/modustrialmaker/?hl=en

Also, check out my Modustrial Maker website, where I plan to post more content, including photos and details of past projects that were completed before I started documenting my work with video for this channel.

www.modustrialmaker.com</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Andy Phillip</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCDQz4H7tz6Fwu5_5rg4W6pA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-o3HpE6YTNzI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Lw5cHeHc5Aw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Trying to make interesting pieces using different combinations of woods and resins , sometimes they work sometimes they don't !! Thanks for watching ...
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Patrick Adair Designs</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCJ82SlfYWJag5794tE64ZZA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-DgfyH1jzxFU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/P3pA-QPP8YI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi! My name is Patrick Adair and I love creating. I film a lot of the projects I do and upload them here. I specialize in rings made of materials like carbon fiber, titanium, and other random rare materials.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Arbortech</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCY5uXmsTQPfLxt169OaxaaA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-CJynMhiNsX0/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/KTaIiYB1Wj8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Arbortech is an Australian company specializing in woodworking and masonry power tools.

The first woodworking product designed and developed by Arbortech was the Woodcarver Blade which was released to the Australian market in 1988. From here we went on to develop more innovative, safe and performance enhanced woodworking tools such as the Arbortech Power Chisel, Mini-Grinder and the latest woodworking superstar products to date are the Arbortech TURBO Plane and the Mini TURBO. </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Thomas Anton Geurts</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCd7KZmlU3I4joZaLUMpmn-g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-RBooXLBZ96w/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/a6_MYoboWmg/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello dear visitor!
This channel contains some of my work,
i have a degree as a woodworker since 2009, And i hope you will enjoy my videos!

Besides sharing knowledge, one of my goals i hope to achieve by making video's is bringing also a calming experience.
I find it very hard to rush while editing a video, probably because i'm having trouble absorbing to much information myself.
If someone finds the video's relaxing/calming and insightfull, that makes it more worth for me than just giving the information.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Make Something </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCtaykeSsGhtn2o2BsPm-rsw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-_XCpsHztWnk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/3A1cwidOupM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Woodworking projects for the beginner and advanced woodworker. I show that making and building is fun and rewarding for all skill levels. I focus on design and originality and show you that anyone can be a creative woodworker.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>I Like To Make Stuff </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC6x7GwJxuoABSosgVXDYtTw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-kVJyRVXzd7E/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/jFcJXJDNz68/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I like to make all sorts of stuff, with all sorts of materials. I have lots of projects including woodworking, metalworking, electronics, 3D printing, prop making and more!

These videos are my attempt at teaching, inspiring and empowering others to make the stuff that they want to have. Hopefully you'll see something here that will inspire you to make something that you're passionate about!
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>I Like To Make Stuff 2</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCruM8e10ljDk6VEe1XrUxQA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-5hEF1lqaDus/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/UdlhNbROZvI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Behind the scenes and extra stuff that doesn't fit on http://www.youtube.com/iliketomakestuffcom </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>April Wilkerson</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC4v2tQ8GqP0RbmAzhp4IFkQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Q2JA-AIO-ck/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/EKQwaVl2_a4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I am an obsessed DIYer and Woodworker. I'm not professional or have any training, so I just pick the project I want to tackle and figure it out step by step.

I picked up my first tool in January of 2013. I couldn't afford to buy the things I wanted around my home, so I decided to try my hand at making them instead. I was hooked after my first project so I just never stopped.

I put out a video as well as a written tutorial on all the projects I do to improve my home and workshop. You can find my website at Wilkerdos.com</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>jimmydiresta</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCiEk4xHBbz0hZNIBBpowdYQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-zHnRwS1sk6I/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/e86upfV2RVQ/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I make stuff for a living, what you see me do here is my Job.  I have been using tools for over 40 years. I have developed my comfort level with tools through years of experience. DON'T DO THE DANGEROUS THINGS I DO. Thank You for watching and subscribing!
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Jay Bates</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC-7XY-W_C84cW2MNqujgFpg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-b5kAO6E7LSQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/3l71ZJYDGjE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>© Jays Custom Creations LLC

These videos are for entertainment purposes only. </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Laura Kampf</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCRix1GJvSBNDpEFY561eSzw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-RkDtiQl-_Qc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6L9--55KnBg/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Watch me make all kinds of stuff in my shop!

Build Videos on Sundays
Vlogs every other week
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>frank howarth</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3_VCOJMaivgcGqPCTePLBA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-GMkkUpV4PX0/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/bJaQNN3eAXs/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Architecture at a small scale expressed through woodworking and film making.

Disclaimer:  My videos here are for entertainment, to share what I do, and to maybe provide some inspiration.  Woodworking can be dangerous if all safety precautions are not taken.  Please don't try anything I am doing just because you saw me doing it. Understand that there are years of learning and experimentation by me that are not in the videos.  You can have a safe, enjoyable, and even inspirational time in your shop by understanding your own tools, materials, and your own skill level.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Shop built</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCZBqq0o54ShN5cSTflT2MnQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Wiw2O1GDSdo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/bvHoeNwxNGc/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>just some videos of stuff I build in my shop.
New videos every second Friday! sometimes, not really:(
Use all proper safety precaution when working around power tools. including using the the proper PPE.
These videos are for entertainment only. </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Roger Webb</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCVbRweyeFzc6j7_VYQjwxYQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-DtGKT_vE5iU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/b6btAGRJWSw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to my workshop, all kinds of projects is my interest, woodturning, woodwork, metalwork, CNC Routers and computers.
30 Million views over113,000 subscribers is proof that there is something of interest for you here ;-)
</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>SG Art Turning</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCKmU3_I2MD3843jJRIQjnMg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-jMq-yTGRBHk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Xyw__BRvnxA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Woodturning</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Mike Waldt</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCI_tt3HOlpZguB8ebtB4k1w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-09dXR_5rlus/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/loYVrkThI7s/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Wood Turning Projects and Tips   -
"The aim of the wise is not to secure pleasure, but to avoid pain" - Aristotle
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Erik Anderson</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCfdxhrmOgVlW4le9B3T34JQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-rt-tf9n2yME/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/ZnOEylG4krA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>This Channel is dedicated to woodturning.  On my channel art you will see a g+ if you click on that link it will take you to photos of my work.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Will Matthews</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCh9J-RX5wpjjJdYZ3WVkrYg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-_dRBj4vxnDw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/y6Dbkgq7Y4A/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>If you enjoy watching woodworking, tool restoration, blacksmithing, forging, making and other craftsman projects, then subscribe and stay tuned! I endeavour to post videos of my journey as I build, create & discover. I am by no means an expert, but hope to provide some entertainment and value to the viewer through these videos.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Hand Tool Rescue</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCasG9kJWi1eVxM0QkyqKVJQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-tSQenI6Wdp8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/94RaV91C5H4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Tool restorations and rescues.

I rescue tools and put them back in the hands of people who can appreciate them.

I will restore a tool for free if it is interesting enough for a video.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>The Small Workshop</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCWSRNbhnlahD43ZNPkNUTzA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-xyJgob9n_xc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/lmiMHL0oGDU/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Homemade tools and workshop projects, in wood and metal!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Alec Steele </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCWizIdwZdmr43zfxlCktmNw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-V_jCF9fW3Bc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/nMWJKdlFdTU/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey! My name is Alec Steele, I'm a blacksmith and Youtuber. This YouTube channel is designed to give you an entertaining insight into the life of a blacksmith in the 21st Century through my daily vlogs, teach you blacksmithing online and interact with you through my weekly live show, Saturday's 5pm EST, 2pm PST, 10pm BST. </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>John Heisz I Build It</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCjA8vRlL1c7BDixQRJ39-LQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-s1iavblFQoE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/GNe5z6utYU0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Videos on woodworking and workshop related projects.
Check out my website for hundreds of cool projects: www.ibuildit.ca

Me and my shop are in Ontario, Canada. I'm a carpenter by trade and have worked in commercial construction since 1985.

Concerning my videos:
I can't and won't cover (or follow) every safety rule when doing a project, and it's not my responsibility to train the people that watch my videos. It is up to them to learn, understand and follow the safety rules concerning the tools they choose to work with.
My videos are not comprehensive tutorials - they are a look at how I did the project and should be viewed as entertainment or a source of inspiration.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Mistry MakeTool</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3SfkkQw9TmpjsFZTp3bdYw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-N576LzxOykI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/_mniYfI3aJg/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>“Mistry MakeTool” is a small Homemade Tools Project on YouTube channel run by myself, Sandip Mistry.
All you need to know about the Proper Use and  Guidelines  of Power Tools/ Hand Tools / Machinery Tools.
And I show You All Tools Life Hacks
AII TOOLS TO HELP YOU WORK BETTER..</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Gunflint Designs</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCgwaPlarb9k0PS2BQphCLNQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-pG2tjuRUYkw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/lLU7Nq6mIEA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>My name is Mark and I am a graphic designer and photographer by trade, but one of my favorite hobbies is getting out into my shop and building or fixing things. I decided to start this channel because I have often gone online looking for ways to build something, only to come up empty and deciding to figure it out on my own. I am hoping that through my trial and error I can provide others with ideas or inspiration to create their own custom projects.

I am a very busy person and I like it that way. You’ll never find me just sitting around. If I’m not tinkering on things around my house (or at my day job) then I am probably out doing something that I find exciting somewhere in the wilds of Wyoming.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Paoson WoodWorking</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC4PI8VEr1ZaKn4TBcXoy3qg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-LGCi6chwdqI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/2rfCSEUN68k/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>In this channel you will find all sorts of stuff related to woodworking, computer science, electronics, musical instruments...  On my website you will find more information.
About the videos:
My videos are not tutorials, they are only meant to be viewed as entertainment or as a source of inspiration. Woodworking is dangerous... always seek professional advice and training before using any power tools.
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Gökmen ALTUNTAŞ</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCnRwrrMKMCvcHhY5hhE3YZw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-DuddN-S1n_Y/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/vvIyz6ddXyA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>DIY Creators</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UChKlSK39lLg8eZHIX0iVzLA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-CJyJi101xpk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6DaYzr_FUnU/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Type of videos I make
- Furniture and home decor
- Woodworking and shop projects
- Limited tools (for woodworking beginners)
- Concrete </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>DIY Perks</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCUQo7nzH1sXVpzL92VesANw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-LkuGDPTRTeA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/HxBqjPiHTNY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I'm Matt, and here on DIY Perks you'll find plenty of interesting DIY projects on a variety of topics, including computers, woodworking, electronics, audio, and more!
I hope you enjoy my content, and please consider subscribing if you do!

Please do not send project questions to the below address - it's for business enquiries/general enquiries only.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Creative Channel</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCFwdmgEXDNlEX8AzDYWXQEg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-A95bSwBfzBM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/tRJcP_JKSX4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Channel Creative
Edition of Video homemade, processing instructions, details, made entirely from passion, learning, and knowledge on network and always wanted to share to everyone ...
- DIY toys, strange, toy models, automobile, boat, airplane model
- The extremely interesting toy, and creative or useful
We always want to provide you with guidance, experience, tips, how to make fun toys, the most rewarding.
- If you have ideas, experience, creativity why do not you share with everyone?
- We can not succeed without support of the of your passion.

Reupload video is strictly forbidden in any form, I will report youtube without prior notice</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>izzy swan</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCO39zTYpvWL5jx2q15Ma_Hw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-LgBZvuN7r10/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/STD8-Hk_PFo/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Here you will find everything from money saving tips,  woodworking projects, jigs and  completely wild contraptions. I have been building and designing since I was old enough to swing a hammer.  With a mind for out of the box thinking and an unusual mix of  artfull design and engineering interest, you never know whats going to happen next. with new videos every week   Come Hangout!  It's a fun Ride!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Epic Workshop</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCYZm1vNmk0x_nqGu9wHKv0A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-4WA7gNrIGMM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/OJAf3t3mH5U/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Black Beard Projects</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC8q2GgxOUS_Dzd5KIYeJQIw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-K8K9ALaOm7c/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/8pn2J1Rm1U0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to Black Beard Projects!

I’m 26 years old and live in Italy.

On my channel you’ll see all kinds of DIY projects. I have been doing things like this for years and now I want to share this passion with you.
New videos will come regularly and every time I will propose you something interesting. Be sure to subscribe you won’t be bored :D

Comments and suggestions are welcome.

See you soon!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>The Redsmith</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCqV0qSeS6i0qdymBFlLvnOw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-zQ-wdJQCIe8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/A6eUwf5rvIE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello, I'm The Redsmith. I'm a maker. I mainly work with wood, metal and leather.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Andrea's Workshop</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCIgcC0FXCaKROxx6LHZSZdg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-OVTvix7ME2o/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/90lFOMIINbk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>2014-2015 Lived in Mexico and had workshop only in garden.

2016 I moved back to Croatia and now I finally got a shop which is under construction.

I started to buy my own tools in 2013 and 2014 and started to build more serious projects and sometimes projects to sell.

Thank you for visiting my channel.
Cheers!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Scrap wood City</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCocEQojx6I6s9K_Ah2rTSlQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-_djrk-ZF-D8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/gQ68rKlBEzs/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I create things with wood scrap. </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Geeks Wood Shop</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCWIfRAZiiYeyN6pukhNBeQQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ioa2F7cKNSQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/XSj7B2cDpsg/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DIY Home and Garden</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC-PaPywUKo7dSn800KRYqDg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-XJ6BkJBQRZo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/76f7NIDtYdw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>DIY projects - step by step</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCvmsdOYwO29MYFHyU_yvtLA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ohzCMtLnJUI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/WXBb_Q3n2go/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi !
This channel is about DIY projects, ideas, renovations etc.
I'm doing many things and sometimes I have camera with me. As You will notice, sometimes my son makes the projects with me, because it is also our common hobby to make something toghether/

Here You can find some woodworking, some toys, games for children. some metalworks, knives, room, garden and home decorations and other DIY stuff and crafts. I really like to make things so I'm making a lot of them:)

New video at least once a week.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Inventables</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCK833BWBzZv7nbmU72CP4wg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/--ImfSGqSUng/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/UBySjWfYlHY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Visit our website at http://inventables.com

Our goal is to ignite a revolution in digital fabrication. To do this, we make products that bring out the maker in all of us.

Key to this is simplifying the path from idea to finished product. We believe that 3D carving is the most effective and efficient way for people to bring their ideas to life.

We offer everything necessary to make 3D carving easy and inspiring: powerful machines, intuitive software, and unique, beautiful materials.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Natural Nerd</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCggHsHce2n3vvbJf_8YKrMA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-0YjX3QHEDVY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/qk0My-vN7kw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>We're Martina & Hansi, and we like to make things. LEDs, props and and a tad of pop-culture are things that we like! Hit the subscribe button if you want to come along and do some cool stuff!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>GreatScott!</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC6mIxFTvXkWQVEHPsEdflzQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-99PZZFc0gqU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/WbIPi9QYA94/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Awesome Electronics Tutorials, Projects and How To´s</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Modern Builds</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCIxAaCJ84uefATKmazDyIjw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-B3kflbH9FtA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6oUn9yn6V8c/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Modern Builds is a collection of do-able DIY projects that anyone can complete with just a little time and creativity</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>HomeMadeModern</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC6pdMJwtkbCNoQRwbaNt77A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-rHqQAP9ylT8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/wNVGt3ijw5c/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>HomeMade-Modern.com is an online design source that shares design ideas with hopes of inspiring people to make more of the things they own.
Check out our 2nd youtube channel:  https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCM2ItlQkxzKz3lWhlU7Se0w/videos
Follow us on Instagram for project updates:  https://www.instagram.com/benjaminuyeda/?hl=en

Disclaimer: These videos are intended for entertainment and inspiration only. Woodworking and making stuff is dangerous. Always seek professional advice and training before using any power tools. If you have any uncertainty before performing any woodworking or fabricating procedure, stop and learn a safer method. Do not attempt anything simply because you saw it in one of my videos. Summary: be smart, use common sense, and respect your power tools.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Get Hands Dirty</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCETeXD_3awsQv-9rSdCYXQQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-GnIRXdxrOno/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/O5UINRGf7Ws/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>This is all about inspiring you to build stuff with your own hands!
I'm Cristiana and I make pretty much everything you see and hear and I love developing my work on lots of different medias and processes.
Enjoy and Subscribe!</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Chris DePrisco</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCgMIBD3cVwYUpdzcTOydimA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-E6X9GJgC7Ow/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/rBuoxmTH73M/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>General machining and hacking - making useful stuff out of raw materials and old, broken things.
</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Well Done Tips</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCJF8RIGIyirxgDnHgQfKcLg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-nCnYmTvcNis/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/jvsO3qldz1s/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Well Done Tips - It's all about how things should be done! If you're doing it - do it right!

What I'm making - is for my, my family or my friends needs only. I'm not a professional in any area where I working, but every time I'll do my best to get top result.
I like to make something, I like to spent time by making something. And with all my videos I want to inspire others to grab some tools and make something by your self!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Jonathan'sWorkshop</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3izzqKAMMXENiB98c0t1QA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-QGGbiQsdjAU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/KZxx0esLbX8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Engineering student fairly new to the woodworking world. Join me on my woodworking journey through the trials, errors, and successes. I'm always striving to learn more and better myself in this craft, so if you see anything you're curious about or if you want to give some advice, please reach out either over the comment section or by email. I love all the engagement from my viewers and fellow craftsmen in this community.


New videos posted monthly. Videos of woodworking, with a mixture of other projects.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Essential Craftsman</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCzr30osBdTmuFUS8IfXtXmg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-EbeQGGYRpwk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Nq76xZHyuhk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Informational videos related to blacksmithing, general construction, safety & productivity, and various other trades. The videos feature Scott Wadsworth, and cover a wide array of topics, tools, history, opinions, and lessons. The purpose of the channel is to showcase the knowledge that is gained through experience, and encourage respect for the craftsmen,  their tools,  and history.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Shelfology</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCYfxXYGVcSuOL3PgqGBG5XA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-o6CpXM1VqgU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/fU7ZR8bI29o/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>How to install all of our awesome products, and FAQ's. Downloads, guides, and purchase at www.shelfology.com</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Mistry MakeTool</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3SfkkQw9TmpjsFZTp3bdYw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-N576LzxOykI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/_mniYfI3aJg/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>“Mistry MakeTool” is a small Homemade Tools Project on YouTube channel run by myself, Sandip Mistry.
All you need to know about the Proper Use and  Guidelines  of Power Tools/ Hand Tools / Machinery Tools.
And I show You All Tools Life Hacks
AII TOOLS TO HELP YOU WORK BETTER...</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>The Samurai Carpenter</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC06fO6LNH_AUgjbmqaZRV5Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-2qkQEgD8w7w/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/XKyG633UjTM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Showing the world that there are still passionate craftsmen around who love what they do and find joy in enriching peoples lives with relationship and art.  My videos are for inspiration purposes only and I do not consider myself an expert.  Using power tools can be dangerous so be safe and work at your own risk.</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Jackman Works</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCaI4Tib6te88f_P9r8w5Tmw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Ndva53SH3TU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/u2OaLLARRPs/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Home for woodworking, construction, upcycling, reclaiming, welding, epoxy, etc. My goals are to inspire you to make cool things, get people excited about making, and teaching while keeping it super fun and interesting. Thanks for stopping by!

- Paul Jackman
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>tim sway</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3CvHbiVAaYiMY2DMd1fcEQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-TFAwg29AD3I/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/IHYlSSSTLWQ/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>i make worthless things priceless. and some other stuff. www.timsway.net</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Matthew Cremona</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCDpL0v-Ifie7u05lbfO3zJQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-wtUhzoMDiBQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/HNwflfJ3TFE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey everyone! My name is Matt and I love woodworking.  I build fine furniture using my own blend of hand and power tools and I start with cutting down a tree. My designs have a clean straight line look but I also really enjoy building period pieces. My videos aim to motivate others to challenge themselves and try something new.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>MM Wood Studio</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCZtjmKv6CdSegERDtOJUXBA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-o9ZC9iuy5fs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/61tyH4Lyejk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>MM Wood Studio is an online wood working school specializing in intermediate to advanced level projects deconstructed for the home woodworker.

To learn more and see our projects head over to http://www.mmwoodstudio.com
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Popular Woodworking</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCyxaLtaHLTUjCauqWWqCs_A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-h_CVdaYd2cI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/o4dtq2Ol_Vc/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome. We are a community of woodworkers passionate about making projects for the home and shop. Whether you are new to wooodworking or you are advancing to more developed woodworking techniques, our editors are here for you!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>FineWoodworking</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC47EhkMV18WlRqV3VhUH3yg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ao2w9KnDZGs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/AhaO1x9C91s/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Have you ever considered woodworking as a hobby but didn't where to begin? Tune in for this video series from the editors of Fine Woodworking magazine, and we'll guide you through the process. From choosing your first tools to setting up a workspace to completing your first woodworking projects, you'll discover just how easy it is to get started in woodworking. Visit our Web site for more free articles, videos, and downloadable project plans.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Paul Sellers</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCc3EpWncNq5QL0QhwUNQb7w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-b6-mrXbgvNE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/UvNOQ2z5XPM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Paul Sellers teaches woodworking online, in classes and in books. On his YouTube channel, you will find woodworking videos and instruction. Paul Sellers' channel is where he shares his woodworking experience. The woodworking videos what you can do with wood and help you to achieve better results.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Matt Estlea - Furniture</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCxWzA3ZlYEOLr1JkKH0ZMyg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-slNa_oj915s/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/jucOBOsDWnY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi there, my name's Matt Estlea and I'm a furniture making student based in the UK. I study at Rycotewood Furniture Centre, Oxford during the week and work part-time at Axminster Tools and Machinery in Basingstoke on the weekends. I use a blend of power and hand tools in my work and would love to share my experience with you in the form of long projects, techniques, tricks and product reviews to help extract your best woodworking potential.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>GuysWoodshop</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCyFyhwdDZxLCpolnaAAC1kw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-kB0M3_Bhtcs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/7Y3t4RHJ7Jk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>MM Wood Studio</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCZtjmKv6CdSegERDtOJUXBA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-o9ZC9iuy5fs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/61tyH4Lyejk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>MM Wood Studio is an online wood working school specializing in intermediate to advanced level projects deconstructed for the home woodworker.

To learn more and see our projects head over to http://www.mmwoodstudio.com
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Canadian Woodworks</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCERIGfN6ATn5-U2DGhDzOvw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-p6f9CJ6f5ec/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/YAd4ihEMKNw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Canadian handmade custom rocking chairs and table</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>The Wood Whisperer</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCKp44bWWZIiOPShPN_ytShw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-pzUii7xXzf8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/CL6HBOH1zXo/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Education and entertainment for the modern woodworker!

Have a question? Use http://www.thewoodwhisperer.com/contact/ for a quicker response</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>GarageWoodworks</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCg2cP-IsE2EsdYsvaX4MJmg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-VPEoy5WGuaA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/jZ35x0Lk3fQ/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Build woodworking projects with Garage Woodworks.
http://www.garagewoodworks.com

Advertise with GarageWoodworks LLC by making contact at http://www.garagewoodworks.com/comments.php</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>WoodWorkWeb</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCMd9JgqSESwyuOs0yuSTlEw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-zVbg9tHvtyU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/hzCQSdl44Kk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to Woodworkweb TV, the interactive resource for all woodworkers. This channel provides woodworking tips, tool reviews and step by step videos for making your own woodworking projects, jigs, and woodworking hacks.
Visit www.woodworkweb.com for more Detail, Plans and Search for for more information..</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>ThisWoodwork </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCZXRKRLIJalPdM9tAANuyUg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-DCBAdZ6WJws/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/8Q1LlvBrwTQ/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Woodworking and woodturning project and how to videos!

I am Alex Harris, a 22 year old woodworker. Here at my channel I post how-to videos of all kinds of woodworking and woodturning projects, demonstrating that just about anyone can get involved in the hobby.
Interested in making things yourself? You can learn more about woodwork, or just have fun watching me make something right here!

Be sure to Subscribe to ThisWoodwork to be notified whenever great new woodworking and woodturning videos go up!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>scottcarvings</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC4nqxR9IfLchIutaeW2PXiw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-h511AAx83N4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/eMoJXfDNLSE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>SimpleCove</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCmlRWK6jRFi2No_gDBDjwow/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-pvj3jFBTuws/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/4Ry5sQgHg-g/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>No matter what you make, share it with the world! Create your free maker portfolio on SimpleCove.com</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Andrew Pitts ~ FurnitureMaker</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCwkafRE_3ZOFltns2p1sJZw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-V-icgUxBIHQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/nGsVvq-Dehs/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>These woodworking videos show how Andy makes his fine custom furniture in his woodworking workshop. He also often demonstrates new uses for his ShopBot Desktop CNC routing machine, and has included other useful videos such as how to photograph furniture.
Andy designs and makes fine custom contemporary furniture, as well as wood carvings and liturgical furniture. The finest hardwoods and materials are used in his furniture.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>JordsWoodShop / Periodic Furniture Studio</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCt1ySOwzjjaepu7VWMtxlgw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ZUmfz--TndU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/NpRONm2032A/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>JordsWoodShop - the best woodworking show in Australia! Subscribe to receive free woodworking videos every week!</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Mitch Peacock - WOmadeOD</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCHNLNiFWZcy39ew7OskHdtw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-D0EhPKmbmzk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/VSMrKsk8ug0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Anyone with an interest in creating things, especially in wood, should find something they enjoy here

I sometimes mix many materials in my creations, and these videos are now branded with the Cre8 logo, so that pure woodies can avoid them ;-)

Some of the techniques I will share with you have been learnt, others I have developed myself and these may be unique. Whether they are the best ways to do things - that's up to you to decide!
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Nick Ferry</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCrbGKAwkVaQmTowmTYBm5Vg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-tHRcX7Q3KaQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/1_uuLdGL0QY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Making things is what I like to do.  I am going to put build videos on Fridays showing how to make a variety of things.  Wednesdays I do my vlog or "talkie talkie" going over previous builds and talking about general shop stuff.  If you are a builder, maker or DIYer this channel is for you.  Keep up to date by subscribing so you don't miss a thing.  Thanks for stopping by and I'll see you soon!
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Jay Bates</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC-7XY-W_C84cW2MNqujgFpg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-b5kAO6E7LSQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/3l71ZJYDGjE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>




<plugin>
  <title>Giaco Whatever</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCYH-XXUE2QDaWKvABsWJh8w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-gVlyW2lRlmA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/8TFHzooMD_Q/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Stuff and Video Maker!
My videos are really far from being tutorials. I teach myself how to do things taking and camera along.
My hope is to inspire you to make anything you want!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Jeremy Schmidt</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC0T7tvy44mlQCjaTtparOZw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-gjHm4_irp5o/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/fCQGbxE5Xq0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I am a woodworker, metalworker, and maker. I love to make tools, so that is the subject of many of my videos. I hope to throw out a few ideas that will help other makers, and inspire everyone to make something!

Note: If you leave a comment--especially a question--and I do not reply, check your comment settings. You likely have it set so that I cannot reply.

Note: I will occasionally show what some may believe to be unsafe practices. Safety is a personal responsibility. If you feel uncomfortable doing something that I did in a video, don't do it. I am not responsible for injuries, should you choose to follow my example.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>David Waelder</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCcapFP3gxL1aJiC8RdwxqRA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-t1Aht2rwmmg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/lOybZcG8z4Y/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I make things from all kinds of materials. The channel is pretty organic, I shoot things I like, and find interesting. Use caution with your tools, this channel is for entertainment, and inspiration. Thanks for tuning in!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Kyle Toth</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCn_4fr5sKRorFuq479M7Kig/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-MiWcIqopMsQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/D7l870_rzCU/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>When you think of Wood Think of Toth. Making custom woodworks in Southern California.
For inquiries Contact  Woodbytoth@gmail.com
If you want some thing made by me just ask!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>frank howarth</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3_VCOJMaivgcGqPCTePLBA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-GMkkUpV4PX0/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/bJaQNN3eAXs/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Architecture at a small scale expressed through woodworking and film making.

Disclaimer:  My videos here are for entertainment, to share what I do, and to maybe provide some inspiration.  Woodworking can be dangerous if all safety precautions are not taken.  Please don't try anything I am doing just because you saw me doing it. Understand that there are years of learning and experimentation by me that are not in the videos.  You can have a safe, enjoyable, and even inspirational time in your shop by understanding your own tools, materials, and your own skill level.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Jay Bates</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC-7XY-W_C84cW2MNqujgFpg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-b5kAO6E7LSQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/3l71ZJYDGjE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>The Rehab Life</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC5ncuNyZTN3OGuixQXOiAYQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-87utZ1spox8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/x70_FkkR0QI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Minneapolis Property Rehabbers!
Easy DIY videos to make cool cheap stuff for your home.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Ana White</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC8oVoLGDj2spRfZfxgf54tw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-KlyJval_yW0/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/3qn4T1X50Ag/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Let's Build Something!!!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Shanty2Chic</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCMJiIIydhPvmDvLfeHvKiLQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-30xc5hRtwYk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/nRx16UF59Ec/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Sisters, woodworkers, renovators, and lovers of tools.

 If you have a project you want us to build, let us know in the comments or on our social media @shanty2chic :)  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Crafted Workshop</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC-hTi9atsD6wAl2s46LpAVw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Gn54PAf6sJc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/mMfteLZUg5w/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Weekly how-to project videos about woodworking, metalworking, and more. Created by Johnny Brooke.
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>GardenFork</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCAh44GRXNB-iB0IWBJ0gGbQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-BYnPPPTxtNY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/OyuCsekrkOY/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>GardenFork is an eclectic DIY Maker channel with how to videos on urban homesteading, home improvement, cooking, gardening, beekeeping and more.  

We post  new videos every week, which range from Artisan Dutch Oven Bread to Plywood Boats to Starting a New Beehive.

The show is a mashup of Alton Brown's Good Eats, Make Magazine, and This Old House, but we leave in all the mistakes.  

Done is better than perfect is the GardenFork mantra. Life is messy and so is GardenFork, come along for the ride!
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>tim sway</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3CvHbiVAaYiMY2DMd1fcEQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-TFAwg29AD3I/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/IHYlSSSTLWQ/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>i make worthless things priceless. and some other stuff. www.timsway.net</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Raina's Universe</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UChK5xGod0gVc9G6DVqduw5Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-pLQqt9suwy8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/OSz3pHYunv8/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>hi, I'm Raina. I'm 16. I vlog. In NYC. Subscribe and join Raina's Universe!

I’m a violinist, orchestra and chamber music player, clarinetist, figure skater. I love pets, physics and space, baseballs, traveling, and getting to know the world. I like a bunch of things, so you'll see that my videos are about a bunch of different things!


Who are these people in my videos?🤔

-Jimmy Diresta appears in a few of my videos. 
He's known me since I was little, and he has over 1,000,000 subscribers. Subscribe to him.</summary>
</plugin>




<plugin>
<title>Death Wears Bunny Slippers - Owning a Missile Silo</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCd50A5qLv8FemVufSvDgkCQ/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/ACSszfEUzbqN9CQh-VlG6BqAPNslOXE2mFqPNujYYQ=s88-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>I'm one of those people that probably won't ever have a savings account because I'm spending money on ridiculous crap. Well, a Titan II Nuclear Missile Silo seemed like a good idea at the time. Maybe I was drunk. Since 2010 I've ended up in the hospital a few times and almost died a few others. And while we just created this channel, we've been recording videos of interesting events for the last 6 years. Some of it wasn't shot in HD because I was too broke spending my money on a hole in the ground. Sorry about that. 

We appreciate your support as we continue the adventure of owning one of the most ridiculously awesome things ever. 
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Chris Salomone</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC1V-DYqsaj764uBis9-UDug/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-xmUq1xPrpgQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/wsXLLhNIuTc/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I love designing things..and I tolerate building them.

I'm not the greatest designer, woodworker, film maker, speaker, or anything else. But I think the things I make are pretty decent...and I enjoy them. I hope you'll enjoy them too.

At the very least I hope to entertain you, and at the very most I hope to inspire you. 

Thank you for reading...and happy building!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>ZH Fabrications</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCDdZMJDDpyvI9WJyY7IZP7w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Dnym9KU4qzM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/8KlWcPBTp1U/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey, I'm a metal fabricator, woodworker, and amateur blacksmith who is new to youtube, and I'm terrible at introductions. I'm going to try and do my best to get one video a week posted here, I'd like to hear your input as well as your ideas for upcoming projects.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title></title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel//</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>
