################################################################################
<cache>10800</cache>
<fanart>https://images.fastcompany.net/image/upload/fc/3060718-poster-p-1-10-ways-to-make-slack-simpler-safer-and-less-annoying.jpg</fanart>
<thumbnail>http://pngimg.com/uploads/youtube/youtube_PNG10.png</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
###################################################################################




<plugin>
  <title>Alec Steele</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCWizIdwZdmr43zfxlCktmNw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-V_jCF9fW3Bc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/nMWJKdlFdTU/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>My name's Alec Steele and here you'll find near-daily videos documenting the process of building some awesome projects here in the shop. As a blacksmith, most of the projects start as lumps of steel, or stacks of different alloys for making damascus, that I forge out into blades, sculpture, art or tools before taking the project to the machining equipment or into the grinding room for finishing. Each project teaches me a lot and stretches the bounds of my knowledge. I make a lot of mistakes but they serve as an excellent teacher. There's always something important for me to learn in the shop! 

I want my work to be the spark that ignites the desire for you to get into your shop (or kitchen/basement/garage) and make something too! Whether it's stitching a leather wallet or forging a giant sword, you'll love the creative process.

Be sure to follow me on instagram @alecsteele for behind the scenes and grab some awesome t-shirts at https://alecsteeleshop.com/

Thanks! 
Alec</summary>
</plugin>







<plugin>
  <title>Master Engraver TV</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCQPGRIDdNnbLKK0Qwvo0-pw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAxu9YdycD3yrrG7pRyWQCroV1HGnd5JhHD_hg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Master Engraver TV is dedicated to providing informational videos on the art of hand engraving. Layne Zuelke is one of only 50 Firearms Engravers Guild of America Certified Master Engravers with over 30 years experience at the bench and the owner of Southern Custom Engraving studio in Baton Rouge, Louisiana. You’ll fine in depth tutorials on all aspects of gun, knife, watch and jewelry engraving. Everything from basic subjects to advanced techniques using all manner of equipment  will be covered. The channel was started in  an effort to provide authoritative, in depth information on a craft that for centuries was learned only by exhaustive self discovery or by long apprenticeships. While these videos cannot replace formal study under a qualified instructor, they will serve to fill in the gaps and unlock some of the mystery behind the fine art of hand engraving. If we teach those who know less and learn from those who know more we are all better for it.
  </summary>
</plugin>




<plugin>
  <title>EvanAndKatelyn</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCUuMYw2l2UeWyTGYixYfRCA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-poIhH2w02l8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/UPhxau3FzCA/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey guys, we're Evan and Katelyn and we make stuff together: woodworking, 3D printing, welding, props, CNC, home projects, sometimes practical stuff, sometimes totally unnecessary but fun stuff.

The reason we started this channel is partly for y'all, but partly for us too. We want to show that making stuff is fun and accessible, even if you're figuring it out as you go (like we often are). But also, we wanna work together. We're basically each others favorite person, and being able to do stuff we love with the person we love is pretty much the dream.

So if you like making things, enjoy a heavy dose of goofiness and expertly aimed high fives, and want to see a random stream of cool things we make in a new video each week, please consider subscribing and sharing our channel. Thanks! Bye!
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Michaelcthulhu</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCGca03sbLq7OUnXMdvRHyBQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-M80n2s-9j2o/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/fmMfJHYsnos/s176-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I make Giant Swords. I sell them to people. People like you. Check out my Facebook page. Don't follow me on Twitter.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>AWE me </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCNKcMBYP_-18FLgk4BYGtfw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Cyvc2dQEOzk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/5dI0etkZ3Jc/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>AWE me is here to Amaze, Wow, and Educate.
Home to Mind-Blowing shows Man At Arms: Reforged, Super Fan Builds, DIY Prop Shop and DIY Cosplay Shop, and Epic How To! 

New videos  every other Monday at 10am PDT.

Whether it’s a video with our expert blacksmiths forging Katarina’s Daggers from League of Legends, or our master prop builder making a Groot (Guardians of the Galaxy) swing set for a Super Fan, or Joe Bereta teaching you the easy way to become Batman, AWE me will inspire you to raise your game!
</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Mr. Volt</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCvOOv9tfBMSzcXnDkgzMufA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-5wuVSn5-omQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/S8DPHvbSzik/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Props - Gadgets - DIY Technology</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Epic Workshop</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCYZm1vNmk0x_nqGu9wHKv0A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-4WA7gNrIGMM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/OJAf3t3mH5U/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>The Redsmith</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCqV0qSeS6i0qdymBFlLvnOw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-zQ-wdJQCIe8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/A6eUwf5rvIE/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello, I'm The Redsmith. I'm a maker. I mainly work with wood, metal and leather.</summary>
</plugin>







<plugin>
  <title>Make N' Create</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCbOOTKHBOXyFfACvhGJnSCg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-biCne7GjWqU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/CF0kRwUA8RU/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I'm a guy who likes to work with wood and alot of other different materials and make whatever i find fun. So i decided to make videos out of whatever it is i'm making.
Disclaimer: I am by no means a professional. Anything you see in my videos may not be the best/smartest/safest way of doing it.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>3D Central</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCeYZg5Ynx0gGdeKQ-v7N8nQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-GE-hlFp7W0s/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/fXBlJTnXzl8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi, we're 3D Central! We've been 3D Printing since 2011, and we've turned our passion into Virginia's first 3D Printing shop!

Want to send us something? Want to visit the shop? Here's our address, check out our hours on our page!
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Tempest Rings</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCfdCFlodE6Lphcy9Gr6_1BQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-5fSU-WnvTyw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/wwx4_bhUKoE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Just making rings.Just making rings.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Modustrial Maker</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC9aRTgvFLqnK1S0RsWZzlMw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-lYhUFQiE-D4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/UgZSlv2UFX8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>DIY Build Videos for my modern industrial creations.   If you like what you see, subscribe to get notifications about future videos.

To see what I'm working on before build videos are posted, follow me on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/modustrialmaker/?hl=en

Also, check out my Modustrial Maker website, where I plan to post more content, including photos and details of past projects that were completed before I started documenting my work with video for this channel.

www.modustrialmaker.com</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Patrick Adair Designs</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCJ82SlfYWJag5794tE64ZZA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-DgfyH1jzxFU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/P3pA-QPP8YI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi! My name is Patrick Adair and I love creating. I film a lot of the projects I do and upload them here. I specialize in rings made of materials like carbon fiber, titanium, and other random rare materials.</summary>
</plugin>






<plugin>
  <title>I Like To Make Stuff </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC6x7GwJxuoABSosgVXDYtTw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-kVJyRVXzd7E/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/jFcJXJDNz68/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I like to make all sorts of stuff, with all sorts of materials. I have lots of projects including woodworking, metalworking, electronics, 3D printing, prop making and more!

These videos are my attempt at teaching, inspiring and empowering others to make the stuff that they want to have. Hopefully you'll see something here that will inspire you to make something that you're passionate about!
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>I Like To Make Stuff 2</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCruM8e10ljDk6VEe1XrUxQA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-5hEF1lqaDus/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/UdlhNbROZvI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Behind the scenes and extra stuff that doesn't fit on http://www.youtube.com/iliketomakestuffcom </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>jimmydiresta</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCiEk4xHBbz0hZNIBBpowdYQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-zHnRwS1sk6I/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/e86upfV2RVQ/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I make stuff for a living, what you see me do here is my Job.  I have been using tools for over 40 years. I have developed my comfort level with tools through years of experience. DON'T DO THE DANGEROUS THINGS I DO. Thank You for watching and subscribing!
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Laura Kampf</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCRix1GJvSBNDpEFY561eSzw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-RkDtiQl-_Qc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6L9--55KnBg/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Watch me make all kinds of stuff in my shop!

Build Videos on Sundays
Vlogs every other week
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Shop built</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCZBqq0o54ShN5cSTflT2MnQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Wiw2O1GDSdo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/bvHoeNwxNGc/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>just some videos of stuff I build in my shop.
New videos every second Friday! sometimes, not really:(
Use all proper safety precaution when working around power tools. including using the the proper PPE.
These videos are for entertainment only. </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Will Matthews</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCh9J-RX5wpjjJdYZ3WVkrYg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-_dRBj4vxnDw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/y6Dbkgq7Y4A/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>If you enjoy watching woodworking, tool restoration, blacksmithing, forging, making and other craftsman projects, then subscribe and stay tuned! I endeavour to post videos of my journey as I build, create & discover. I am by no means an expert, but hope to provide some entertainment and value to the viewer through these videos.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Hand Tool Rescue</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCasG9kJWi1eVxM0QkyqKVJQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-tSQenI6Wdp8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/94RaV91C5H4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Tool restorations and rescues.

I rescue tools and put them back in the hands of people who can appreciate them.

I will restore a tool for free if it is interesting enough for a video.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>The Small Workshop</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCWSRNbhnlahD43ZNPkNUTzA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-xyJgob9n_xc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/lmiMHL0oGDU/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Homemade tools and workshop projects, in wood and metal!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>John Heisz I Build It</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCjA8vRlL1c7BDixQRJ39-LQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-s1iavblFQoE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/GNe5z6utYU0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Videos on woodworking and workshop related projects.
Check out my website for hundreds of cool projects: www.ibuildit.ca

Me and my shop are in Ontario, Canada. I'm a carpenter by trade and have worked in commercial construction since 1985.

Concerning my videos:
I can't and won't cover (or follow) every safety rule when doing a project, and it's not my responsibility to train the people that watch my videos. It is up to them to learn, understand and follow the safety rules concerning the tools they choose to work with.
My videos are not comprehensive tutorials - they are a look at how I did the project and should be viewed as entertainment or a source of inspiration.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Mistry MakeTool</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3SfkkQw9TmpjsFZTp3bdYw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-N576LzxOykI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/_mniYfI3aJg/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>“Mistry MakeTool” is a small Homemade Tools Project on YouTube channel run by myself, Sandip Mistry.
All you need to know about the Proper Use and  Guidelines  of Power Tools/ Hand Tools / Machinery Tools.
And I show You All Tools Life Hacks
AII TOOLS TO HELP YOU WORK BETTER..</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Paoson WoodWorking</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC4PI8VEr1ZaKn4TBcXoy3qg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-LGCi6chwdqI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/2rfCSEUN68k/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>In this channel you will find all sorts of stuff related to woodworking, computer science, electronics, musical instruments...  On my website you will find more information.
About the videos:
My videos are not tutorials, they are only meant to be viewed as entertainment or as a source of inspiration. Woodworking is dangerous... always seek professional advice and training before using any power tools.
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Gökmen ALTUNTAŞ</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCnRwrrMKMCvcHhY5hhE3YZw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-DuddN-S1n_Y/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/vvIyz6ddXyA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>DIY Creators</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UChKlSK39lLg8eZHIX0iVzLA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-CJyJi101xpk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6DaYzr_FUnU/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Type of videos I make
- Furniture and home decor
- Woodworking and shop projects
- Limited tools (for woodworking beginners)
- Concrete </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>DIY Perks</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCUQo7nzH1sXVpzL92VesANw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-LkuGDPTRTeA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/HxBqjPiHTNY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I'm Matt, and here on DIY Perks you'll find plenty of interesting DIY projects on a variety of topics, including computers, woodworking, electronics, audio, and more!
I hope you enjoy my content, and please consider subscribing if you do!

Please do not send project questions to the below address - it's for business enquiries/general enquiries only.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Creative Channel</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCFwdmgEXDNlEX8AzDYWXQEg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-A95bSwBfzBM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/tRJcP_JKSX4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Channel Creative
Edition of Video homemade, processing instructions, details, made entirely from passion, learning, and knowledge on network and always wanted to share to everyone ...
- DIY toys, strange, toy models, automobile, boat, airplane model
- The extremely interesting toy, and creative or useful
We always want to provide you with guidance, experience, tips, how to make fun toys, the most rewarding.
- If you have ideas, experience, creativity why do not you share with everyone?
- We can not succeed without support of the of your passion.

Reupload video is strictly forbidden in any form, I will report youtube without prior notice</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>izzy swan</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCO39zTYpvWL5jx2q15Ma_Hw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-LgBZvuN7r10/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/STD8-Hk_PFo/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Here you will find everything from money saving tips,  woodworking projects, jigs and  completely wild contraptions. I have been building and designing since I was old enough to swing a hammer.  With a mind for out of the box thinking and an unusual mix of  artfull design and engineering interest, you never know whats going to happen next. with new videos every week   Come Hangout!  It's a fun Ride!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Black Beard Projects</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC8q2GgxOUS_Dzd5KIYeJQIw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-K8K9ALaOm7c/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/8pn2J1Rm1U0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to Black Beard Projects!

I’m 26 years old and live in Italy.

On my channel you’ll see all kinds of DIY projects. I have been doing things like this for years and now I want to share this passion with you.
New videos will come regularly and every time I will propose you something interesting. Be sure to subscribe you won’t be bored :D

Comments and suggestions are welcome.

See you soon!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Geeks Wood Shop</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCWIfRAZiiYeyN6pukhNBeQQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ioa2F7cKNSQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/XSj7B2cDpsg/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DIY projects - step by step</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCvmsdOYwO29MYFHyU_yvtLA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ohzCMtLnJUI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/WXBb_Q3n2go/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi !
This channel is about DIY projects, ideas, renovations etc.
I'm doing many things and sometimes I have camera with me. As You will notice, sometimes my son makes the projects with me, because it is also our common hobby to make something toghether/

Here You can find some woodworking, some toys, games for children. some metalworks, knives, room, garden and home decorations and other DIY stuff and crafts. I really like to make things so I'm making a lot of them:)

New video at least once a week.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Inventables</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCK833BWBzZv7nbmU72CP4wg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/--ImfSGqSUng/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/UBySjWfYlHY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Visit our website at http://inventables.com

Our goal is to ignite a revolution in digital fabrication. To do this, we make products that bring out the maker in all of us.

Key to this is simplifying the path from idea to finished product. We believe that 3D carving is the most effective and efficient way for people to bring their ideas to life.

We offer everything necessary to make 3D carving easy and inspiring: powerful machines, intuitive software, and unique, beautiful materials.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Natural Nerd</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCggHsHce2n3vvbJf_8YKrMA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-0YjX3QHEDVY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/qk0My-vN7kw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>We're Martina & Hansi, and we like to make things. LEDs, props and and a tad of pop-culture are things that we like! Hit the subscribe button if you want to come along and do some cool stuff!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>GreatScott!</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC6mIxFTvXkWQVEHPsEdflzQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-99PZZFc0gqU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/WbIPi9QYA94/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Awesome Electronics Tutorials, Projects and How To´s</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Modern Builds</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCIxAaCJ84uefATKmazDyIjw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-B3kflbH9FtA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6oUn9yn6V8c/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Modern Builds is a collection of do-able DIY projects that anyone can complete with just a little time and creativity</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>HomeMadeModern</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC6pdMJwtkbCNoQRwbaNt77A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-rHqQAP9ylT8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/wNVGt3ijw5c/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>HomeMade-Modern.com is an online design source that shares design ideas with hopes of inspiring people to make more of the things they own.
Check out our 2nd youtube channel:  https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCM2ItlQkxzKz3lWhlU7Se0w/videos
Follow us on Instagram for project updates:  https://www.instagram.com/benjaminuyeda/?hl=en

Disclaimer: These videos are intended for entertainment and inspiration only. Woodworking and making stuff is dangerous. Always seek professional advice and training before using any power tools. If you have any uncertainty before performing any woodworking or fabricating procedure, stop and learn a safer method. Do not attempt anything simply because you saw it in one of my videos. Summary: be smart, use common sense, and respect your power tools.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Chris DePrisco</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCgMIBD3cVwYUpdzcTOydimA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-E6X9GJgC7Ow/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/rBuoxmTH73M/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>General machining and hacking - making useful stuff out of raw materials and old, broken things.
</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Well Done Tips</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCJF8RIGIyirxgDnHgQfKcLg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-nCnYmTvcNis/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/jvsO3qldz1s/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Well Done Tips - It's all about how things should be done! If you're doing it - do it right!

What I'm making - is for my, my family or my friends needs only. I'm not a professional in any area where I working, but every time I'll do my best to get top result.
I like to make something, I like to spent time by making something. And with all my videos I want to inspire others to grab some tools and make something by your self!</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Essential Craftsman</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCzr30osBdTmuFUS8IfXtXmg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-EbeQGGYRpwk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Nq76xZHyuhk/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Informational videos related to blacksmithing, general construction, safety & productivity, and various other trades. The videos feature Scott Wadsworth, and cover a wide array of topics, tools, history, opinions, and lessons. The purpose of the channel is to showcase the knowledge that is gained through experience, and encourage respect for the craftsmen,  their tools,  and history.</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>tim sway</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3CvHbiVAaYiMY2DMd1fcEQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-TFAwg29AD3I/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/IHYlSSSTLWQ/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>i make worthless things priceless. and some other stuff. www.timsway.net</summary>
</plugin>








<plugin>
  <title>Giaco Whatever</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCYH-XXUE2QDaWKvABsWJh8w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-gVlyW2lRlmA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/8TFHzooMD_Q/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Stuff and Video Maker!
My videos are really far from being tutorials. I teach myself how to do things taking and camera along.
My hope is to inspire you to make anything you want!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Jeremy Schmidt</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC0T7tvy44mlQCjaTtparOZw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-gjHm4_irp5o/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/fCQGbxE5Xq0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I am a woodworker, metalworker, and maker. I love to make tools, so that is the subject of many of my videos. I hope to throw out a few ideas that will help other makers, and inspire everyone to make something!

Note: If you leave a comment--especially a question--and I do not reply, check your comment settings. You likely have it set so that I cannot reply.

Note: I will occasionally show what some may believe to be unsafe practices. Safety is a personal responsibility. If you feel uncomfortable doing something that I did in a video, don't do it. I am not responsible for injuries, should you choose to follow my example.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>David Waelder</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCcapFP3gxL1aJiC8RdwxqRA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-t1Aht2rwmmg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/lOybZcG8z4Y/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I make things from all kinds of materials. The channel is pretty organic, I shoot things I like, and find interesting. Use caution with your tools, this channel is for entertainment, and inspiration. Thanks for tuning in!</summary>
</plugin>




<plugin>
  <title>Ana White</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC8oVoLGDj2spRfZfxgf54tw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-KlyJval_yW0/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/3qn4T1X50Ag/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Let's Build Something!!!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Shanty2Chic</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCMJiIIydhPvmDvLfeHvKiLQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-30xc5hRtwYk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/nRx16UF59Ec/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Sisters, woodworkers, renovators, and lovers of tools.

 If you have a project you want us to build, let us know in the comments or on our social media @shanty2chic :)  </summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>GardenFork</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCAh44GRXNB-iB0IWBJ0gGbQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-BYnPPPTxtNY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/OyuCsekrkOY/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>GardenFork is an eclectic DIY Maker channel with how to videos on urban homesteading, home improvement, cooking, gardening, beekeeping and more.  

We post  new videos every week, which range from Artisan Dutch Oven Bread to Plywood Boats to Starting a New Beehive.

The show is a mashup of Alton Brown's Good Eats, Make Magazine, and This Old House, but we leave in all the mistakes.  

Done is better than perfect is the GardenFork mantra. Life is messy and so is GardenFork, come along for the ride!
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Raina's Universe</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UChK5xGod0gVc9G6DVqduw5Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-pLQqt9suwy8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/OSz3pHYunv8/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>hi, I'm Raina. I'm 16. I vlog. In NYC. Subscribe and join Raina's Universe!

I’m a violinist, orchestra and chamber music player, clarinetist, figure skater. I love pets, physics and space, baseballs, traveling, and getting to know the world. I like a bunch of things, so you'll see that my videos are about a bunch of different things!


Who are these people in my videos?🤔

-Jimmy Diresta appears in a few of my videos. 
He's known me since I was little, and he has over 1,000,000 subscribers. Subscribe to him.</summary>
</plugin>




<plugin>
<title>Death Wears Bunny Slippers - Owning a Missile Silo</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCd50A5qLv8FemVufSvDgkCQ/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/ACSszfEUzbqN9CQh-VlG6BqAPNslOXE2mFqPNujYYQ=s88-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>I'm one of those people that probably won't ever have a savings account because I'm spending money on ridiculous crap. Well, a Titan II Nuclear Missile Silo seemed like a good idea at the time. Maybe I was drunk. Since 2010 I've ended up in the hospital a few times and almost died a few others. And while we just created this channel, we've been recording videos of interesting events for the last 6 years. Some of it wasn't shot in HD because I was too broke spending my money on a hole in the ground. Sorry about that. 

We appreciate your support as we continue the adventure of owning one of the most ridiculously awesome things ever. 
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>ZH Fabrications</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCDdZMJDDpyvI9WJyY7IZP7w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Dnym9KU4qzM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/8KlWcPBTp1U/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hey, I'm a metal fabricator, woodworker, and amateur blacksmith who is new to youtube, and I'm terrible at introductions. I'm going to try and do my best to get one video a week posted here, I'd like to hear your input as well as your ideas for upcoming projects.</summary>
</plugin>

