##########################################################################################
<cache>10800</cache>
<fanart>https://u.cubeupload.com/Nd8UdD.png</fanart>
##########################################################################################

<plugin>
  <title>Moondra</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC0bkqrWNBKxGZi-4gIfaCpg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mBqAHWqKJrsHFRL1KspcRFozEg8GMQVq898bg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>What's going on guys, I love all things related to science and technology.
This channel will mainly focus on Python related tutorials, but I'm also learning Swift at the moment as well have an interest in C++/ Cuda to optimize my code. 

Please leave comments and feedback as to what you like or dislike, and what you would like to see.

Thanks for stopping by!
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>buildwithpython</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCirPbvoHzD78Lnyll6YYUpg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mClB0hGNcgwL7DGBKyErVNwlh6kmodS_RCyJg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Learn python by building in-depth projects and going beyond the basics. The channel currently includes Python Network Programming, Socket Programming, building GUI's, Python Web Development using Django.
</summary>
</plugin>
<plugin>
  <title>Hackster.IO</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCqQzKnjSPjkJGMcjPg-Wktw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-GsgtE2acfzQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/jECLjdqJflM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hackster is the fastest growing, online community for creating hardware. From beginners to the advanced, Hackster empowers people everywhere to learn, build and sell their creations without the traditional overhead of manufacturing, retail and venture capital. Founded by hardware and software entrepreneurs, Hackster’s mission is to help Makers succeed in their own right.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Adafruit</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCpOlOeQjj7EsVnDh3zuCgsA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-R5LcGpdqijA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/cRkSb00nxz4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Adafruit was founded in 2005 by MIT engineer, Limor "Ladyada" Fried. Her goal was to create the best place online for learning electronics and making the best designed products for makers of all ages and skill levels. Adafruit has grown to over 50 employees in the heart of NYC with a 15,000+ sq ft. factory. Adafruit has expanded offerings to include tools, equipment and electronics that Limor personally selects, tests and approves before going in to the Adafruit store. Limor was the first female engineer on the cover of WIRED magazine and was recently awarded Entrepreneur magazine's Entrepreneur of the year. Ladyada is on the NYC Industrial Business Advisory Council. In 2014 Adafruit was ranked #11 in the top 20 USA manufacturing companies and #1 in New York City by Inc. 5000 "fastest growing private companies".</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Pimoroni</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCuiDNTaTdPTGZZzHm0iriGQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://pbs.twimg.com/profile_images/886668856089079836/OcvZ5_wV_400x400.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Pimoroni are a bunch of Makers and Educators with a workshop in Sheffield, UK. We make friendly electronics, mainly for the Raspberry Pi, and run a beautiful shop for Makers, where we ship the best gear worldwide.
http://shop.pimoroni.com</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Geek Gurl Diaries</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCxrp2coE9wRrnlOO3V3UmdQ/</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>Like Raspberry Pi, Arduino, Python, Programming, Computer Science, Logic, Electronics, and being geeky and awesome? I do, so I started to make videos for people like me!  Welcome to the Geek Gurl Diaries, where us gurl's discuss, create, demo and interview all things geek. If you have ideas for videos or tutorials, or you know someone cool I could interview then please get in touch.

I also host Crash Course Computer Science if you are interested in learning more about how computers work. https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL8dPuuaLjXtNlUrzyH5r6jN9ulIgZBpdo</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Afrotechmods</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCosnWgi3eorc1klEQ8pIgJQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Z5BCK-CRpnw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/yzOKIagS8G0/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Straight to the point electronics tutorial videos with practical examples taught by a professional electronics engineer.
Advertising opportunities available on the main website http://www.afrotechmods.com.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>The Ben Heck Show</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UChturLXwYxwTOf_5krs0qvA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-8OHTkE0rqRo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/5wcFROnoTIE/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>**New Episodes Every Friday**

Join master hacker, engineer, and tech hobbyist Ben Heck as he tackles new and fun interesting projects each week. Whether he's combining a PS3, Wii U, and Xbox into one mega video game system or building his own pinball machine, Ben shows you step by step how you can take on all kinds of electronic projects. Ben also shares useful tips and answers your questions about 3D printing, microcontrollers, circuitry, modeling, design, and much more. What should Ben build next? Let us know!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Glitch's Gadgets</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCVYXdg27BqwS2P9vo4p29dw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-MRiE0Y-KNhM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/oSdeHexo-8w/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
<title>WorkshopScience</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCGWi9th5QN2OsQYtc7r9Enw/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ne4GA1D1F5o/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/lgLT5AhBBB0/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>This channel is dedicated towards aerial cinematography, RC models and virtual reality</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Ronald Nelson</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCvITGCFI7UBQt62OBZ368KQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAwidjTOgVY_9y7500PHpLRQVaOKNULwa6Podw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>This channel is about me and what I do. More recently it has become a place where I show some of the DIY items that I make and some of these I give away or sell. For more information visit: http://indukudesign.com/</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>ElectroBOOM</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCJ0-OtVpF0wOKEqT2Z1HEtA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-iXZgN0vGYlE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6yamX7m-CMo/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Find the craziness in engineering from me, Mehdi Sadaghdar, but don't try them at home...
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Electronoobs</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCjiVhIvGmRZixSzupD0sS9Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAwexDsD2_5W7-cCG9PlZz8uEQn7l2wgSDzfFQ=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>If you are interested in electronics, 3D printing or just want to build something, here you will learn all that. Tutorials on basic circuits , building printers , lights , lasers, arduino and much more. I will upload videos periodically and I'm sure that you would like them. ENJOY and learn
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
<title>Data Science Dojo</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCzL_0nIe8B4-7ShhVPfJkgw/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAy9ZfyjqlAP1tpk_Kc-EgLKblWgU3P8IQOLyQ=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>At Data Science Dojo, we believe data science is for everyone. Our in-person data science training has been attended by more than 3,500+ from over 600 companies globally. This channel contains tutorials, community talks, and courses on data science and data engineering.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>CodeWithOhid</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/CodeWithOhid/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAx-hdU1enTNWouovDr5vk-JC-gIfLiVq-gBgg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>It's time to take your skills to another level. 

What topics I am covering in this channel:
✔️ Python   ✔️ C++   ✔️ Bootstrap   ✔️ Wireframe Design   ✔️ More Upcoming</summary>
</plugin>
