<plugin>
  <title>Shop Time</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3CrzXzBFVqEopj5T1jiRtA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-XEL_2E2Ni3Y/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/QkojIu83a0U/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Just a geek with a full set of power tools!

I do woodworking, woodturning or whatever piques my interest at the time. My hope is to have one part woodworking and one part crazy. I 'll try my best to make something interesting. This is just for fun, please don't do what I do in the shop.

All of the content shown is for the sole purpose of entertainment and is not intended for educational purposes in any format. Anyone choosing of their own free will to reenact or recreate any of this content assumes all personal liability and or responsibility by doing so. Woodworking especially with power tools is very dangerous and can cause serious bodily harm,  therefore proper education and training is advised.  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Andy Phillip</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCDQz4H7tz6Fwu5_5rg4W6pA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAwjPRf5grn5Fcr7KyFklGkJBJFKLQpFJtVoTA=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>I try to make interesting pieces using different combinations of woods and resins , sometimes they work sometimes they don't !! Thanks for watching ...
I have started posting work in progress pictures on instagram if anyone's interested see link below ...


DISCLAIMER :
My videos are for entertainment only. Always read and understand your manufacturers guidelines and safety instructions. 
The methods I use may not be safest so please be responsible for your own safety ..
If in doubt - "DON'T DO IT"
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Woodturners Journal</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCKYZcU_4PWu5OtZ0h-Jsx5g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAy5jqSVuRHWLn1EZDUDxOFlmEQb8ZWgC6PRHQ=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>This channel is for woodturners or people that are interested in woodturning.  It's a place to watch and see some of my projects come to life, ask questions, learn, and maybe become inspired to turn your own projects.
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Le PicBois</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCcM_SykaFqrxVnq52MjI6UA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAyUx1aZFExRiawYoOTRccFANJbLGEmEran9Lw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>This channel is mainly about woodturning & woodworking. But if you see me fooling around, don't panic that's normal! ;)</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Keith Barrow</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC1xj8Lp_fmCX0GXr208rP9w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAyKrXW_UnkcawIZVZSgL6xKoG1-h7do9dYkCQ=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Woodturning from the beginning.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Nick Zammeti</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC3-0S7vXfwYY2jj5EkMpymA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAyC7jvKhOA8_gfmANLI6XyrslbT-X9WtbkOFQ=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello and welcome to my channel. 

My name is Nick and I make unique crafted items from wood and resin.  All items I make are one of a kind. I sell most things on my website. www.nzwoodturning.co.uk </summary>
</plugin>