
<plugin>
<title>nuggetnoggin</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCm_Fbx0tAqAOB3cA4d1GnXw/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-82a1Gy6FdWs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/j-gDjb5FEe8/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>I'm Michael, I have been metal detecting for 8 years now. I really enjoy discovering the past! Come along with me and feel the excitement of treasure hunting.

If you are interested in purchasing a Metal Detector please visit my store at https://www.battleground-detectors.com

God bless!</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Broken Window Theory</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCQjlzE-BSD1PDW988vbqVjw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAy-Lq57hbH3vbcKgZfERzfzSL4O8ldEXF_ovg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Abandoned buildings, haunted locations, rotten or lost places - however you call it - we urbex it. Urban Exploration is a passion we pursue for some years now. We - that are Till and Marco, two students from Germany. Our goal is to consistently produce high quality and unique videos about these special places - about Urban Exploring. 

See you in the comments or on our social media channels. Or maybe at the next abandoned place? ;)</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Exploring the Unbeaten Path</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC73dVtWf9mpjiWYkXyIlm7A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-rUShiHKDPpA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Fd1kmEJgaOs/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>For 11 years we visit the coolest abandoned buildings in Europe, Asia, Africa and the US and experience crazy adventures.
    After the TV series "Exitus" (Which was broadcasted in Belgium and The Netherlands in 2016) we decided to make our own channel
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Abandoned or Cool</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCbVIfFGdSc4BJFL0qdglHiQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAyrLJcUrm39zoadjEna_Kh6ChAPkslAac5ghw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Join as as we travel the United States exploring abandoned or cool places. We try to incorporate a bit of history or fact into our videos as well as use regular and drone Footage.</summary>
</plugin>
UCpoTXOogFTivQw1aG5W1mTQ

<plugin>
  <title>Si-finds</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCpoTXOogFTivQw1aG5W1mTQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAwalls0nqz9jycPVxIUDFtGO8CL_F9bzxgaIw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Alright Mudlovers! Get close-up and personal with me - a REAL Thames Mudlark. My full permit allows me to search restricted areas on the Thames foreshore that others can't. I aim to meet all kind of mudlarkers at different parts of the Thames to team up, gain knowledge and to find and share with you the awesome artefacts lost over the last 2,000 years in our sacred Father Thames. 
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>nicola white mudlark - Tideline Art</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC2K7yEwPIcPaQT5FM78dpyw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAz3xlewjpw37ND8h2nkB16haU-ClCd2drOjew=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Mudlarking along the River Thames, London. The River Thames is one of the largest archaeological sites in the world when the tide is out! It has also been used as a rubbish receptacle since London began, by the many civilisations that have lived along its banks.  Mudlarking is a term which has been around since the 16th century, and was originally the word used to describe the poorest of the poor, often young children and old women, who searched the Thames mud for any little bits and pieces that they could sell to make a bob or two. Richer people often used to throw coins down into the Thames mud from the bridges and watch with glee whilst the poor mudlarks scrabbled around for coins. I have been mudlarking in London for almost 15 years now and have a Port of London authority permit. See the Port of London Authority website for details. This youtube channel follows my Thames adventures and the delightful pieces of history, both new and old, that I find in the wonderful River Thames.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
<title>Adventures In Dirt</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCHqWBzqE7eFx_CY0R1kHd3w/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAzHkKU8X1z6VDIFn-VosQ-9tHxjrQ_W6iqBxQ=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>Adventures In Dirt with a metal detector - This is a channel dedicated to chronicling all my adventures in dirt and uncovering lost history.  I love to be outdoors and enjoy the hobby of metal detecting and gold prospecting.  Exploring the area around me and learning about the history of my surrounding communities teaches me about what was.... and with a little luck, maybe I can find what was left behind.  

I am a recreational treasure hunter, gold prospector, metal detectorist, and fan of history.  If you are interested in any of these, please subscribe, I am sure we will get along just fine.  ~DK

Follow this URL for a current list of DK's metal detecting gear:   
https://kit.com/adventuresindirt/metal-detecting-kit</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
<title>Digging Canuck</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCC_qT3rthSW6VEiwQrf2uqA/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAzVjUphihd0jITlPJlRHLQEySpOReS_WwzNng=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>Metal detecting, lots of fun and SNACKS!   

⏩ Videos: Tuesday

🔴 Live Stream:  OFF THE CUFF (Thursday 7:30pm eastern)
🔴 Live Stream:  COFFEE WITH LIZ (Sunday 10:00am eastern)

🚨 Retired LEO.

🍩 If you'd like to join me on a dig, feel free to send me an email.  I'll buy the coffee and donuts ;-)

📮 Send your letters, cards etc to:

PO Box 10024 Meadowlands
Ancaster, ON L9K-1P2
Canada</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
<title>stealth diggers</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCQYXpNBRRAfOfZpd6tAFVtw/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAyktWhGbaCGNWNt4eBgAAOuy7QjOqC3WY-q4w=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>Stealth Diggers metal detecting relic hunting & Not Thursday VLOG 
Stealth Diggers means we leave a location we are digging clean and looking like you were never there IT DOES NOT MEAN BREAK THE LAW. We detect & preserve for the love of local history.Thanks so much for watching.
check out our website www.notthursday.com

https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&hosted_button_id=CU3KVG4UJ8CHE
Stealth Diggers T shirts & gear.
http://stores.ebay.com/ThirdLifeMerchandise/Stealth-Diggers.html

Stealth Diggers Amazon page
https://www.amazon.com/shop/stealthdiggers

If you would like to be a patron of SD & help it grow check out this membership based service.
www.patreon.com/stealthdiggers
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
<title>adveNZures</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC8a6TgmL1M1ncPnm1jZ_QSA/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAyCchPH-qNTNiAkFlQxjfP4YFVmLNDFR_zRWg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>Come and join my adventures with metal detecting, freshwater fishing, relic hunting, and magnet fishing. 

Welcome to adveNZures
Let's Make This An Adventure </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
<title>Dillon Finds</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCXzNMvs0bBJYZiHYL663svA/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAyDjz5fXkmedTGUYAWYeRfGKAUvhCTPIp6I0Q=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>I'm a 14 year old enjoying my life just metal detecting...subscribe for videos ahead!</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
<title>iDigStuff Adventures</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCFnzwcDm6c-yajSm8JC38iw/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAxonQjFUpgQ9mwWBiZc6BXkJqY9ouW7IsJDWw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>Join me as I go to amazing locations that have historic value, or simply ones that will make you say: woah! I also do metal detecting in places ranging from parks to historic WW2 fields and Roman settlements.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
<title>Diggin' with Seven</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCCA5FzK74x-6gJlBRoL0jqw/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAyRV_EocRyCXDnsAZNN3lwCQkh3ZDWcVcJlxA=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>Send all messages to digginwithseven@gmail.com

Also check out our podcast at spreaker.com/digginwithseven

Mail correspondence can be sent to:
Diggin' with Seven
PO Box 81
Tompkinsville, KY 42167

Metal Detecting. Diggin' with Seven is based in southern Kentucky. My passions are Civil War relics and Colonial house sites, but I will engage in all kinds of detecting throughout the year. I do what I do to bring history to life and hopefully entertain the viewer. If you love old history, tune in to Diggin' with Seven each week as I upload a new video every Tuesday. Don't forget to like, subscribe, and share our YouTube channel.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
<title>J Three B Digg'n Canada</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCwWa4Cay9Ej48TOF8PvLV8A/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAwZ9iIfRGMkEYlnKuWLlnTCBDD9BHVacsJ44Q=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>Bringing you Canadian Metal Detecting at it's best!
I Recover and preserve lost history while Metal Detecting, river searching and exploring right here in Canada.
I find treasure such as silver & gold, Fur Trade artifacts and much more Just like Aquachigger, Nuggetnoggin, Quarter Hoarder, The Silverslingers and others!

Check out my videos here on youtube, facebook & Twitter to see what we find like coins, gold, silver, jewelry, relics from history and more!

https://www.facebook.com/jthreebdiggincanada
https://twitter.com/jthreeb

E-Mail: jthreeb@yahoo.ca</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
<title>Chocolate Cherry Coins</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCKr-a3H_d8OJOj61FipBl5Q/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAzkfktQtqdArLxmxdb_wPEjRLwFIMnEnh1SLg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>I have been collecting coins ever sense I was 10 years old. It started with my Grandfather giving me silver dollars. Then my Grandmother giving me Chinese coins. Myself looking through my change, looking through rolls, picking up finds at auctions, flea markets, garage sales, coin shows, coin shops and on line. I also collect silver rounds. 
 This Spring 2018 I started Metal Detecting. It is a hobby that quickly became addicting and so much fun. I like to Metal Detect the beach, the woods and all kinds of parks.
 I enjoy watching others show their coin collections and learn from their knowledge. I also enjoy watching others Metal Detect and learn from their years of experience. 
 I want to thank anyone who stops by my page and watches my videos. I appreciate everyone of yous ! 
 Hope you have a wonderful day :-)

DONATE:
paypal.me/SilverLakecm

If you ever wish to send me anything or contact me by mail
My Address is:

Chocolate Cherry Coins
1045 10th Street PMB 140
Menominee, MI 49858</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Chill Bill</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCVWsO7_BMNwrVoJRJEcyUhA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAx8pg2TulKGCwfzatp0rbxIEgNQvfpZe9y1jg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Treasure hunting videos. From Mudlarking (Mud larking) river treasure in the Thames, to searching shipwreck coins from pirate galleons, to Templar artifacts unearthed metal detecting. Finding treasure is here. coins, jewelry, gems and even flint tools.
Still looking to find that gold hoard, I use metal detectors like the Deus XP, Minelab Excalibur, Garrett AT Pro and CTX3030, for land, beach, sea and river treasure.
Join Chill Bill metal detecting.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Lucy's Larking Adventures</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCaFO9uJ36Tv5BOMvUqKL3CQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAwSb0AlSzC8j_2k2jMHxQfMccshe6r4evcLog=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi welcome to Lucy's Larking Adventures! On my channel, I'll be sharing my hobbies with you, mostly consisting of larking at some lovely locations in the South West of England. I love digging around for old bits of forgotten history, and the joy of finding something old. My favourite things to discover while mud- or water larking are old pottery pieces and bottles. I also enjoy discovering and exploring abandoned places to get a glimpse of times gone by! Hope you enjoy watching my videos!</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Aquachigger </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCv61IAZLDELwk2Kk5hfX0mg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAzUiv-U6kn1B0l1QRRFOOK4F0HGBUwqYBRLaw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Metal detecting, treasure, history, coins, river treasure, adventure, nature, animals and MOAR! That is what my channel is about. I enjoy caving, SCUBA diving and flying my powered paraglider. I foster sick and injured pets. My channel is family friendly. My videos are meant to be fun, educational and informative.  Snail Mail: Beau Ouimette PO Box 543 Williamsport Md. 21795 

Affiliate links to see and purchase the gear I use:
Metal Detectors and MOAR:  https://goo.gl/jmpNNn
Wetsuits and water gear: https://goo.gl/j1Xxay
Flashlights: goo.gl/FFjJKe
Garrett Metal Detectors: https://goo.gl/nbzDYH

Don't forget to check out my Patreon page if you wish to become more involved with my channel. 
http://bit.do/chiggspatreon

PLEASE SUBSCRIBE IF YOU LIKE MY VIDEOS! THANKS....</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Deep Digger Dan</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCs5IxVpqCYv7xiPsclF8mFA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAzjzPhWg8rwxRwMvxk8neQYmOFczoEgXL8yJQ=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>A collection of all my metal detecting videos, advice, disasters, dilemmas and dreams.</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
<title>Historical Magpie</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCwIpFFjwmR4BEPbf7oV4F5A/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mDYiNshpqD07UA50KRJCZKYFLZ9R-ngu9TfzQ=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>I started metal detecting in January 2017 and  still have lots to learn. I hope you enjoy my videos! There will also be uploaded drone videos plus holidays away as well as a few random videos. I hope you enjoy my channel and  if you do - please give the videos a thumbs up!  If possible - please subscribe. A YouTube channel is nothing with out people viewing the content, so thank you for your support 👍🇬🇧
Steve (historical magpie) you the subscribers make the channel i just create the video's</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
<title>Addictedtobleeps</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCjlEYE57maiv4T_6uvzrVCQ/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mDfQ8ToHShTg4Vl2WCzF8jb6QkeuVa3quMXIw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>Metal detecting in South East England. Advice to beginners through my own experience. Stories of my finds, and sometimes humorous experiences as a metal detector in these parts!  Tips on getting fields, using equipment and much more also featured here!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
<title>EnglandsHistory</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCDaILf7E0y67tL1vlhvP0rA/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mAiESw-JLoddeVcLa-zU_W0DZlaJNgn7Hfngg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>Welcome to my Youtube channel Englandshistory.

On my channel you will get fun and giggles plus product reviews, rally reports and every day detecting adventures. 
I travel all over the UK looking for lost history that was dropped or buried many years ago.
The main part about the hobby is finding items but i get so much joy from the banter that we all have with like minded detectorists.
Don't forget to subscribe to follow me on my adventure it's going to be fun.

Above on my banner you will see my social media icons, if you fancy a chat about the hobby don't hesitate to message me.

You can support the channel here, paypal.me/tectingsidWelcome to my Youtube channel Englandshistory.

On my channel you will get fun and giggles plus product reviews, rally reports and every day detecting adventures. 
I travel all over the UK looking for lost history that was dropped or buried many years ago.
The main part about the hobby is finding items but i get so much joy from the banter that we all have with like minded detectorists.
Don't forget to subscribe to follow me on my adventure it's going to be fun.

Above on my banner you will see my social media icons, if you fancy a chat about the hobby don't hesitate to message me.

You can support the channel here, paypal.me/tectingsid</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
<title>Hadesdetecting</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC_9f7Zhfxna8vWyqbHIGr9Q/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mAsHk63N5E75lbribui7H-sUuRbWTfLeRH5aA=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>An insight into my Hobby for the last 5 years detecting fields,beaches and any intersting land i can find.Hopefully discovering some hidden items along the way

Check out my facebook page for photos,upcoming outing and unseen bits that didnt make it to a video
https://www.facebook.com/hadesdetecting/
</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
<title>Relics n Roots</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCfCjlVUTTEuTpLi0KZPDIuA/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mB765FLTFj2PKPcyXUBSr64nXpgSnn8kEz-WA=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>My Name is Nick
Welcome to my Channel
Please SUBSCRIBE! 
Metal Detecting
GL&HH Everyone</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
<title>The Giant Garrett Detectorist</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCPDHKe4n60CeFJKCRPTP_9g/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mAzWThNtrYSbX4nRqNJoCrbiIem1lpAGRRF7g=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>I'm starting this channel to show how a bad detectorist can still go out and enjoy themselves 😁😁😁😁😁

Contact me on monkeyflump@gmail.com  

All the best and take care</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
<title>Thors Treasure</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCVFqjoXsP5KHqKteTp64ziQ/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mC6dt_wGmED1yfmlyZkGNQITJccWH_fr2dKqg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary>Join me on the hunt for Treasure in Scotland Metal Detecting And Gold Prospecting where ever I get permission saving history 1 thing at a time We are Time Travellers. Sometimes it's not the find itself but the history behind it 


Metal Detector :Tesoro Cortes 


Facebook Thors Treasure
Or send me a pm on here 😀
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
<title>DIGGER 1</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCOP3Er8usgjV5yIIdcudX0w/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mD_dtgSb-tlObdAZNCkNxFxASgRnBBBbUPCeA=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
<summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Defunctland </title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCVo63lbKHjC04KqYhwSZ_Pg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AAuE7mAwH1loC-naCjfZOlaVVMfFWWavhvMMGiBtOQ=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello and welcome to Defunctland! Defunctland is a YouTube series discussing the history of extinct theme park and themed entertainment experiences. We also have a podcast, VR project, spin-off, and a whole bunch of fun stuff! Welcome to the channel!</summary>
</plugin>
