
<plugin>
<title>nuggetnoggin</title>
<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCm_Fbx0tAqAOB3cA4d1GnXw/</link>
<thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-82a1Gy6FdWs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/j-gDjb5FEe8/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
<summary>I'm Michael, I have been metal detecting for 8 years now. I really enjoy discovering the past! Come along with me and feel the excitement of treasure hunting.

If you are interested in purchasing a Metal Detector please visit my store at https://www.battleground-detectors.com

God bless!</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Broken Window Theory</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCQjlzE-BSD1PDW988vbqVjw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAy-Lq57hbH3vbcKgZfERzfzSL4O8ldEXF_ovg=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Abandoned buildings, haunted locations, rotten or lost places - however you call it - we urbex it. Urban Exploration is a passion we pursue for some years now. We - that are Till and Marco, two students from Germany. Our goal is to consistently produce high quality and unique videos about these special places - about Urban Exploring. 

See you in the comments or on our social media channels. Or maybe at the next abandoned place? ;)</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Exploring the Unbeaten Path</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC73dVtWf9mpjiWYkXyIlm7A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-rUShiHKDPpA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Fd1kmEJgaOs/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>For 11 years we visit the coolest abandoned buildings in Europe, Asia, Africa and the US and experience crazy adventures.
    After the TV series "Exitus" (Which was broadcasted in Belgium and The Netherlands in 2016) we decided to make our own channel
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Abandoned or Cool</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCbVIfFGdSc4BJFL0qdglHiQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAyrLJcUrm39zoadjEna_Kh6ChAPkslAac5ghw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Join as as we travel the United States exploring abandoned or cool places. We try to incorporate a bit of history or fact into our videos as well as use regular and drone Footage.</summary>
</plugin>
UCpoTXOogFTivQw1aG5W1mTQ

<plugin>
  <title>Si-finds</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCpoTXOogFTivQw1aG5W1mTQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAwalls0nqz9jycPVxIUDFtGO8CL_F9bzxgaIw=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Alright Mudlovers! Get close-up and personal with me - a REAL Thames Mudlark. My full permit allows me to search restricted areas on the Thames foreshore that others can't. I aim to meet all kind of mudlarkers at different parts of the Thames to team up, gain knowledge and to find and share with you the awesome artefacts lost over the last 2,000 years in our sacred Father Thames. 
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>nicola white mudlark - Tideline Art</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC2K7yEwPIcPaQT5FM78dpyw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/a-/AN66SAz3xlewjpw37ND8h2nkB16haU-ClCd2drOjew=s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no</thumbnail>
  <summary>Mudlarking along the River Thames, London. The River Thames is one of the largest archaeological sites in the world when the tide is out! It has also been used as a rubbish receptacle since London began, by the many civilisations that have lived along its banks.  Mudlarking is a term which has been around since the 16th century, and was originally the word used to describe the poorest of the poor, often young children and old women, who searched the Thames mud for any little bits and pieces that they could sell to make a bob or two. Richer people often used to throw coins down into the Thames mud from the bridges and watch with glee whilst the poor mudlarks scrabbled around for coins. I have been mudlarking in London for almost 15 years now and have a Port of London authority permit. See the Port of London Authority website for details. This youtube channel follows my Thames adventures and the delightful pieces of history, both new and old, that I find in the wonderful River Thames.
</summary>
</plugin>
