##########################################################################################
<cache>10800</cache>
<fanart>https://wallpaperscraft.com/image/youtube_logo_information_portal_48619_1280x720.jpg</fanart>
##########################################################################################



<plugin>
  <title>Kays Seriously Bad Cooking</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCeKWgImK1RAD9IGjWZqxmIw/</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>LadBaby Official</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCVBXTHC8cAKUHyK3LytUzHA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-jBcoebuoa2A/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/pA24PoNrxfE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello and welcome to the OFFICIAL LadBaby YouTube channel!

    Follow mine and the missus journey into responsible parenthood as I try (and normally fail) to transition from 'Lad to Dad'.

    Home of the Zim Zimmer baby walker, Toolbox Lunchbox, Skip Pool Party AND a heap load of me winding up the missus.

    Ill educated, sometimes humorous, poorly spelt, casually inappropriate and HONEST approach to first time fatherhood. The road to responsible parenting is never easy…especially when you haven’t got a clue what you’re doing!

    Ohh...and don't forget to Subscribe for all the latest videos!
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>My Virgin Kitchen</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCAzyupPG4vdo8jd9nJ13LAw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-EEXzm10q6dc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/MeyIBA01MMs/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>A fun food cooking channel. If you are looking for easy how to recipe tutorials mixed with food fun & easy to follow homemade cooking you may have come to the right place! I’m a self-taught cook here on YouTube inspiring you to learn how to cook with me. Recipes on my own, cooking with kids or other friends and family it’s all about trying to get you cooking easy recipes, laughing and learning and hopefully picking up some new cooking ideas.
    There’s also a dose of food fun too, so if you like giant food videos or mini food videos, taste tests, or testing the latest kitchen gadgets you’ll probably like it here!
    I used to be a Virgin in the kitchen (hence the name) and absolutely hated cooking or attempting to make any recipes no matter how simple!
    I am completely self-taught in the hope that I can inspire you guys to attempt the recipes too and get in the kitchen - cooking is all about confidence! I hope you enjoy my mix of fun food recipe videos , subscribe for regular videos
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>The Barrys</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCd0h13f33ouSAKxMQfabL6A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-tsUMFk-pzMI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/cizaKqS-DBc/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to 'The Barry's' a spin-off channel from MyVirginKitchen. This is our channel for lots of behind the scenes videos, family vlogs and whatever we fancy really.
We are a family living in the South West England in a little seaside town in Somerset called Weston Super Mare with our pugs Amy & Boston. We hope you enjoy the content here on the channel we will try to put up a new video every week when possible, but you can always catch us on the MyVirginKitchen channel.
Be sure to follow us on our personal social media accounts if you enjoy our videos as we have lots of even more behind the scenes stuff going on there.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Barshens</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCDYytfm5PZin4N0hT_nLxDQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-HWw1iJ_n1q8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Z8ZZnZ0Zhh4/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>A weekly 'entertainment' show (used in the loosest of words) with new videos every Friday, hosted by Stuart Ashen (Ashens) & Barry Lewis (MyVirginKitchen). A tongue in cheek entertainment show with elements of nostalgia, taste testing, and well, anything you want really! 
Remember to subscribe and follow us on other social media platforms for behind the scenes bits and bobs and enjoy the ride. 
We also do a Barshens Podcast:
Search: "Barshens" on iTunes / Stitcher or other podcast app
RSS feed (manually add podcast to your listening app) is:
http://feeds.soundcloud.com/users/soundcloud:users:220933321/sounds.rss
Soundcloud link https://soundcloud.com/barshens
If you listen & like the podcast please like, rate, subscribe & review us on iTunes etc to help push up the list 

We hope you have as much fun watching as we do making these videos.
A weekly 'entertainment' show (used in the loosest of words) with new videos every Friday, hosted by Stuart Ashen (Ashens) & Barry Lewis (MyVirginKitchen). A tongue in cheek entertainment show with elements of nostalgia, taste testing, and well, anything you want really! 
Remember to subscribe and follow us on other social media platforms for behind the scenes bits and bobs and enjoy the ride. 
We also do a Barshens Podcast:
Search: "Barshens" on iTunes / Stitcher or other podcast app
RSS feed (manually add podcast to your listening app) is:
http://feeds.soundcloud.com/users/soundcloud:users:220933321/sounds.rss
Soundcloud link https://soundcloud.com/barshens
If you listen & like the podcast please like, rate, subscribe & review us on iTunes etc to help push up the list 

We hope you have as much fun watching as we do making these videos.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>ThreadBanger</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCBMxQPhfM6nkhQ8vPfQhkCg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-jtztztnSuUQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/DN7E4vwCoLU/s176-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Threadbanger...Not Yo Mama's DIY Channel
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Jack</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCYzPXprvl5Y-Sf0g4vX-m6g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-6KbRToTL_9o/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/byNnz42pdGk/s176-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Top of the mornin’ to ya, laddies! Welcome to my channel, my name is jacksepticeye.  I am the most consistently energetic videogame commentator on youtube.  If you like daily videos on videogames, for example happy wheels, undertale, gta, and more you have come to the right place!
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Daz</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCDBCCMlFD-hArPbWv38FINA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-oT5iMr0pMFs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/i2yhGmJFq2g/s176-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to the official channel of Daz Games! Here you’ll find all my Try Not To Laugh Challenge, Sketch and Reaction videos where you’ll enjoy my responses to videos from Jacob Sartorius, Musical.ly and everything else on the internet you hold so dearly. I like to do commentary walkthroughs and playthroughs of games like Sims, Uncharted 4, GTA V, Minecraft and many other games. New gaming videos will be posted five to six times a week. Be sure to Subscribe to never miss one!
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>The DickeyDines Show</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCxuvDkUxwEERVG9OZkxBtaA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-LjAU0UZLPTA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/1_YJAlckEzI/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Jared Dines and Austin Dickey

Comedy/Games/Skits - Good hangs

New videos every week!!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Jared Dines</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCJcYRr8rpsxVPfWA5vkuxFw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-qcTDzeJeihg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/TyoUzkFZ3kw/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Comedy/Music/Vlogs. Vocalist/Guitarist/Drummer. All things Metal/Metalcore.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Facts.</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCmEnDJfwzlfVZyDdIznoiww/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-E-_-hLZgZBo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/FW6dzzYnYg8/s176-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>We create 5 new videos every week featuring Irish people trying out new foods or watching tv shows / YouTubers that they have never tried or watched before.
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Alonzo Lerone</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCqTk2nsJ9K_PRaDFG0rY4XA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-WY8LRnu6Zgk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/KVQ06C-mLjw/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to the official YouTube channel of comedian/entertainer Alonzo Lerone. Looking for comedy, or just a good laugh? You’re in luck! On this channel, you’ll find a variety of fail compilations showcasing the internet’s funniest and dumbest fails curated by Alonzo Lerone from Twitter, Facebook, advertisements, and much more.
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Colin Geddis</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCV0ZVuhtv5GUbybSIayMB9Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-cK4EiWGjOM0/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/foKiVbKagLI/s176-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>This is the official GEDZILLA Films youtube channel. All videos on this channel have been created by Colin Geddis, a Northern Irish stand-up comedian and film-maker. This channel contains N.I. online comedy hits such as I AM FIGHTER, The Scene with Besty McD, 50 shades of Gay, Never Ever Drink and Drive and Audio Picnic video podcasts. Follow Colin on twitter: @COLINGEDDIS or check out his website www.colingeddis.com for stand-up comedy gig dates and official Gedzilla Films merchandise. Enjoy.
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>SlingShot Guy</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCVZlxkKqlvVqzRJXhAGq42Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-UqaQNlKVr5c/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/gZATtMD9V1A/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>This channel is all about launchers.

    Most of them are powered by rubber, a fascinating material that converts muscle energy into kinetic energy! But we also present bladed weapons and launchers powered by other energy sources.

    Inventions, reviews, stunts and destruction - if that is what you want, you came to the right place for sure!
  </summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Antonella</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCcEnSe6MTOpGIy96ZVi2WHA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Dqoo6XGJG-g/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/hC4iD1s82Q4/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi this is my channel of uncensored reviews of all sorts. Please be warned I may use a few choice words not for the faint hearted and not to be listened to around children. I review stuff and say it how it is. Happy watching. I hope you enjoy. Please subscribe if you like my reviews.
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Carpool Karaoke</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/playlist/PLZ1f3amS4y1ffYEhGZDtawaEyRQQu69Bw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-NhxJe9XKyV8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/XkSb5PFaHP8/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Bunny</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCGwPbAQdGA3_88WBuGtg9tw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ExFhgTMOP2A/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/SZrc2tlLKJs/s176-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Bunny2 Banana Peppers</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCSvzb90XLo2f-j7sfwQsrYA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-yoYfOvYOX_8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/VaxjyVicc_E/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Pinkstylist</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCAAszizDDdScfqclAybLiEA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-vb4KZWrYqIk/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/JVOqQAwFGmw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>On my channel I mainly do Special Effects/Theatrical Makeup Tutorials mostly based off requests from my viewers :)
    No matter how crazy the look ;D The bigger the better! :D

    I also do prank videos and videos to help brighten your day and help make you smile :D
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>How To Minecraft</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCmbnlwXAdGYACzvStDjquaA/playlists/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-V_DH2XKmnOI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/meZT27EC9DA/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I'm Vikkstar and this is where I post series on games I enjoy!
  </summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Tom Fletcher</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCLsgDgYTlIDN3cCLSMpooNQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/--isawJXPEbY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/5i7QOkiI-ek/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Mediocre guitarist in Mcfly. Generally lame, occasionally awesome. Owner of multiple cats.
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Giovanna Fletcher</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCxq-KSr68wJaXiVJW848e6A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-kEArpEojlhM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/NbC9jwPcw6I/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello! My name is Giovanna, known to many simply as Gi. My aim across all my social is to create a fun and positive little place on the Internet for people to come and feel uplifted. I document my life as an author, presenter, blogger and columnist, but most importantly my roles as wife to Tom and mum to Buzz and Buddy.

    Mondays are MUMDAYS, with a new video posted at 9AM each week. Fridays are home to our DEAR CARRIE series, essentially video diaries to my sister in law who we never get to see. Tom adds his thoughts from his channel on Sundays with Carrie replying with her DEAR TOM&GI video on Wednesdays.
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>10 Second Songs</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCm6r_b2K5jn1JGkwDcwJXrQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-zjoyPfKx3sg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/SG37-KoA4QI/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>My name is Anthony Vincent and I'm the voice of Ten Second Songs, custom songs made in ANY style. WWW.TENSECONDSONGS.COM.  Make sure to subscribe to my channel to see/hear some more awesome music from me!
  </summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>H.J. Freaks</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCeyS2RhY-7Rtb4KFLRyZhMg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-afeVJxY7SIU/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/MMockl54rMw/s176-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>H.J.Freaks, THE RATED-R Super-Stupid Bassist!
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Vet Ranch</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCXSCm3S2XZHLBz8kH0N5Heg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-1r1BMTocC8U/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/dQaX2f4zxJs/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>A place for veterinarians to share some amazing stories
  </summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Exploring the Unbeaten Path</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC73dVtWf9mpjiWYkXyIlm7A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-rUShiHKDPpA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Fd1kmEJgaOs/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>For 11 years we visit the coolest abandoned buildings in Europe, Asia, Africa and the US and experience crazy adventures.
    After the TV series "Exitus" (Which was broadcasted in Belgium and The Netherlands in 2016) we decided to make our own channel
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Goodwood Road & Racing</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC8rador8CU-pTJ6p7WNiv6w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-zMHS-SqcCLY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/_8Vbx9I-v20/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to Goodwood Road & Racing; the ultimate pit stop for racing day action, motor sport festivals, car and bike news and reviews, road tests, corporate race days and more!
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Jay Leno's Garage</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCQMELFlXQL38KPm8kM-4Adg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-FyLHrCVfntI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/4C9MwGbvp0E/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>A new video every Sunday! Visit Jay Leno's Garage, the Emmy-winning series where Jay Leno gives car reviews, motorcycle reviews, compares cars, and shares his passion and expertise on anything that rolls, explodes, and makes noise. Classic cars, restomods, super cars like the McLaren P1, sports cars like Porsche 918 Spyder and Camaro Z28, cafe racers, vintage cars, and much, much more.
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>All 4</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCiZ47iCEOmqsyZU_6XP9ekg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-35jewTP4NZI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6yqr7WfSVn0/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>The home of original short documentaries showcasing youthful culture, from fashion to video games, music to body art, digital culture to dating and sex.
    New releases every week
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Fail Army</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCPDis9pjXuqyI7RYLJ-TTSA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-_8lHSPO3nNI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/-THVRONaQco/s176-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>FailArmy is the world’s number one source for epic fail videos and hilarious compilations. We’re powered by fan submissions and feedback from all around the world, with over 30 million fans across digital platforms.
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Fail Army Crashes</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCoiSFyUELlmpYGzkbXyhsPw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-KpeVnoa_nO4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/AGwLt_UeVrE/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to FailArmy Crashes Channel! On this channel you can watch car crashes videos, car crash compilations!
    Be safe on the roads!
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>boogie2988</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC4_bwov47DseacR1-ttTdOg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-StjNof_9ek4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/2asNIh5sKLc/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hello!  I am youtuber Boogie2988.  You might know me as Boogie, or as one of my characters... Most notably the raging gamer Francis.  I make vlogs, comedy sketches, video game related news and articles, rage videos, parodies, game play videos, and other gaming videos as well!

    So if you're a gamer looking for gaming videos, gaming news, or gameplay you're in the right place.  If you like watching a fat funny guy named francis destroy gaming consoles and going  on rants and rages then this is the right place for that too!

    I also make serious videos and vlogs about life topics that give advice on a variety of things to help you live a slightly better life and learn from my mistakes about weight loss, or succeeding on youtube, and more!
  </summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>ElectroBOOM</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCJ0-OtVpF0wOKEqT2Z1HEtA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-iXZgN0vGYlE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/6yamX7m-CMo/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Find the craziness in engineering from me, Mehdi Sadaghdar, but don't try them at home...
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Afrotechmods</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCosnWgi3eorc1klEQ8pIgJQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Z5BCK-CRpnw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/yzOKIagS8G0/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Straight to the point electronics tutorial videos with practical examples taught by a professional electronics engineer.
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Blender Guru</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCOKHwx1VCdgnxwbjyb9Iu1g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-KDc5u8wSA8c/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/FWj0Rn77GZI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Blender tutorials and general artist advice
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Epic Videos</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCb2vqOqQBEvTbHxNlT66AbA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-NhIVmjbFuKQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/BvJTNn-VVkE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Top videos. Fail, Win, Viral, Cute, Fun, Hard and Epic.
    Original videos
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Epic Laughs</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCPAt6mvC-wKunwKyiEeAxFQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-2pyb7lUoCNA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/yPBkBKgc6rU/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Funny videos, epic laughs. We collect the best fails, funny pets and hilarious moments to give you a good laugh. Sit back and enjoy!
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Funny Pets</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCeZe0VwwhEf8KTI2FHfJtTg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-GnKaM5fK234/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Vh1ttLwTDXQ/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Funny Dog Videos. Funny Cat Videos. Funny Pet Videos! Funny Pets is bringing you the best funny pet videos that we can find. Please subscribe and we will make you laugh!
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>The Pet Collective</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCPIvT-zcQl2H0vabdXJGcpg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-8gepiMGDAss/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/ORw6_GSQhuM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Submit your pet videos here! http://submit.thepetcollective.tv/

    The Pet Collective is home to the top trending clips, most entertaining memes, and funniest animal videos online.  Simply put, we think animals are the best ever. If you agree, let’s make it YouTube official right here, right meow: Subscribe here - http://tpc.tv/1Qd1gdP

    We welcome your video submissions for use on our channel! Submit your fun pet videos here: http://bit.ly/32-submit-here
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>CryptTV</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCpJ6Dn01AqjvFVN2EiK72Ag/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-OW3BbnpzeBI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/EWgZJCexfoU/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Get the best in HORROR from Crypt TV. New scary films added every:
    TUESDAY at 1pm.
    THURSDAY  at 1pm.
    FRIDAY at 1pm.

    We love scary stories, we believe scary stories unite us and the best ones make us a little more connected to each other. Crypt TV collaborates with storytellers around the world to bring the next generation of monsters stories to life -- for you, for free, everyday. Follow us @CryptTV everywhere and find your #MonsterWithin

    Three new short films a week with deep dive into horror every MONDAY with FRIGHT HYPE.
  </summary>
</plugin>




<plugin>
  <title>steveo</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCt54Hzhj7RpCWOYpoFJLKAQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-GVgtFV4NTt4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Y6sO6OqQfAQ/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>I'm Steve-O, the guy from Jackass and Wildboyz. I'm known for stapling my balls to my leg, putting huge jellyfish on my head, and plenty of other crazy, funny stuff. Since the last Jackass movie, I've never stopped doing crazy stuff, and this is the place to see all of it. Nothing sucks on my channel. If you enjoy trick shots, you'll love how I incorporate hot chicks with huge, glorious boobs into them with my Titty Trick Shots videos. If you love skateboarding, comedy, and funny, dangerous stunts like The Stunt That Broke My Legs and My Biggest Jump Ever, then my How To Get Famous and Venomous Spider Stunt videos will rock your world! My pranks are just as wild, too, check out my Golden Shower Prank! I'm about to post my favorite stunt video of the year, it's called Jumping Off A Bridge From A Moving Trampoline, don't miss it! Subscribe for new videos, and check out my whole channel! Thanks so much! - STEVE-O
  </summary>
</plugin>
<plugin>
  <title>Topless Baker</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCOvPpNDsz_ePFOTKhmDaDnQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-EveMnTEQKk8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Hbkj2wFSP_k/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Topless Baker is all about making cooking more approachable and making those recipes that seem daunting, really easy! Food brings everyone together, so these videos aim to make your life easy in the kitchen, while impressing everyone around you.

Every week I'll be uploading a brand new video, showing you how to make the food that I love to eat so that it can go straight from my kitchen to yours!

</summary>
</plugin>




<plugin>
  <title>The 'Wee' Podcast</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCd4RsuTJQiKnCs4W4Rj-I-g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-M8-TaY-cZpo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/QXoxoXhlf2M/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Weekly Podcast hosted by Phil and Clarky. Sitting, thinking, talking, tea. Join us! #TheWeePodcast
  </summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>TheBackyardScientist</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC06E4Y_-ybJgBUMtXx8uNNw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-IZZnLTRrXGY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/VGWto8NZJQY/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Aloha YouTubers, I am The Backyard Scientist!

I like to make videos on all the crazy stuff I do. From exploding arrows, to making instruments, molten aluminum to science/chemistry experiments - I do it so you don't have to! I'm always thinking of more stuff to do, if you have an idea, id love to hear it!

Almost everything I do can be considered dangerous!!  If you insist on trying my videos at home, just remember- if you play with fire, you're going to get burned. Electricity is deadly. Be safe guys :)

</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>R0C1NANT3</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCipM1n60kIYu-Obuz49H30g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-ZT1N9FUwC4Q/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Hr2xZOLHVcE/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Supporting content for advdogs.com - a site dedicated to going on adventures with your dog in a safe and courteous manner.
  </summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>SpaceX</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCtI0Hodo5o5dUb67FeUjDeA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-iCfXaGf-xjE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/8qxokSVUHME/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>CoolHardLogic</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCx3s3t5kpD4VMfJjDi5keXw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/--JwefITEWzw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/j7o_TqnCXxg/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Putting silly beliefs and nonsense to the test for education and amusement. </summary>
</plugin>
