##########################################################################################
<cache>10800</cache>
<content>set</content>
##########################################################################################

<dir>
	<title>300 Collection (2006-2014)</title>
	<tmdb>collection/125570</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iVzIeC3PbG9BtDAudpwSNdKAgh6.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nKQqh6kJvPdpOJD24enD3Bm1Hy5.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>Alien  Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/8091</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iVzIeC3PbG9BtDAudpwSNdKAgh6.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/52Lhwd7srnktMFDYkfhtMoZdabT.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>A science fiction horror film franchise, focusing on Lieutenant Ellen Ripley (Sigourney Weaver) and her battle with an extraterrestrial life-form, commonly referred to as "the Alien". Produced by 20th Century Fox, the series started with the 1979 film Alien, then Aliens in 1986, Alien³ in 1992, and Alien: Resurrection in 1997.
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Back To The Future Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/264</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/UV8VEgAxgKVnCVnZhFACmhxjE4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c9C9Pg2QctyjZHRmS0P8rZg1OTA.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>The family friendly action packed, sci-fi Back to the Future movie collection.
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Bad Boys Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/14890</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tSVbihfvVTCbcm0zXKA7L8R6Y9v.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/k9hhSHg5GS4UgWQC6MHBOZrarji.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>2 Films about the cop duo nick named 'Bad Boys', blowing stuff up and crazy car chases. They get the job done but at an expensive cost.
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Batman Collection</title>
	<link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Johnstonevo/20ap/master/base/20AP/movies/batman.xml</link>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/adQxUvQW8HXNsvMG5aj71pHh9T.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9SpZvXLZDGGtFqVDByGqSGI64Kw.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary></summary>
</dir>


    <dir>
      <title>The Beatles</title>
      <trakt>https://api.trakt.tv/users/lockebcl/lists/the-beatles/items</trakt>
	  <fanart></fanart>
	  <content>set</content>
    </dir>



<dir>
	<title>Blade Runner Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/422837</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/de3nql7XipNOdLJhRNouPecxvmM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xiOw9kLNfFPoe3j3J6nHqDTT1fu.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>The Blade Runner movie Series Collection</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>The Boondock Saints Collection (1999-2009)</title>
	<tmdb>collection/87186</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/u4hp2I1DgWw2ZnkX2VTZDixGP87.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w700_and_h392_bestv2/kdxXEiS3sDB7pvQapiqiTRbwkKr.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>The Boondock Saints movie series.
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Bourne Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/31562</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lTfOZ25PhQkmGb5NHmaFnwB7b13.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vA5xMglyZv7yzDTj1qUTU4OvelV.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>Matt Damon is Jason Bourne, an elite government agent determined to outwit and outmaneuver anyone who stands in the way of his finding out the secrets of his mysterious past. Follow his explosive, action-packed adventures in five blockbuster films from one of the most popular series of all time: The Bourne Identity, The Bourne Supremacy, The Bourne Ultimatum, The Bourne Legacy and Jason Bourne.</summary>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Cocoon Collection (1985-1988)</title>
	<tmdb>collection/86307</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qKtNXCcY3DMJ8T7cs47yDwpU5fT.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/o32F4wuQJPBnP5FVkOGP9DxGYJI.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Cocoon is a 1985 American science fiction fantasy comedy-drama film directed by Ron Howard about a group of elderly people rejuvenated by aliens. The movie stars Don Ameche, Wilford Brimley, Hume Cronyn, Brian Dennehy, Jack Gilford, Steve Guttenberg, Maureen Stapleton, Jessica Tandy, Gwen Verdon, Herta Ware, Tahnee Welch, and Linda Harrison. The film is loosely based on the novel of the same name by David Saperstein. A sequel, Cocoon: The Return, was released in 1988 in which almost all of the original cast reprised their roles.
	</summary>
	<content>boxset</content>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Carry On Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/37261</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2P0HNrYgKDvirV8RCdT1rBSJdbJ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/38tF1LJN7ULeZAuAfP7beaPMfcl.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>Carry On... is a series of British comedy films, directed by Gerald Thomas and produced by Peter Rogers.</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>The Chronicles of Narnia</title>
	<tmdb>collection/420</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sh6Kn8VBfXotJ6qsvJkdfscxXKR.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vlv2skpXYg02TRg1iyXGvDvZSZ9.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>Modern theatrical film productions based on the series of books from the 1950’s book series 'The Chronicles of Narnia' by C.S. Lewis.</summary>
</dir>



<dir>
	<title>Cloverfield Collection (2008-2018)</title>
	<tmdb></tmdb>
	<summary></summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/as01o40tJ2FhtheqeXf7bVZ0EQO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart></fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>DC Extended Universe</title>
      <trakt>https://api.trakt.tv/users/tetharion/lists/worlds-of-dc/items</trakt>
	<thumbnail>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/wwcbm/images/b/bc/Dc_cinematic_universe-logo.png</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://res.cloudinary.com/culturemap-com/image/upload/q_auto/ar_4:3,c_fill,g_faces:center,w_1200/v1510845927/photos/265138_original.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>The DC Extended Universe (DCEU) is an unofficial term used to refer to an American media franchise and shared universe that is centered on a series of superhero films, distributed by Warner Bros. Pictures and based on characters that appear in American comic books by DC Comics. The shared universe, much like the original DC Universe in comic books and the television programs, was established by crossing over common plot elements, settings, cast, and characters. The films have been in production since 2011 and in that time Warner Bros. has distributed five films. The series has grossed over $3.7 billion at the global box office, currently making it the fourteenth highest-grossing film franchise.
  </summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Death Wish Collection (1974-1994)</title>
	<tmdb>collection/14377</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3IGNbJJXSeL427meXfAR7gpSwZW.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/m3K7AXN8Wi6VIRtVlpF1E6nzEn1.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Five films about Paul Kersey, an architect with no luck whatsoever. First His wife is murdered when their apartment is broken into, 8 years later his mentally ill daughter is raped and murdered. After all this Kersey is never the same and ends up taking on the drug lords and various criminals of the world.
	</summary>
	<content>boxset</content>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Die Hard Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/1570</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nglknikAiEbsF9CW5xV9fC378JH.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7LSSYjSt94Hs3YYDzMGLkAdGLoF.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>An action film series centered around the character of John McClane, a New York City police detective who finds himself fighting a group of terrorists in each film.</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Dirty Harry Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/10456</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nlpixhOhb3JmFqVXKjCwpYFpldf.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bS1ioomHh2emKAZ6vWn17UZnhDx.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>Dirty Harry is the name of a series of films and novels featuring fictional San Francisco Police Department Homicide Division Inspector "Dirty" Harry Callahan, portrayed by Clint Eastwood. Eastwood's character also helped popularize the .44 Magnum, as Harry Callahan is famously shown wielding his Smith & Wesson Model 29 revolver.</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>The Divergent Series Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/283579</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nXuCj7NcsC2bPJlwD6t2l9ZTDnt.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uExS9jcaFBM1wJhkn1Q1P0MFpv6.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>A series of dystopian science fiction action films based on the Divergent novels by the American author Veronica Roth.  in a dystopian and post-apocalyptic Chicago where people are divided into distinct factions based on human virtues. Beatrice Prior (Tris) is warned that she is Divergent and thus will never fit into any one of the factions. She along with Tobias Eaton (Four) soon learn that a sinister plot is brewing in the seemingly perfect society.</summary>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Escape From ... Collection (1981-1996)</title>
	<tmdb>collection/115838</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8Zih8QGPJNXUuws0fIZmjxjs2Su.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/u3tHIjkTj8C2gHOTFmzZgEXOQxp.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>A John Carpenter action film series following the main protagonist Snake Plissken, a former Special Forces operative turned criminal who is called upon to breach dangerous environments for search-and-rescue missions of the utmost priority.
	</summary>
	<content>boxset</content>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Expendables Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/126125</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ptF9rVkzoXVO1bnglLISgnJ7Ccr.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lA7oDSt6LkyDqtbFGbyuG0afmTI.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>An ensemble action film series about a group of elite mercenaries. The series pay tribute to the blockbuster action films of the 1980s and early 1990s, and stars an array of action veterans from those decades.</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Fantastic Beasts Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/435259</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wsVseA7i3FqX24m26Z2gD3EtH4l.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jc1Sh8U6dvWv9rHaRl8aosTAoPN.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them is a 2016 fantasy film directed by David Yates. A spin-off of the Harry Potter film series, it was produced and written by J. K. Rowling, in her screenwriting debut, and inspired by her book of the same name. The film stars Eddie Redmayne as Newt Scamander with Katherine Waterston, Dan Fogler, Alison Sudol, Ezra Miller, Samantha Morton, Jon Voight, Carmen Ejogo, Ron Perlman and Colin Farrell in supporting roles. It is the first instalment in the Fantastic Beasts series, and the ninth overall in J. K. Rowling's Wizarding World. Initially, in October 2014, the studio announced the film would be the start of a trilogy. The sequel is  to be released on 16 November 2018, followed by the third on 20 November 2020. In July 2016, David Yates confirmed that Rowling had written the screenplay for the second film and has ideas for the third. However, in October 2016 Rowling confirmed that the series would comprise five films.
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>



<dir>
	<title>The Fast and the Furious Collection (2001-2021)</title>
	<tmdb>collection/9485</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mCkqJf4ijbNoBWvJ0RTWZJuhJUA.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/z5A5W3WYJc3UVEWljSGwdjDgQ0j.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>An action film series centered on illegal street racing and heists.</summary>
	<content>boxset</content>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Ghostbusters Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/2980</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zsSnQq4lGocDkqsrdVUTNNjZz7R.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/g54JU2Bn4EFezsawnI7ccpAzPC7.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>Ghostbusters is a 1984 American supernatural comedy film, directed and produced by Ivan Reitman and written by Dan Aykroyd and Harold Ramis. The film stars Bill Murray, Aykroyd, and Ramis as three eccentric parapsychologists in New York City who start a ghost-catching business. The second film, Ghostbusters II, was released in 1989 and the third movie, Ghostbusters, was released in 2016.
	</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Gremlins Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/89151</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mcrb8SdAOrJpSMbWWS3Hv304FCG.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2Oz7EyiM9nNeP7appRFkMZNeYRo.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>Gremlins is a 1984 American horror comedy film directed by Joe Dante, Steven Spielberg was the film's executive producer and the screenplay was written by Chris Columbus. The film is about a young man who receives a strange creature called a Mogwai as a pet, which then spawns other creatures who transform into small, destructive, evil monsters. This story was continued with a sequel, Gremlins 2: The New Batch, released in 1990. Unlike the lighter sequel, the original Gremlins opts for more black comedy, which is balanced against a Christmas-time ting. Both films were the center of large merchandising campaigns.</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>The Hangover Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/86119</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aMmNLuyXvdBih1R5RRHtdtNaS6N.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uEtsf26a9RsRDy85MOIv1xAj44x.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>The Hangover is a 2009 American comedy film, co-produced and directed by Todd Phillips and written by Jon Lucas and Scott Moore. It is the first film of The Hangover franchise. The film stars Bradley Cooper, Ed Helms, Zach Galifianakis, Heather Graham, Justin Bartha, and Jeffrey Tambor. The Hangover tells the story of Phil Wenneck, Stu Price and Alan Garner, who travel to Las Vegas for a bachelor party to celebrate their friend Doug Billings' impending marriage. However, Phil, Stu and Alan have no memory of the previous night's events and must find Doug before the wedding can take place. It was followed by 2 sequels.
	</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Harry Potter Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/1241</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8Xmkc1HvCOpMlbFvVabrtr6HAsp.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hWK8gTH2riuv65Ej43hPSeE16Mu.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>The Harry Potter films are a fantasy series based on the series of seven Harry Potter novels by British writer J. K. Rowling.
	</summary>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>HellBoy Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/17235</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/81B1OdGY7f3TVN06eKra25vHzYk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/i6WF7cYiogl8g5ryZDbZBw8RNVN.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>The character Hellboy is a demon who fights for the U.S. government and himself against dark forces including Nazis and Baba Yaga, in a series of tales that have their roots in folklore, pulp magazines, vintage adventure, and horror fiction. This collection includes the theatrical release films.
	</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Herbie Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/12087</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nZ1ZGuFP0okrwuGhvl7A2q3YSul.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1bR4Dnb3cbftFGVljXpf3CkGYfA.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>Herbie is an anthropomorphic 1963 Volkswagen Beetle, a character that is featured in several Disney motion pictures starting with the 1968 feature film The Love Bug. He has a mind of his own and is capable of driving himself, and is a serious contender in auto racing competitions. Throughout most of the franchise, Herbie is distinguished by red, white and blue racing stripes from front to back bumper, a racing-style number "53" on the front trunk lid, doors, and engine lid, and a yellow-on-black '63 California license plate that says, "OFP 857". One exception to this is his introduction in The Love Bug, where he initially appears as a nondescript white vehicle with a gray colored fabric sunroof (a.k.a. "ragtop"), the style of sunroof offered on VW Beetles made through 1963.
	</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Highlander Collection</title>
	<link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Johnstonevo/20ap/master/base/20AP/movies/highlander.xml</link>
	<animated_thumbnail></animated_thumbnail>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w472_and_h708_bestv2/mNIXoyFicGseg9NoG3NHKZolKze.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/m8HRNju4wYm8ISm0Mth7KMmTTrH.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>Following the exploits of two immortal Scottish highlanders Conner and Duncan Macleod. Born of different times and fighting throughout the centuries to gain the mystical prize. Spanning history friendship, devastating relationships and legendary battles each immortal learns that there seemingly never ending life is more of a curse than a gift. But for the sake of mankind they must go on fighting to survive until only one remains
	</summary>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>The Hobbit Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/121938</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hm2VtxeCBqWJnPNmvXPPXiHydyp.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7wO7MSnP5UcwR2cTHdJFF1vP4Ie.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>The Hobbit collection is a three-part epic fantasy-adventure film directed and produced by Peter Jackson and based on J. R. R. Tolkien's fantasy novel of the same name. The trilogy of films are  in Middle-earth 60 years before "The Lord of the Rings", and will act as a prequel to Jackson's The Lord of the Rings trilogy.
	</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Hunger Games</title>
	<tmdb>collection/131635</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ttbKy12hDjSHQcM7sCoeW1WsDlW.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lWZB4VFSlU292oJ3ZAzAzPi9GU0.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>A science fiction film series based on the novel of the same name by Suzanne Collins. The film series takes place in a dystopian post-apocalyptic future in the nation of Panem, featuring the protagonist, Katniss Everdeen.
	</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Indiana Jones Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/84</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lpxDrACKJhbbGOlwVMNz5YCj6SI.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6kh59mZizZsttZPR0HAdXk6Ve2n.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>The Adventure films series from the Director George Lucas and Steven Spielberg, starring Harrison Ford as the archeologist Dr. Henry Walton "Indiana" Jones, Jr..
	</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Jack Reacher Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/403374</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7baSUtFKi8PQ9SLo6ECYBfAW2K8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3FHrAeYMogXd6K1e5tUzQAiS7GE.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>Jack Reacher (formerly One Shot) is a 2012 American action thriller film written and directed by Christopher McQuarrie, based on Lee Child's 2005 novel One Shot. The film stars Tom Cruise as the title character, with Rosamund Pike, David Oyelowo, Richard Jenkins, Jai Courtney, Werner Herzog and Robert Duvall also starring. Cruise reprised his role in the sequel, Jack Reacher: Never Go Back, based on the 2013 novel Never Go Back, which was released in October 2016.
	</summary>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Jump Street Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/212562</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vufY0iuDNXGEdYOgZNcJFAEZeak.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iiAbTNYXpMadPDH4MkjUoJzcGn4.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>A series of films based on the lives of the Jump Street program, an undercover police unit in which young-looking detectives infiltrate schools and similar tings attended by minors to investigate crimes.
	</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>The Karate Kid Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/8580</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/o6h2F0C5eZOy50Q76fNYzc9mvvw.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sq4c328WCIFIVD7B9ZGFRwDbUTH.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>The first three films in the series follow Daniel LaRusso, who learns to harness karate for good through the eccentric mentorship of a janitor named Mr. Miyagi. In the fourth and final film of the original series, Mr. Miyagi becomes the caretaker of his friend's granddaughter in attempt to steer her away from trouble. The fifth film is a remake of the original film's premise without maintaining any of the original character names and replacing karate with kung fu.
	</summary>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Kingsman Collection (2015-2017)</title>
	<tmdb>collection/391860</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uk7UCjLyvSodRU5ufbiemCEZ3SG.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8XZnIWG7on74SaJ6t23kdPOYXUG.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>The story of a super-secret spy organization that recruits an unrefined but promising street kid into the agency's ultra-competitive training program.
	</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Lethal Weapon Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/945</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7PH31kIhz6BnzoP9cxG7JbkB6fT.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w780/5zg6QLY0tdDLVHLwn28oowG3m8H.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>Lethal Weapon is a buddy cop movie series starring Mel Gibson and Danny Glover. A total of four films have been made since the first one in 1987, and all have been a success at the box-office.
	</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Lord Of The Rings Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/119</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/p4UokEk2XnjjRTdXGe6DLYXlbI1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bccR2CGTWVVSZAG0yqmy3DIvhTX.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>The Lord of the Rings trilogy consists of three epic fantasy films, based on the influential novels written by J. R. R. Tolkien, directed by Peter Jackson.
	</summary>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Machete Collection (2010-2013)</title>
	<tmdb>collection/210006</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7kN9MY7htPG0sI598VJK2pB6zEs.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vURYjEnOd8if3juhZh6HRcTJs7T.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>Series of the movies about former Mexican Federale Machete. An expansion of a fake trailer that was included in Rodriguez's and Quentin Tarantino's 2007 Grindhouse double-feature. Machete continues the B movie and exploitation style of Grindhouse and includes some of the footage. Isador "Machete" Cortez first appearance was as the Uncle in all four Spy Kids movies.
	</summary>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Mad Max Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/8945</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tSVbihfvVTCbcm0zXKA7L8R6Y9v.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w780/jZowUf4okNYuSlgj5iURE7CDMho.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>Mad Max is an Australian dystopian action media franchise. Mad Max references are deeply embedded in popular culture; references to its dystopian, apocalyptic, and post-apocalyptic themes and bizarre landscape and desolate wasteland imagery.
	</summary>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>The Man With No Name Trilogy</title>
	<tmdb>collection/48317</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2WXES6zvf5LEUMEfi0BXmtXIOUl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uAkE1MAvFUiYjOllgDRndispKu3.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>Sergio Leone's landmark "Spaghetti Western" "Dollars Trilogy" series, featuring Clint Eastwood as "The Man with No Name".
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Marvel Collection</title>
      <trakt>https://api.trakt.tv/users/donxy/lists/marvel-cinematic-universe/items</trakt>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aC3VJyuNpymHAf9pyQqB20EK4v6.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zuW6fOiusv4X9nnW3paHGfXcSll.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>The Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU) is an American media franchise and shared universe that is centered on a series of superhero films, independently produced by Marvel Studios and based on characters that appear in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. The franchise has expanded to include comic books, short films, television series, and digital series. The shared universe, much like the original Marvel Universe in comic books, was established by crossing over common plot elements, tings, cast, and characters. Phil Coulson, portrayed by Clark Gregg, is an original character to the MCU and the only character to appear across all the different media of the MCU.
	</summary>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Matrix Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/2344</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lh4aGpd3U9rm9B8Oqr6CUgQLtZL.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bRm2DEgUiYciDw3myHuYFInD7la.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>The Matrix collection depicts a complex science fiction story incorporating many philosophical elements. Written and directed by the Wachowski brothers and produced by Joel Silver.
	</summary>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>The Maze Runner Collection (2014-2018)</title>
	<tmdb>collection/295130</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/beR71cbwXH0vySlTMPZo0GQ54Q9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eQ8iwAvGfuNnPjBCKTIVp5PsFw.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>The film series consists of science-fiction dystopian action adventure films based on The Maze Runner novels by the American author James Dashner. They begin with Thomas who wakes up trapped in a maze with a group of other boys, he has no memory of the outside world other than dreams about an organization known as W.C.K.D. Only by piecing together fragments of his past with clues he discovers in the maze can Thomas hope to uncover his purpose and a way to escape.
	</summary>
	<content>boxset</content>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Monty Python Collection</title>
	<link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Johnstonevo/20ap/master/base/20AP/movies/montypython.xml</link>
	<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/71gX0Wf9DVL._SY445_.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://images4.alphacoders.com/118/thumb-1920-11826.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary></summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Mummy Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/1733</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4UMn5KmXopgpkC862Ms3t5j1sXl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1BeKi6IytbfQlQocJSvP2k6sO1a.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>The Mummy film series is a remake of The Mummy, loosely based on the original 1932 film. The first two films in the series were written and directed by Stephen Sommers.
	</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>The Neverending Story Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/91430</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tXuOhgEbXoba7vVIybzGlnycoNq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2IqXJIR1i0f6Ngq3A6rjXhQNqFc.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>“A boy who needs a friend finds a world that needs a hero in a land beyond imagination!”
	</summary>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Ocean's Collection (2001-2007)</title>
	<tmdb>collection/304</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oHUHccvraYF8lYp6BxRoujRtH8Q.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/z2TbwtEzjMxYZ8TXfbJmhbahkom.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>The Ocean's Trilogy is a star-studded film series about a group of professional robbers who get together to pull off some mind-boggling heists.
	</summary>
</dir>





<dir>
	<title>Pirates of the Caribbean Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/295</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zT5UKFhq9nk97VGlBbAxlAK8UFN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cnKAGbX1rDkAquF2V1wVkptHDJO.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>Pirates of the Caribbean is a series of fantasy swashbuckler films produced by Jerry Bruckheimer and based on Walt Disney's theme park ride of the same name. Directors of the series include Gore Verbinski (1–3), Rob Marshall (4), and Joachim Rønning and Espen Sandberg (5). The series was most notably written by Ted Elliott and Terry Rossio (1–4); other writers include Stuart Beattie (1), Jay Wolpert (1), and Jeff Nathanson (5). The stories followed the adventures of Captain Jack Sparrow (Johnny Depp), Hector Barbossa (Geoffrey Rush), Joshamee Gibbs (Kevin McNally), Will Turner (Orlando Bloom), and Elizabeth Swann (Keira Knightley). The films take place in a fictional historical ting; a world ruled largely by alternative versions of the British Empire, the East India Company and the Spanish Empire, with pirates representing freedom from the ruling powers.
	</summary>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Pitch Perfect Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/306031</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/n1bCFVJeVxX1yCTnXy4OCRwynF1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jolu4gMP6g2VmUZt099U6X6jNNJ.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>A series of musical comedy films follow Barden University's all-girl a cappella group, The Barden Bellas.
	</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Police Academy Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/9338</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xvv8H9lqTvSqtll8fksEcIhTnMx.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/RhpI828r9EKPV4x0pyHiqCDZDQ.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>Police Academy is a series of American comedy films, the first six of which were made in the 1980s. The seventh and to date last installment, Mission to Moscow, was released in 1994. The new film is scheduled for production for 2014. The series opened with Police Academy (1984) which started with the premise that a new mayor had announced a policy requiring the police department to accept all willing recruits. The movie followed a group of misfit recruits in their attempts to prove themselves capable of being police officers. The main character, Carey Mahoney (Steve Guttenberg), was a repeat offender who was forced to join the police academy as punishment.
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Prometheus Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/135416</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gMjiXB5dhV8nN77xXnhTIhARE7a.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cK83Pq8SJoeSTnLJucr8IWn35KF.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>Prometheus is a 2012 science fiction film directed by Ridley Scott, written by Jon Spaihts and Damon Lindelof and starring Noomi Rapace, Michael Fassbender, Guy Pearce, Idris Elba, Logan Marshall-Green and Charlize Theron. It is  in the late 21st century and centers on the crew of the spaceship Prometheus as it follows a star map discovered among the artifacts of several ancient Earth cultures. Seeking the origins of humanity, the crew arrives on a distant world and discovers a threat that could cause the extinction of the human species. On May 19, 2017 the sequel titled Alien: Covenant will take place ten years after the events of Prometheus. As title alludes to the film will have a connection to the character of Ellen Ripley from original film series.
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Rambo Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/5039</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/feGOEOVrOLyjtEnVa88rQLgD3XY.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7x3GUZALySIuhqkUZjYSFFbYaxl.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>Rambo is an action film series based on the David Morrell novel First Blood and starring Sylvester Stallone as John Rambo, a troubled Vietnam War veteran and former Green Beret who is skilled in many aspects of survival, weaponry, hand to hand combat and guerrilla warfare.
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>



<dir>
	<title>RoboCop Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/5547</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/foJBQb9oEOH0mGh77tXyoxXCfzU.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/azQScQWHpz5puIV4YeCcqgiT9Tn.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>RoboCop is a 1987 American cyberpunk action film directed by Paul Verhoeven and written by Edward Neumeier and Michael Miner. The film stars Peter Weller, Nancy Allen, Dan O'Herlihy, Kurtwood Smith, Miguel Ferrer, and Ronny Cox.  in a crime-ridden Detroit, Michigan, in the near future, RoboCop centers on police officer Alex Murphy who is brutally shot to death by a gang of criminals and subsequently revived by the megacorporation Omni Consumer Products (OCP) as a superhuman cyborg law enforcer known as "RoboCop". Collection includes 2 sequels.
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Rocky Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/1575</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7HxeQbYYlY1KuHy1CashvU7H4QW.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/JhGydj4q5y8MoWZFyj15yKNrzC.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>These sport drama films begin by telling the rags to riches American Dream story of Rocky Balboa, an uneducated but kind-hearted working class Italian-American boxer working as a debt collector for a loan shark in the slums of Philadelphia.
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>



<dir>
	<title>Romancing the Stone Collection (1984-1985)</title>
	<tmdb>collection/89264</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mHJHMng2y2jLHgz2S8AoACVgJMi.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kwgTcDfbrvVTqMOczKfFqJa3d7p.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>An action-adventure romantic comedy film series about the adventures of fictional romance novelist Joan Wilder (Kathleen Turner), and bird exporter Jack T. Colton (Micheal Douglas).</summary>
	<content>boxset</content>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Sharpe Collection (1993-2008)</title>
	<tmdb>collection/69788</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hmdcvEQA2uCGwB8MflWj0zTWov.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oDQk8pqOuiBxfpoTOQUk5Vejt1M.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>Richard Sharpe is the dashing maverick British rifleman fighting against Napoleon in 19th century Europe in this British television series. Based on the best-selling novels by Bernard Cornwell, the series also stars Assumpta Serna as Teresa, Daragh O'Malley as Harper, Abigail Cruttenden as Jane and Cecile Paoli as Lucille.
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>

<dir>
	<title>Smokey And The Bandit Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/87220</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3QClCwnHXmTutb6cMXFsqTEU3BM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ldGGb98U7ytidfLHY5wKazeB6MO.jpg</fanart>
	<content>set</content>
	<summary>The Smokey and the Bandit Collection is a series of movies about the adventures of the legendary Bandit and his run ins with Sheriff "Smokey" Justice.
	</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>The Smurfs Collection</title>
	<tmdb>collection/134897</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4GYf9E6ptMJPinDpnoqHdKNt1H3.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mUN96AWlMupDR7NXaPhFmMEYIBM.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>An American CGI/live-action film series based on The Smurfs comic book series created by the Belgian comics artist Peyo and the 1980s animated TV series.
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>



<dir>
	<title>Star Trek</title>
      <trakt>https://api.trakt.tv/users/dgw/lists/star-trek-canon/items</trakt>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zcB8KxHA4EapOoZZPAvwgmE1iGK.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9BQj9hq0aK6yM9Tm2NJ28jg572y.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Official Star Trek productions, including reboots, excluding fan/documentary/behind-the-scenes productions.

Sorted by production order, not in-universe chronology. I think Star Trek should be viewed in production order, so it's evident how the franchise has changed over the last 50+ years.
</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>




<dir>
	<title>Star Wars Collection</title>
      <trakt>https://api.trakt.tv/users/ruben_vw_/lists/star-wars-canon-timeline/items</trakt>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ghd5zOQnDaDW1mxO7R5fXXpZMu.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/d8duYyyC9J5T825Hg7grmaabfxQ.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>An epic space opera theatrical film series that depicts the adventures of various characters "a long time ago in a galaxy far, far away".<summary>
		<content>set</content>
	</dir>




	<dir>
		<title>Taken collection</title>
		<tmdb>collection/135483</tmdb>
		<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4PNFiSaJWvWhkdOw0KF9Vf7v3gC.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hO1R1TI429PjkOjby4dTPBrWFwn.jpg</fanart>
		<summary>A French action thriller film series based upon fictional former CIA operative Bryan Mills who is abroad in Europe.
		</summary>
		<content>set</content>
	</dir>

	<dir>
		<title>The Terminator Collection</title>
		<tmdb>collection/528</tmdb>
		<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vxiKtcxAJxHhlg2H1X8y7zcM3k6.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cpmbkwSxZnKO69V82A9a34tvk2E.jpg</fanart>
		<summary>A series of science-fiction films about the futuristic conflict between the humans led by John Connor and the terminators that are made and controlled by Skynet, a self-aware super computer that started Armageddon and may indeed end humanity for good. Skynet's most well-known products in its genocidal goals are the various terminator models, such as the T-800 (Model 101).
		</summary>
		<content>set</content>
	</dir>



<dir>
	<title>This is England Collection (2006-2015)</title>
	<tmdb>collection/376863</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wVc7lwmTgDN7QY4G9V8dfYynDec.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2sUnp8H8vSG0BY2WXdZz0qhqWXV.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>This is England (2006): A story about a troubled boy growing up in England, set in 1983. He comes across a few skinheads on his way home from school, after a fight. They become his new best friends even like family. Based on experiences of director Shane Meadows. This is England '88 (2011): Set during Christmas 1988, Lol is haunted by the devastating events that took place two and a half years before. She and Woody both find themselves struggling to cope with their lives without each other after he leaves the gang. This is England '90 (2015): Following on from This Is England ’86 and ‘88, this much-anticipated final chapter finds the gang embracing the rave scene of a new decade. But the utter hilarity and unadulterated joy of the second ‘summer of love’ soon gives way to a war torn winter. As the stark reality of life takes hold and, ultimately, takes life.
	</summary>
	<content>set</content>
</dir>

	<dir>
		<title>Transformers Collection</title>
		<tmdb>collection/8650</tmdb>
		<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vOUPHWV8aGXq4yYQ2csje5LdT6g.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zvZBNNDWd5LcsIBpDhJyCB2MDT7.jpg</fanart>
		<summary>The Transformers series follows the continuing battle between the Autobots and the Decepticons and ultimately, the triumph of good over evil. This collection includes the Theatrically Released Films of the transformers saga only.
		</summary>
		<content>set</content>
	</dir>

	<dir>
		<title>The Transporter Collection</title>
		<tmdb>collection/9518</tmdb>
		<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uakYnYtFxqjS8pjEWW9lGWmdMRz.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qDuTIGAEbxF3jP9zNILLAoxNLpU.jpg</fanart>
		<summary>Follows the expolits of Frank Martin, a professional "transporter" who delivers packages without questions.
		</summary>
		<content>set</content>
	</dir>

	<dir>
		<title>Underworld Collection</title>
		<tmdb>collection/2326</tmdb>
		<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aK8qq0X0pZbf5ncE3JLQ27hdC4F.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2gSaXagD9ZCuBHOsXF4tvtW7Djd.jpg</fanart>
		<summary>A series of action horror films centered on Vampires and Lycans. In the 5th century, a man named Alexander Corvinus was the only survivor of a plague that wiped out his village. Somehow, Alexander's body was able to turn the disease to his own benefit and so he became the first true Immortal. Later, he fathered two sons who became the first Vampire and Lycan by being bitten by a bat and a wolf.
		</summary>
		<content>set</content>
	</dir>


	<dir>
		<title>The Wolverine Collection</title>
		<tmdb>collection/453993</tmdb>
		<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c18HVnKTybcAUYVQd8rOcdbqwY.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hbNMx7sxxqvkX8rLOsTryiSrCPY.jpg</fanart>
		<summary>A Film series based on the Marvel Superhero Wolverine.</summary>
		<content>set</content>
	</dir>

	<dir>
		<title>X-Men Movie Collection</title>
		<tmdb>collection/748</tmdb>
		<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eq2kBgmiagXQgo2S96L8DZ9ou0F.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/roZFGw3Rg6VOYty9y4r5WvgvXoC.jpg</fanart>
		<summary>A superhero film series about a team of mutant superheroes based on the Marvel Comics superheroes of the same name.
		</summary>
		<content>set</content>
	</dir>

	<dir>
		<title>XxX Collection</title>
		<tmdb>collection/52785</tmdb>
		<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/omRo1Pw4phlELRgYOQ7RyAlccLt.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/g9Q2dmbxd1F2hHB5VslPbqGM1JV.jpg</fanart>
		<summary>XXX (pronounced as Triple X and stylized as xXx) is an American action franchise created by Rich Wilkes. The franchise stars Vin Diesel and Ice Cube and consists of three films: xXx (2002), xXx: State of the Union (2005) and xXx: Return of Xander Cage (2017), and a short film: (possibly non-canon) The Final Chapter: The Death of Xander Cage (2005). The series has grossed $656 million worldwide.
		</summary>
		<content>set</content>
	</dir>


    <dir>
      <title>Young Guns Collection (1988-1990)</title>
      <tmdb>collection/9329</tmdb>
			<summary>Young Guns is a retelling of the adventures of Billy the Kid during the Lincoln County War, which took place in New Mexico during 1877–1878</summary>
			<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/26Y1BApN2lOO18NX2ibEHOwbL1L.jpg</thumbnail>
			<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/whZZ13xGyCLFn21yVhQ9RXMSuKh.jpg</fanart>
    </dir>



		<dir>
			<title>The X-Files Collection (1998-2008)</title>
			<tmdb>collection/19387</tmdb>
			<summary>The X-Files (also known as The X-Files: Fight the Future) is a 1998 American science fiction thriller film directed by Rob Bowman. Chris Carter wrote the screenplay. The story is by Carter and Frank Spotnitz. It is the first feature film based on Carter's television series The X-Files that revolves around fictional unsolved cases called the X-Files and the characters solving them. The X-Files has spawned one sequel, a 2008 film entitled The X-Files: I Want to Believe released six years after the series ended.
			</summary>
			<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6BYNXJ6fS7HKsotqWiUJzYiFZJ0.jpg</thumbnail>
			<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/22p3xTTuXc9FEnzyGlfB9KBtR4Y.jpg</fanart>
		</dir>
