################################################################################
  <thumbnail>https://avatarfiles.alphacoders.com/100/100363.jpg</thumbnail>


################################################################################


<dir>
  <title>Man Cave Shows</title>
  <tmdb>list/47260</tmdb>
  <thumbnail>https://avatarfiles.alphacoders.com/100/100363.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://www.desktopbackground.org/download/1280x720/2014/05/20/765189_hot-rod-wallpapers_1600x1200_h.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>TV Shows, Movies about cars, modding and the like.
  </summary>
</dir>




<plugin>
  <title>Goodwood Road & Racing</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC8rador8CU-pTJ6p7WNiv6w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-zMHS-SqcCLY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/_8Vbx9I-v20/s100-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to Goodwood Road & Racing; the ultimate pit stop for racing day action, motor sport festivals, car and bike news and reviews, road tests, corporate race days and more!
  </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Jay Leno's Garage</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCQMELFlXQL38KPm8kM-4Adg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-FyLHrCVfntI/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/4C9MwGbvp0E/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>A new video every Sunday! Visit Jay Leno's Garage, the Emmy-winning series where Jay Leno gives car reviews, motorcycle reviews, compares cars, and shares his passion and expertise on anything that rolls, explodes, and makes noise. Classic cars, restomods, super cars like the McLaren P1, sports cars like Porsche 918 Spyder and Camaro Z28, cafe racers, vintage cars, and much, much more. </summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Hagerty</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCLgEVx4mzk3T3mzgbKG54Eg/playlists/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-CXSm1S1JUB0/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/_7OJxDosi_Q/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Hagerty is your definitive source for all things classic: compelling stories about cool cars and the people who love them; the latest on collector car values and market trends; and all the eye candy, roaring engines and nostalgia you can handle. So strap down, settle in and cruise with us a while. We’re glad you’re here. Subscribe for weekly content.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>Hot Rod Builds US</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCYnqhZMlujN86kZ1OyBEhVQ/playlists/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-LT4iSh2eIdc/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/UvJ0KzLKqhc/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>
</summary>
</plugin>




<plugin>
  <title>Wrecks To Riches | Rust To Riches</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UChDl30jdrg7HlHlqtiLQTKA/playlists/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-xAEWszW1eD8/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/JX38GrAL1is/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>If you like car customizing then you'll love this channel. Featuring custom build shows including Wrecks to Riches, Rust to Riches, Hot Rod - Build Off and more!
</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Motor Trend Channel</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCsAegdhiYLEoaFGuJFVrqFQ/playlists/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-K-cVNW0boRs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Jg9oUhvZgjM/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Get your automotive adrenaline charge right here on the Motor Trend channel. From first drives and tests of the hottest new supercars and classic muscle cars to the latest automotive news from around the world, to the incredible machinery and personalities from beyond the automotive mainstream, the Motor Trend channel has it all, delivered daily.  The Motor Trend channel. Drive it. Race It. Live it.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>HOT ROD Network</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCSXk90dGoNNA8hA6888-xIw/playlists/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-rVkABz2-ZoE/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/ePf90eqBe3I/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>For over 60 years HOT ROD® Magazine has been an American institution.  First published in 1948, HOT ROD® Magazine has been at the center of the automotive performance scene delivering an unrivaled mix of commentary, technical information, trends, and of course, beautiful photography!

Authenticator of the American Hot Rod lifestyle, HOT ROD® Magazine is one of the most recognized automotive brand names in the world.</summary>
</plugin>

<plugin>
  <title>The House Of Muscle</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC4v1DUBqe2mQRqFritd7zVQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-KaGFh8zi7wo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/fA8FXaHlCUc/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>The House Of Muscle: The Show

Muscle cars are a threatened breed. So we, the drivers, the builders and the owners need a place to enjoy and revel in their full shock and awe. So Welcome, motor-heads, to The House Of Muscle.

Every month, Mike Musto travels the country showcasing how these automobiles shape automotive culture. Musto profiles the car and the owners, then takes these amazing machines no-holds-barred test drive.

THOM: Moderns

We’re living in the golden age of muscle cars. An age where engines far surpass the best the 1960s had to offer. These modern cars keep the candles of horsepower burning bright.

THOM: Tuning

The House Of Muscle Tuning show brings you the latest from the aftermarket world. From engine, suspension, and brake upgrades to interior enhancements, we’ll make sure you make the right decisions when updating your ride.

THOM: Extra

The House of Muscle Extra gives viewers a behind the scenes look into the bits which didn’t make it into our full episodes.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Lucky’s Garage Show</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCsAaakmE0dAtG7AVFb7oUEA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-9csNo72ASxs/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/00DSisTaWNQ/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Mobiletechlucky Wiring and fabrication for Custom Cars and HotRods</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DEBOSS GARAGE</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCLXV9vzJwgYOyGaZlD89VfA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Skq4NjOPPCo/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/gBAeV2PjIQ0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>From American Muscle to Classics to Diesels, we show you how to build, swap, and repair all kinds of vehicles on YouTube.
NEW VIDEOS EVERY WEEK</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Finnegan's Garage</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC1IdPylqngGiuHFLJqHbG_g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-E9xnK269FmQ/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/P9KEhoFXIUE/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>TheHoonigans</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCXlfi8sf6cKGQ8sOd0-yRuw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-z2kiBjBhlfw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/z59SIuFzfkw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>This is the official YouTube page of Hoonigan. It contains awesome hoonage, caught on tape.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Mighty Car Mods</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCgJRL30YS6XFxq9Ga8W2J3A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-b8-0ku2pp-U/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/2QftimURo_A/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Mighty Car Mods is an independent automotive series created by a couple of friends, Marty and Moog who started filming videos on Martys mum's driveway in 2007. They've come a long way since then but still have an unwavering focus to show their viewers fantastic automotive projects that they can do themselves at home.
The MCM boys make cars, and they make movies. In fact they do it all, including the music, editing, and automotive with some help from their friends along the way.
Being completely independent, the boys don't have to answer to anyone except their own creative spirit and their focus is on quality over quantity.
It doesn't matter if you have a brand new turbo charged beast, or an old banger found in your grandfathers shed. Mighty Car Mods openly embraces anyone who wants to better themselves and their cars through involvement with the MCM Community.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Haggard Garage</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCIFkGwlFTbYKmxsbLtqq-TQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-M-CNOAVqPJM/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/UXhBxWqhty4/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Just a group of homies with a passion for drifting.
Mint.
Drift Team Haggard
Haggard Racing Co.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>LowMileage</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCOABx_lB4InzJyo5AnJAGXw/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-TtyHCgHo_ts/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/FEhMwadI6h8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>In this channel you will find a variety of old, classic sports car renovation project videos. We strive to provide quality and interesting projects for you. Watch, share and comment on  your favorite video. And importantly - do not forget subscribe to our channel!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Petrolicious</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCgyJPixJl95X1ut3E9K99KA/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-RKoRbVvY7IA/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Z0ckVVccgYw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Petrolicious creates quality, original videos and articles for classic car enthusiasts.
We celebrate the inventions, the personalities, and the aesthetics that ignite our collective lust for great machines. We are fans and fanatics, collectors and racers. We seek to inform, entertain, and inspire our community of aficionados and pique the interest of those who have been missing out.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>CHERAL AUTO</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCTWVyP3BvJaX3vuwQeFyrbg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-4WQhO4xiK3k/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/n-FkJtQ_X68/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>We are here to fulfill your automotive interests and appreciation in everything car-build related, while at the same time help you rediscover new models that you had never considered before
Let CHERAL AUTO be the spark that ignites your automotive imagination and enthusiasm for everything involving car builds, modifications and restorations.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>DIY Garage</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCoV2Qw0sL-ApYQ62k-88K1w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-uW1aXYldd-E/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/4sngo3-cA68/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to DIY Garage, where we feature restoration projects, builds, collision & body repair, engine swaps, tuning, customization, auto reviews and much more! So Subscribe and stay tuned for more videos.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>TheSmokingTire</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCgeGealT0QYcrnoYRMltDZg/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-hXfw2tAFSK4/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/v7cLgaVP-E8/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>The Smoking Tire, hosted by Matt Farah, is the premier destination for automotive video reviews and adventures. No Hollywood, no bosses, no bullshit. From our brains to your eyes and ears, this is The Smoking Tire.</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>B is for Build</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCl4-WBRqWA2MlxmZorKOV7w/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-7cyBadiMc94/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/BBD67j0CCUw/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to B is for Build. A place where Chris and his friends document their life with cars. We fix cars, we break cars, we buy, sell, and trade cars all with the ultimate goal of having fun. Check it out!</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Hand Built Cars</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCScQZ0eVeXrAgbkur8j0w3Q/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-t0sFxBMxmqY/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Yp7GSl8Wca0/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to our channel "Hand Built Cars" where we put together worlds best car build, restoration, rebuild, and modification projects for you to amaze. We link all build threads so you can get in touch with builders and learn how they did build their cars, ask them questions about their builds, so that will help you to build your own project car! :)

Daily uploads for you to see, learn and get inspired for your future projects.

And if you're building your car or you know interesting project that you want to share to the biggest and best car builders community in world just send us an e-mail and tell us about your build and get shout out for massive and fast growing audience worldwide.
</summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>GarageWorkz</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCWKBbPXSUatRO1RddgtPf_A/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-z48aCKSMF28/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/JYYRKidfTdY/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>


<plugin>
  <title>Build Diaries</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC_qVOcO6rXhpRDK3jA7_jkQ/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-8VCQBdJGNWg/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/Ig3SmEpmmRI/s288-c-k-no-mo-rj-c0xffffff/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Build Diaries brings you the most interesting and detailed car restoration, rebuild and restromod project videos.</summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>MyClassicCarTV</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UC2ggrxKhqgTRx7We9vjQRCQ/playlists/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-8WPUhySFp3s/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/hWHsVFO7FBo/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Sin City Motors</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCyWdRrgP_7kgyekQCCCAtBg/</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary></summary>
</plugin>



<plugin>
  <title>Crush Time</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/channel/UCJYL4S3BPWcC2QOpKwU334g/</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-g_L2IjEgFlw/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/e2mpJzZH4Cg/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Crush Time has the best car crash , motorbike, plane and road rush. All crashes are not fatal. Please take these compilations as a learning tool. Be careful on the road!!! Crush Time will also offer funny videos and fails as a separate category.
  </summary>
</plugin>
