#################################################################################
<content>set</content>
<fanart></fanart>
################################################################################
<dir>
  <title>Jensen Ackles</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/49624</tmdb>
  <summary>Jensen Ross Ackles (born March 1, 1978) is an American actor. He is notable for his television roles as Eric Brady in Days of our Lives which earned him several Daytime Emmy Award nominations, as Alec/X5-494 in Dark Angel, and as Jason Teague in Smallville. Ackles now appears as Dean Winchester on the CW television series Supernatural.
</summary>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/39MTpPwzCQEIVnoPW35gAVLoKMt.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://stmed.net/sites/default/files/jensen-ackles-wallpapers-26852-8801025.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Jenny Agutter</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/14464</tmdb>
  <summary>Jennifer Ann "Jenny" Agutter (born 20 December 1952) is an English film and television actress. She began her career as a child actress in the mid 1960s, starring in the BBC television series The Railway Children and the film adaptation of the same book, before moving on to adult roles and relocating to Hollywood.

She played Alex Price in An American Werewolf in London, Jessica 6 in Logan's Run, Joanne Simpson in Child's Play 2 and Jill Mason in Equus. Since the 1990s, she has worked in sound recording, and she is a patron of the Cystic Fibrosis Trust. After a break from acting she has appeared in several television series since 2000, including the British series Spooks and Call the Midwife.

</summary>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2AwYEHV0cXXo3vtjiuwHMEkqh6R.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://www.jennyagutter.net/images/childsplayfull.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Sean Astin</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/1328</tmdb>
  <summary>Sean Astin (born February 25, 1971) is an American film actor, director, and producer better known for his film roles as Mikey Walsh in The Goonies, the title character of Rudy, and Samwise Gamgee in the Lord of the Rings trilogy. In television, he appeared as Lynn McGill in the fifth season of 24. Most recently, he provided the voice for the title character in Disney's Special Agent Oso.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jqF72oav6vmGAWl33GNO6EpZtwA.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.etonline.com/sites/default/files/images/2017-10/1280_sean_astin_getty.jpg</fanart>
</dir>



<dir>
  <title>Richard Attenborough</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/4786</tmdb>
  <summary>Richard Samuel Attenborough, Baron Attenborough, Kt, CBE (29 August 1923 – 24 August 2014) was an English actor, filmmaker, entrepreneur, and politician. He was the President of the Royal Academy of Dramatic Art (RADA) and the British Academy of Film and Television Arts (BAFTA). Attenborough joined the Royal Air Force during World War II and served in the film unit. He went on several bombing raids over Europe and filmed action from the rear gunner's position.

    As a film director and producer, Attenborough won two Academy Awards for Gandhi in 1983. He also won four BAFTA Awards and four Golden Globe Awards. As an actor, he is perhaps best known for his roles in Brighton Rock, The Great Escape, 10 Rillington Place, Miracle on 34th Street (1994) and Jurassic Park.

    He was the older brother of David Attenborough, a naturalist and broadcaster, and John Attenborough, an executive at Alfa Romeo. He was married to actress Sheila Sim from 1945 until his death.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/Abo8fAcdruACs344ut6PNSKH7N4.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://media.nu.nl/m/m1mxt53as6f7_wd1280.jpg/acteur-en-regisseur-richard-attenborough-90-overleden.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Dan Aykroyd</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/707</tmdb>
  <summary>Daniel Edward "Dan" Aykroyd, CM (born July 1, 1952) is a Canadian comedian, actor, screenwriter, musician, winemaker and ufologist. He was an original cast member of Saturday Night Live, an originator of The Blues Brothers (with John Belushi) and Ghostbusters and has had a long career as a film actor and screenwriter.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Dan Aykroyd, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/h2PT9yZYv5ml5hL9jvCpWBTWgU.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://ecowallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/3948_dan_aykroyd.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Bill Bailey</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/24265</tmdb>
	<summary>Bill Bailey (born Mark Bailey 13 January 1964, Bath, Somerset) is an English stand-up comedian, musician and actor. As well as his extensive stand-up work, Bailey is well known for his appearances on Have I Got News for You, Never Mind the Buzzcocks, QI and Black Books.

Bailey was listed by The Observer as one of the 50 funniest acts in British comedy in 2003. In 2007 and again in 2010, he was voted the 7th greatest stand-up comic on Channel 4's 100 Greatest Stand-Ups. Bill Bailey is a patron of International Animal Rescue.

</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2tFyHLXj3XcwA08GfoORx9hv8vg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/kHS7YSkPzHE/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Drew Barrymore</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/69597</tmdb>
  <summary>Drew Blyth Barrymore (born February 22, 1975) is an American film actress, producer, and director. She is a member of the Barrymore family of American actors and granddaughter of John Barrymore. She first appeared in an advertisement when she was 11 months old. Barrymore made her film debut in Altered States in 1980. Afterwards, she starred in her breakout role in E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial. She quickly became one of Hollywood's most recognized child actors, going on to establish herself in mainly comic roles. Following a turbulent childhood which was marked by drug and alcohol abuse and two stints in rehab, Barrymore wrote the 1990 autobiography, Little Girl Lost. She successfully made the transition from child star to adult actress with a number of films including Poison Ivy, Bad Girls, Boys on the Side, and Everyone Says I Love You. Subsequently, she established herself in romantic comedies such as The Wedding Singer and Lucky You. In 1995, she and business partner Nancy Juvonen formed the production company Flower Films, with its first production the 1999 Barrymore film Never Been Kissed. Flower Films has gone on to produce the Barrymore vehicle films Charlie's Angels, 50 First Dates, and Music and Lyrics, as well as the cult film Donnie Darko. Barrymore's more recent projects include He's Just Not That into You, Beverly Hills Chihuahua, Everybody's Fine and Going the Distance. A recipient of a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame, Barrymore appeared on the cover of the 2007 People magazine's 100 Most Beautiful issue. Barrymore was named Ambassador Against Hunger for the United Nations World Food Programme (WFP). Since then, she has donated over $1 million to the program. In 2007, she became both CoverGirl's newest model and spokeswoman for the cosmetic and the face for Gucci's newest jewelry line. In 2010, she was awarded the Screen Actors Guild Award and the Golden Globe Award for Best Actress in a Miniseries or Television Film for her portrayal of Little Edie in Grey Gardens. Description above from the Wikipedia article Drew Barrymore , licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/y8GKPHsBXVGIGBdDzdNxjm0IbKF.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://www.desktopbackground.org/download/1280x720/2015/05/12/946886_download-1920x1080-drew-barrymore-airbrushed-wallpapers_1920x1080_h.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Sean Bean</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/48</tmdb>
  <summary>Shaun Mark "Sean" Bean (born 17 April 1959) is an English film and stage actor. Bean is best known for starring roles in the films Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring, GoldenEye, Patriot Games, Troy, National Treasure and Silent Hill, as well as the television series Sharpe. Bean has also acted in a number of television productions, most recent being HBO's Game of Thrones, as well as performing voice work for computer games and television adverts.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Sean Bean, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iIxP2IzvcLgr5WaTBD4UfSqaV3q.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/11_Sean-Bean.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Kate Beckinsale</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/3967</tmdb>
  <summary>Kathryn Bailey "Kate" Beckinsale is an English actress. She first gained notice, while a student at Oxford University, for making her debut in the film adaptation of Shakespeare's Much Ado About Nothing. Throughout the 1990s, she worked on both film and television, most notably by portraying the title character in the 1996 BBC television series Emma. In 2001, Beckinsale garnered international recognition when she was cast as the romantic lead opposite Ben Affleck in her breakthrough film, Pearl Harbor (2001). Since then, she has portrayed a variety of characters in projects such as Underworld (2003), The Aviator (2004), and Van Helsing (2004). In 2008, she earned a Critic's Choice Award nomination for her performance in Nothing But the Truth. Born in Finsbury Park, London, Beckinsale is the daughter of actor Richard Beckinsale, who died from a heart attack in 1979, and actress Judy Loe. She has a paternal half-sister, Samantha, who is also an actress. Her paternal grandfather was half Burmese, and she has said that she was "very oriental-looking" as a child.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pTRtcZn9gWQZRiet36qWKh94urn.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://s.yimg.com/uu/api/res/1.2/1Hv1g45oam3ro8qdrSVtdg--~B/aD03MjA7dz0xMjgwO3NtPTE7YXBwaWQ9eXRhY2h5b24-/https://s.yimg.com/cd/resizer/2.0/FIT_TO_WIDTH-w1280/93231ce19c22abbc6344389a3c14d30eb2b15c0b.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Mayim Bialik</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/167640</tmdb>
  <summary>Mayim Bialik is an American actress and neuroscientist, known for her roles in Blossom and The Big Bang Theory.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uvTTKl7KOJciJHg24wJHsppRbnI.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.etonline.com/sites/default/files/images/2017-06/1280_mayimbialik_062917.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Jack Black</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/70851</tmdb>
  <summary>Thomas Jacob "Jack" Black (born August 28, 1969) is an American comedian, actor and musician.

    He makes up one half of the comedy and satirical rock duo Tenacious D. The group has two albums as well as a television series and a film. His acting career is extensive, starring primarily as bumbling, cocky, but internally self-conscious outsiders in comedy films. He was a member of the Frat Pack, a group of comedians who have appeared together in several Hollywood films, and has been nominated for a Golden Globe award. He has also won an MTV Movie Award, and a Nickelodeon Kids Choice Award.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Jack Black, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kAyKg3rYGgIhB5KRaIWALuf78W3.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/5_Jack-Black.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Jeff Bridges</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/1229</tmdb>
  <summary>American actor Jeff Bridges has starred in over 50 films during his lengthy career. He comes from a family of performers and was introduced to show business by his father Lloyd. Jeff is most famous for his work in the films Big Lebowski (1998), Seabiscuit (2003), Crazy Heart (2009), and most recently True Grit (2010). His accolades include a long list of Academy Award nominations, and one win for Best Actor in 2010.

    Bridges was born in 1949 and grew up in Los Angeles, California. After high school Jeff traveled to New York to study acting at the famous Herbert Berghof Studio. In the late 1960's Jeff served in the US Coast Guard, and stayed on reserve through the early 1970's to avoid Vietnam. As a child Jeff got a start in acting through his father Lloyd, and even starred in two of his television shows. Jeff achieved major success early in his career when he was nominated for an Academy Award in his first major film, the 1971 drama Last Picture Show. Three years later he starred opposite of Clint Eastwood in Thunderbolt and Lightfoot.

    By 1976 Bridges was casted in the first remake of King Kong, which turned out to be a huge commercial success raking in more than 90 million dollars. Over the next three decades Bridges went on to star in over 50 films and win countless awards for his work. More recently Jeff starred in the 2009 film Crazy Heart, which earned him his first Academy Award for Best Actor.

    In 1977 Jeff married Susan Geston, the two met while filming Ranch Deluxe. Together they have three daughters.

    Along with other entertainment industry leaders, in 1984 Bridges founded the End Hunger Network, a humanitarian effort which aims to eliminate childhood hunger in the US by 2015.

    Along with his charitable work, Jeff is also known for his music and photography.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eronr4zagxsKCBkGsFBDBCOqyma.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://images.everyeye.it/img-notizie/kingsman-the-golden-circle-jeff-bridges-nel-cast-v2-262811-1280x720.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Steve Buscemi</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/884</tmdb>
  <summary>Steven Vincent "Steve" Buscemi is an American actor, writer and film director. He was born in Brooklyn, New York, the son of Dorothy, who worked as a hostess at Howard Johnson's, and John Buscemi, a sanitation worker and Korean War veteran. Buscemi's father was Sicilian American and his mother Irish American. He has three brothers: Jon, Ken, and Michael. Buscemi was raised Roman Catholic.

    In April 2001, while shooting the film Domestic Disturbance in Wilmington, North Carolina, Buscemi was stabbed three times while intervening in a bar fight at Firebelly Lounge between his friend Vince Vaughn, screenwriter Scott Rosenberg and a local man, who allegedly instigated the brawl.

    Buscemi has one son, Lucian, with his wife Jo Andres.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7sDzFRScCv85usSwPG01BTac7UY.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/jvMbU9v5p2U/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Nicolas Cage</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/2963</tmdb>
  <summary>Nicolas Kim Coppola (born January 7, 1964), known professionally as Nicolas Cage, is an American actor, producer and director. He has performed in leading roles in a variety of films, ranging from romantic comedies and dramas to science fiction and action movies. Cage is known for his prolificacy, appearing in at least one film per year, nearly every year since 1980 (with the exception of 1985 and 1991).

    In the early years of his career, Cage starred in critically acclaimed films such as Valley Girl (1983), Racing with the Moon (1984), Birdy (1985), Peggy Sue Got Married (1986), Raising Arizona (1987), Moonstruck (1987), Vampire's Kiss (1989), Wild at Heart (1990), Honeymoon in Vegas (1992), and Red Rock West (1993). Cage received an Academy Award, a Golden Globe, and Screen Actors Guild Award for his performance as an alcoholic Hollywood writer in Leaving Las Vegas (1995) before coming to the attention of wider audiences with mainstream films such as The Rock (1996), Face/Off (1997), Con Air (1997), City of Angels (1998) and National Treasure (2004). He earned his second Academy Award nomination for his performance as Charlie and Donald Kaufman in Adaptation (2002). In 2002, he directed the film Sonny for which he was nominated for Grand Special Prize at Deauville Film Festival.

    Cage owns a production company, Saturn Films, and produced films such as Shadow of the Vampire (2000) and The Life of David Gale (2003).

    Though his performances in The Weather Man (2005), Lord of War (2005), The Bad Lieutenant: Port of Call New Orleans (2009), and Kick-Ass (2010) earned critical acclaim, and films such as Ghost Rider (2007) and Knowing (2009) were box office successes, Cage has been strongly criticized in recent years for his choice of roles, some of which have been universally panned. Most recently, he voiced the character of Grug in the animated film The Croods.

    He was born Nicolas Kim Coppola on January 7, 1964, in Long Beach, California, to parents August Floyd Coppola, a professor of literature, and Joy (Vogelsang), a dancer and choreographer. He was raised in a Catholic family. His father was of Italian descent and his mother is of German and Polish descent. His paternal grandparents were composer Carmine Coppola and actress Italia Pennino, and his paternal great-grandparents were immigrants from Bernalda, Basilicata, Italy. Through his father, Cage is the nephew of director Francis Ford Coppola and of actress Talia Shire, and the cousin of directors Roman Coppola and Sofia Coppola, film producer Gian-Carlo Coppola, and actors Robert Carmine and Jason Schwartzman. Cage's two brothers are New York radio personality Marc "The Cope" Coppola and director Christopher Coppola.

    He attended Beverly Hills High School, which is known for its many alumni who became entertainers. He aspired to act from an early age and also attended UCLA School of Theater, Film and Television. His first non-cinematic acting experience was in a school production of Golden Boy.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Nicolas Cage, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fW37Gbk5PJZuXvyZwtcr0cMwPKY.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.lifetimetv.co.uk/sites/default/files/Nicolas_Cage.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>John Candy</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/7180</tmdb>
  <summary>John Franklin Candy (October 31, 1950 – March 4, 1994) was a Canadian actor and comedian. He rose to fame as a member of the Toronto, Ontario branch of The Second City, its related Second City Television series, and in his role in comedy films such as Stripes, Splash, Cool Runnings, The Great Outdoors, and Uncle Buck. One of his most renowned onscreen performances was that of Del Griffith, the loquacious, on the move, shower curtain ring salesman in the John Hughes comedy Planes, Trains and Automobiles.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article John Candy, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/a53ilUnwQ4q7sM0F0h14dbunKA7.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/C4oFGEA4ejY/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>








<dir>
  <title>Michael Caine</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/3895</tmdb>
  <summary>Sir Michael Caine is an English film actor. He became known for several notable critically acclaimed performances, particularly in films such as Zulu (1964), The Italian Job (1969), Get Carter (1971), Educating Rita (1983) and more recently Batman Begins and The Dark Knight. Caine was knighted in 2000 by Queen Elizabeth II, in recognition of his contribution to cinema. Caine was born Maurice Joseph Micklewhite in Rotherhithe, South East London, the son of Ellen Frances Marie, a cook and charlady, and Maurice Joseph Micklewhite, a fish market porter. He was married to actress Patricia Haines from 1955 to 1958. They had one daughter named Dominique. He dated Bianca Jagger in 1968. Caine has been married to actress and model Shakira Baksh since 8 January 1973. They met after Caine saw her appearing in a Maxwell House coffee commercial and a friend gave him her telephone number. They have a daughter named Natasha.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vvj0JMSFpOajXCE46Hy4dyqSP2U.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://actorspeak.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/MichaelCaine-Quote1.jpg</fanart>
  <content>set</content>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Robert Carlyle</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/18023</tmdb>
  <summary>Robert Carlyle, OBE (born 14 April 1961) is a Scottish film and television actor. He is known for a variety of roles including those in Trainspotting, Hamish Macbeth, The Full Monty, The World Is Not Enough, Angela's Ashes, The 51st State, and 28 Weeks Later. He also portrayed Doctor Nicholas Rush in Stargate Universe.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dLNeFPfJACiCiUz3oEdAjeKIwvZ.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://cdn.playbuzz.com/cdn/d813502a-0f6e-4645-86eb-308c19af71a8/bbc68642-ec42-4b9c-acf8-7fb9f94ee9ea.jpeg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Jim Carrey</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/206</tmdb>
  <summary>James Eugene "Jim" Carrey is a Canadian-American actor, comedian, singer and writer. He has received two Golden Globe Awards and has also been nominated on four occasions.

    Carrey began stand-up comedy in 1979, performing at Yuk Yuk's in Toronto, Ontario. After gaining prominence in 1981, he began working at The Comedy Store in Los Angeles where he was soon noticed by comedian Rodney Dangerfield, who immediately signed him to open his tour performances.

    Carrey, long interested in film and television, developed a close friendship with comedian Damon Wayans, which landed him a role in the sketch comedy hit In Living Color, in which he portrayed various characters during the show's 1990 season. Having had little success in television movies and several low-budget films, Carrey was cast as the title character in Ace Ventura: Pet Detective which premiered in February, 1994, making more than $72 million domestically. The film spawned a sequel, Ace Ventura: When Nature Calls (1995), in which he reprised the role of Ventura.

    High profile roles followed when he was cast as Stanley Ipkiss in The Mask (1994) for which he gained a Golden Globe Award nomination for Best Actor in a Musical or Comedy, and as Lloyd Christmas in the comedy film Dumb and Dumber (1994). Between 1996 and 1999, Carrey continued his success after earning lead roles in several highly popular films including The Cable Guy (1996), Liar Liar (1997), in which he was nominated for another Golden Globe Award and in the critically acclaimed films The Truman Show and Man on the Moon, in 1998 and 1999, respectively. Both films earned Carrey Golden Globe awards. Since earning both awards — the only two in his three-decade career— Carrey continued to star in comedy films, including How the Grinch Stole Christmas (2000) where he played the title character, Bruce Almighty (2003) where he portrayed the role of unlucky TV reporter Bruce Nolan, Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events (2004), Fun with Dick and Jane (2005), Yes Man (2008), and A Christmas Carol (2009).

    Carrey has also taken on more serious roles including Joel Barish in Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind (2004) alongside Kate Winslet and Kirsten Dunst, which earned him another Golden Globe nomination, and Steven Jay Russell in I Love You Phillip Morris (2009) alongside Ewan McGregor.   Description above from the Wikipedia article Jim Carrey, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w640/5tVf0ow8MX4OwjmVoSa5v7qUDka.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://wallpaperscraft.com/image/jim_carrey_smile_sunglasses_actor_celebrity_charming_18677_1920x1080.jpg</fanart>
  <content>set</content>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Helena Bonham Carter</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/1283</tmdb>
  <summary>Helena Bonham Carter (born 26 May 1966) is an English actress of film, stage, and television. She made her film debut in K. M. Peyton's A Pattern of Roses before winning her first leading role as the titular character in Lady Jane. She is known for her roles in films such as A Room with a View, Fight Club, and the Harry Potter series, as well as for frequently collaborating with director Tim Burton, her domestic partner since 2001. Bonham Carter is a two-time Academy Award nominee for her performances in The Wings of the Dove and The King's Speech; her portrayal of Queen Elizabeth in the latter film garnering her a BAFTA Award in 2011.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Helena Bonham Carter, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rHZMwkumoRvhKV5ZvwBONKENAhG.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://hdwallsource.com/img/2016/1/monochrome-helena-bonham-carter-face-wallpaper-58014-59780-hd-wallpapers.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Jackie Chan</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/18897</tmdb>
  <summary>Jackie Chan, born Chan Kong-sang, is a Hong Kong actor, action choreographer, filmmaker, comedian, producer, martial artist, screenwriter, entrepreneur, singer and stunt performer. In his movies, he is known for his acrobatic fighting style, comic timing, use of improvised weapons, and innovative stunts. Jackie Chan has been acting since the 1970s and has appeared in over 100 films. Chan has received stars on the Hong Kong Avenue of Stars and the Hollywood Walk of Fame. As a cultural icon, Chan has been referenced in various pop songs, cartoons, and video games. Chan is also a Cantopop and Mandopop star, having released a number of albums and sung many of the theme songs for the films in which he has starred. Chan was born on April 7, 1954, in Victoria Peak, in the former Crown colony of Hong Kong, as Chan Kong-sang (meaning "born in Hong Kong") to Charles and Lee-Lee Chan, refugees from the Chinese Civil War. He was nicknamed Paopao (Chinese: 炮炮, literally meaning "Cannonball") because he was such a big baby, weighing 12 pounds, or about 5.4 kgs. Since his parents worked for the French Consul to Hong Kong, Chan spent his formative years within the grounds of the consul's residence in the Victoria Peak district. Chan attended the Nah-Hwa Primary School on Hong Kong Island, where he failed his first year, after which his parents withdrew him from the school. In 1960, his father immigrated to Canberra, Australia, to work as the head cook for the American embassy, and Chan was sent to the China Drama Academy, a Peking Opera School run by Master Yu Jim-yuen. Chan trained rigorously for the next decade, excelling in martial arts and acrobatics. He eventually became part of the Seven Little Fortunes, a performance group made up of the school's best students, gaining the stage name Yuen Lo in homage to his master. Chan became close friends with fellow group members Sammo Hung and Yuen Biao, the three of them later to be known as the Three Brothers or Three Dragons. At the age of 17, he worked as a stuntman in the Bruce Lee films Fist of Fury and Enter the Dragon under the stage name Chan Yuen Lung. He received his first starring role later that year, in Little Tiger of Canton, which had a limited release in Hong Kong in 1973.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pmKJ4sGvPQ3imzXaFnjW4Vk5Gyc.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://wallpaperscraft.com/image/jackie_chan_actor_smile_glasses_108295_1920x1080.jpg</fanart>
  <content>set</content>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Emilia Clarke</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/1223786</tmdb>
  <summary>Emilia Isabelle Euphemia Rose Clarke (born 23 October 1986) is an English actress.

    Clarke rose to prominence in 2011 for her breakthrough role as Daenerys Targaryen in the HBO series Game of Thrones, a performance that has gained her both critical and popular acclaim. In 2017, Clarke became one of the highest paid actors on television for earnings of £2 million per episode of Game of Thrones.

    Clarke made her Broadway debut as Holly Golightly in a production of Breakfast at Tiffany's in March 2013. In 2015, she was named Esquire's Sexiest Woman Alive. She is also known for her starring roles as Sarah Connor in the science fiction film Terminator Genisys (2015) and as Louisa Clark in the romance film Me Before You (2016). In November 2016 she was cast as the female lead in the upcoming Star Wars Han Solo anthology film.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Emilia Clarke, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/j7d083zIMhwnKro3tQqDz2Fq1UD.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://hdwallsource.com/img/2014/6/beautiful-emilia-clarke-wallpaper-40161-41097-hd-wallpapers.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Misha Collins</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/42747</tmdb>
	<summary>Misha Collins (born Misha Dmitri Tippens Krushnic August 20, 1974) is an American actor and producer. He is best known for his role as the angel Castiel on the CW television series Supernatural.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2zT9VQwJgi54N7FMf4QJ2qogJec.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://wallpapersboom.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/4169_misha_collins.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Billy Connolly </title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/9188</tmdb>
	<summary>William "Billy" Connolly, Jr., CBE (born 24 November 1942) is a Scottish comedian, musician, presenter and actor. He is sometimes known, especially in his native Scotland, by the nickname The Big Yin (The Big One).His first trade, in the early 1960s, was as a welder (specifically a boilermaker) in the Glasgow shipyards, but he gave it up towards the end of the decade to pursue a career as a folk singer in the Humblebums and subsequently as a soloist. In the early 1970s he made the transition from folk-singer with a comedic persona to fully-fledged comedian, a role in which he continues. He also became an actor, and has appeared in such films as Indecent Proposal (1993); Mrs. Brown (1997), for which he was nominated for a BAFTA; The Boondock Saints (1999); The Man Who Sued God (2001); Water (1985);The Last Samurai (2003); Timeline (2003); Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events (2004); Garfield: A Tail of Two Kitties (2006); and The X-Files: I Want to Believe (2008). Connolly reprised his role as Noah "Il Duce" MacManus in Boondock Saints II: All Saints Day. Connolly appears as the King of Lilliput in the 2010 remake of Gulliver′s Travels.
  </summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7e1rVdJah2r0DaMpovrhbR2dHPS.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart></fanart>
</dir>



<dir>
  <title>Robbie Coltrane</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/1923</tmdb>
  <summary>Robbie Coltrane, is a Scottish actor, comedian and author. He is known both for his role as Dr Eddie "Fitz" Fitzgerald in the British TV series Cracker and as Rubeus Hagrid in the Harry Potter films.

    Coltrane was born Anthony Robert McMillan in Rutherglen, South Lanarkshire, the son of Jean McMillan Ross, a teacher and pianist, and Ian Baxter McMillan, a general practitioner who also served as a forensic police surgeon. He has an older sister, Annie, and a late younger sister, Jane.

    Coltrane moved into acting in his early twenties, taking the stage name Coltrane (in tribute to jazz saxophonist John Coltrane) and working in theatre and stand-up comedy. Coltrane soon moved into films, obtaining roles in a number of movies such as Flash Gordon. On television, he also appeared as Samuel Johnson in Blackadder.

    His roles went from strength to strength in the 1990s with the TV series Cracker and a BAFTA award as the stepping stone to parts in bigger films such as the James Bond films GoldenEye and The World Is Not Enough and a major supporting role as half-giant Rubeus Hagrid in the Harry Potter films.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/u07QKPs7wvXxzjXi1UUBSGjjmQm.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2QLkRsBa2fGCebhFinKorOSl70D.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Billy Connolly</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/9188</tmdb>
  <summary>William "Billy" Connolly, Jr., CBE (born 24 November 1942) is a Scottish comedian, musician, presenter and actor. He is sometimes known, especially in his native Scotland, by the nickname The Big Yin (The Big One).His first trade, in the early 1960s, was as a welder (specifically a boilermaker) in the Glasgow shipyards, but he gave it up towards the end of the decade to pursue a career as a folk singer in the Humblebums and subsequently as a soloist. In the early 1970s he made the transition from folk-singer with a comedic persona to fully-fledged comedian, a role in which he continues. He also became an actor, and has appeared in such films as Indecent Proposal (1993); Mrs. Brown (1997), for which he was nominated for a BAFTA; The Boondock Saints (1999); The Man Who Sued God (2001); Water (1985);The Last Samurai (2003); Timeline (2003); Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events (2004); Garfield: A Tail of Two Kitties (2006); and The X-Files: I Want to Believe (2008). Connolly reprised his role as Noah "Il Duce" MacManus in Boondock Saints II: All Saints Day. Connolly appears as the King of Lilliput in the 2010 remake of Gulliver′s Travels.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Billy Connolly , licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7e1rVdJah2r0DaMpovrhbR2dHPS.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.mulierchile.com/billy-connolly/billy-connolly-002.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Terry Crews</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/53256</tmdb>
  <summary>Terrence Alan "Terry" Crews is an American actor, comedian, voice artist former player in the National Football League. He is perhaps best known for his role as family patriarch Julius on the UPN/CW sitcom Everybody Hates Chris. Currently, he stars in the TBS sitcom Are We There Yet? as Nick Kingston-Persons. Additionally, he stars in the BET reality series The Family Crews, and has appeared in such films as The 6th Day, Friday After Next, White Chicks, Idiocracy and The Expendables. In 2010, Crews was featured in several Old Spice TV commercials for their "Odor Blocker Body Wash", directed by Tim Heidecker and Eric Wareheim.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Terry Crews, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/p2JIlYNwjC5ASfmVXvy30DVzXyG.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.etonline.com/sites/default/files/images/2017-11/terry_crews_474270929.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Benedict Cumberbatch </title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/71580</tmdb>
  <summary>Benedict Timothy Carlton Cumberbatch (born 19 July 1976) is an English film, television, and theatre actor. His most acclaimed roles include: Stephen Hawking in the BBC drama "Hawking" (2004); William Pitt in the historical film "Amazing Grace" (2006); the protagonist Stephen Ezard in the miniseries thriller "The Last Enemy" (2008); Paul Marshall in "Atonement" (2007); Bernard in "Small Island" (2009); and Sherlock Holmes in the modern BBC adaptation series "Sherlock" (2010).

    He is the son of actors Timothy Carlton (Timothy Carlton Congdon Cumberbatch) and Wanda Ventham.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wz3MRiMmoz6b5X3oSzMRC9nLxY1.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://wallpaperscraft.com/image/benedict_cumberbatch_actor_celebrity_library_97365_1920x1080.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Kaley Cuoco</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/53862</tmdb>
  <summary>Kaley Cuoco is an American film and television actress and singer. She is best known for her roles as Bridget Hennessy on the sitcom 8 Simple Rules, Billie Jenkins on the supernatural drama Charmed, and Penny on the sitcom The Big Bang Theory.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yyPwB7LyGBc2FBRripcngOo3yuD.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.etonline.com/sites/default/files/images/2016-05/1280_kaley_cuoco_051016.jpg</fanart>
</dir>



<dir>
  <title>Jamie Lee Curtis</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/8944</tmdb>
  <summary>Jamie Lee Curtis (born November 22, 1958) is an American actress and author. Although she was initially known as a "scream queen" because of her starring roles in several horror films early in her career, such as Halloween, The Fog, Prom Night and Terror Train, Curtis has since compiled a body of work that spans many genres. Her 1998 book, Today I Feel Silly, and Other Moods That Make My Day, made the best-seller list in The New York Times. Curtis has appeared in advertisements for Activia since 2007, and is a blogger for The Huffington Post online newspaper. She is married to actor, screenwriter, and director Christopher Guest.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Jamie Lee Curtis, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w440_and_h660_bestv2/c4poMDwQ0nUj81m4WPriiv96ExZ.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://img.etonline.com/1242911076001/201610/349/1242911076001_5173405614001_et-jamieleecurtis-101616-hulu.jpg?pubId=1242911076001</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Willem Dafoe</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/5293</tmdb>
  <summary>Willem Dafoe (born July 22, 1955) is an American film, stage, and voice actor, and a founding member of the experimental theatre company The Wooster Group. He has had roles in a wide range of films, including Streets of Fire, To Live and Die in L.A., Platoon, Born on the Fourth of July, The English Patient, The Last Temptation of Christ, Mississippi Burning, Wild at Heart, The Boondock Saints, Inside Man, The Life Aquatic with Steve Zissou, Spider-Man, Shadow of the Vampire, The Aviator, American Psycho, Antichrist, and voice roles in Fantastic Mr. Fox and Finding Nemo.

    Dafoe has been nominated for the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor twice. The first was for his role in Platoon in 1986 and the second time for his performance in Shadow of the Vampire in 2000.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Willem Dafoe, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xM5lhOR5tWWdIlFpBDeZJx9opIP.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://geekireland.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/08/Willem-Dafoe-Death-Note.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Leonardo DiCaprio</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/6193</tmdb>
  <summary>Leonardo DiCaprio is an American actor and film producer.

    He began his film career by starring as Josh in Critters 3 before starring in the film adaptation of the memoir This Boy's Life (1993) alongside Robert De Niro. DiCaprio was praised for his supporting role in the drama What's Eating Gilbert Grape (1993), and gained public recognition with leading roles in the drama The Basketball Diaries (1995) and the romantic drama Romeo + Juliet (1996), before achieving international fame with James Cameron's epic romance Titanic (1997) He has been nominated for six Academy Awards—five for acting and one for producing—and in 2016, he won the Academy Award for Best Actor for The Revenant.

    DiCaprio is the founder of his own production company, named Appian Way Productions. He is also a committed environmentalist.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/A85WIRIKVsD2DeUSc8wQ4fOKc4e.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://www.much.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/leonardo-dicaprio-1280-720.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Judi Dench</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/5309</tmdb>
  <summary>Dame Judith Olivia "Judi" Dench, CH, DBE, FRSA (born 9 December 1934) is an English film, stage and television actress.

    Dench made her professional debut in 1957 with the Old Vic Company. Over the following few years she played in several of William Shakespeare's plays in such roles as Ophelia in Hamlet, Juliet in Romeo and Juliet and Lady Macbeth in Macbeth. She branched into film work, and won a BAFTA Award as Most Promising Newcomer; however, most of her work during this period was in theatre. Not generally known as a singer, she drew strong reviews for her leading role in the musical Cabaret in 1968.

    During the next two decades, she established herself as one of the most significant British theatre performers, working for the National Theatre Company and the Royal Shakespeare Company. In television, she achieved success during this period, in the series A Fine Romance from 1981 until 1984 and in 1992 began a continuing role in the television romantic comedy series As Time Goes By.

    Her film appearances were infrequent until she was cast as M in GoldenEye (1995), a role she has played in each James Bond film since. She received several notable film awards for her role as Queen Victoria in Mrs. Brown (1997), and has since been acclaimed for her work in such films as Shakespeare in Love (1998), Chocolat (2000), Iris (2001), Mrs Henderson Presents (2005) and Notes on a Scandal (2006), and the television production The Last of the Blonde Bombshells (2001).

    Regarded by critics as one of the greatest actresses of the post-war period, and frequently named as the leading British actress in polls, Dench has received many award nominations for her acting in theatre, film and television; her awards include ten BAFTAs, seven Laurence Olivier Awards, two Screen Actors Guild Awards, two Golden Globes, an Academy Award, and a Tony Award.

    She was married to actor Michael Williams from 1971 until his death in 2001. They are the parents of actress Finty Williams.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Judi Dench, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2is9RvJ3BQAku2EtCmyk5EZoxzT.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://static.dnaindia.com/sites/default/files/styles/full/public/2015/01/28/305558-judi-dench-getty.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Johnny Depp</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/85</tmdb>
  <summary>John Christopher "Johnny" Depp II (born June 9, 1963) is an American actor and musician. He has won the Golden Globe Award and Screen Actors Guild award for Best Actor.

    Depp rose to prominence on the 1980s television series 21 Jump Street, becoming a teen idol. Turning to film, he played the title character of Edward Scissorhands (1990), and later found box office success in films such as Sleepy Hollow (1999), Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl (2003), Charlie and the Chocolate Factory (2005), and Rango (2011). He has collaborated with director and friend Tim Burton in seven films, including Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street (2007) and Alice in Wonderland (2010). Depp has gained acclaim for his portrayals of people such as Edward D. Wood, Jr., in Ed Wood, Joseph D. Pistone in Donnie Brasco, Hunter S. Thompson in Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas, George Jung in Blow, and the bank robber John Dillinger in Michael Mann's Public Enemies.

    Films featuring Depp have grossed over $2.6 billion at the United States box office and over $6 billion worldwide. He has been nominated for top awards many times, winning the Best Actor Awards from the Golden Globes for Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street and from the Screen Actors Guild for Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl. He also has garnered a sex symbol status in American cinema, being twice named as the Sexiest man alive by People magazine in 2003 and 2009.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Johnny Depp, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ea4fTp9T8Zy2KWxyFsqDIBgHZmb.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://wallpaperscraft.com/image/johnny_depp_eyeglasses_eyes_smile_60961_1280x720.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Peter Dinklage</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/22970</tmdb>
  <summary>Peter Dinklage (born June 11, 1969) is an American film, television and theater actor. Since his breakout role in the 2003 film The Station Agent, he has acted in Elf, Underdog, Find Me Guilty, the 2007 Death at a Funeral film and the 2010 remake, and The Chronicles of Narnia: Prince Caspian. Since 2011 he has starred in the HBO series Game of Thrones, based on George R.R. Martin's series of novels A Song of Ice and Fire.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Peter Dinklage, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8Z7cq5pUkz8FtpzOBsd0tgZPoO6.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://wallpapersdsc.net/wp-content/uploads/2016/10/Peter-Dinklage-Computer-Wallpaper.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Robert Duvall</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/3087</tmdb>
  <summary>Robert Selden Duvall (born January 5, 1931) is an American actor and director. He has won an Academy Award, two Emmy Awards, and four Golden Globe Awards over the course of his career. Duvall has been in some of the most acclaimed and popular films of all time, among them To Kill a Mockingbird, The Godfather, The Godfather Part II, MASH, Network, True Grit, Bullitt, The Conversation, Apocalypse Now, Tender Mercies, The Natural and Lonesome Dove. He began appearing in theatre during the late 1950s, moving into small, supporting television and film roles during the early 1960s in such works as To Kill a Mockingbird (1962) (as Boo Radley) and Captain Newman, M.D. (1963). He started to land much larger roles during the early 1970s with movies like MASH (1970) (as Major Burns) and THX 1138 (1971). This was followed by a series of critical successes: The Godfather (1972), The Godfather Part II (1974), Network (1976), The Great Santini (1979), Apocalypse Now (1979), and True Confessions (1981). Since then Duvall has continued to act in both film and television with such productions as Tender Mercies (1983) (for which he won an Academy Award, The Natural (1984), Colors (1988), the television mini-series Lonesome Dove (1989), Stalin (1992), The Man Who Captured Eichmann (1996), A Family Thing (1996), The Apostle (1997) (which he also wrote and directed), A Civil Action (1998), Gods and Generals (2003), Broken Trail (2006) and Get Low (2010).

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Robert Duvall, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1aBC7NxPy10ofng6HsJBecJ1vMZ.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.lifetimetv.co.uk/sites/default/files/Robert_Duvall.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Clint Eastwood</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/190</tmdb>
  <summary>Clinton "Clint" Eastwood, Jr. (born May 31, 1930) is an American film actor, director, producer, composer and politician. Following his breakthrough role on the TV series Rawhide (1959–65), Eastwood starred as the Man with No Name in Sergio Leone's Dollars Trilogy of spaghetti westerns (A Fistful of Dollars, For a Few Dollars More, and The Good, the Bad and the Ugly) in the 1960s, and as San Francisco Police Department Inspector Harry Callahan in the Dirty Harry films (Dirty Harry, Magnum Force, The Enforcer, Sudden Impact, and The Dead Pool) during the 1970s and 1980s. These roles, along with several others in which he plays tough-talking no-nonsense police officers, have made him an enduring cultural icon of masculinity. Eastwood won Academy Awards for Best Director and Producer of the Best Picture, as well as receiving nominations for Best Actor, for his work in the films Unforgiven (1992) and Million Dollar Baby (2004). These films in particular, as well as others including Play Misty for Me (1971), The Outlaw Josey Wales (1976), Pale Rider (1985), In the Line of Fire (1993), The Bridges of Madison County (1995), and Gran Torino (2008), have all received commercial success and/or critical acclaim. Eastwood's only comedies have been Every Which Way but Loose (1978) and its sequel Any Which Way You Can (1980); despite being widely panned by critics they are the two highest-grossing films of his career after adjusting for inflation. Eastwood has directed most of his own star vehicles, but he has also directed films in which he did not appear such as Mystic River (2003) and Letters from Iwo Jima (2006), for which he received Academy Award nominations and Changeling (2008), which received Golden Globe Award nominations. He has received considerable critical praise in France in particular, including for several of his films which were panned in the United States, and was awarded two of France's highest honors: in 1994 he received the Ordre des Arts et des Lettres medal and in 2007 was awarded the Légion d'honneur medal. In 2000 he was awarded the Italian Venice Film Festival Golden Lion for lifetime achievement. Since 1967 Eastwood has run his own production company, Malpaso, which has produced the vast majority of his films. He also served as the nonpartisan mayor of Carmel-by-the-Sea, California, from 1986 to 1988. Eastwood has seven children by five women, although he has only married twice. An audiophile, Eastwood is also associated with jazz and has composed and performed pieces in several films along with his eldest son, Kyle Eastwood. Description above from the Wikipedia article Clint Eastwood, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bfHv9PvpGDaCyFrce1pMvyDRTWM.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://wallpapersdsc.net/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Clint-Eastwood-Widescreen.png</fanart>
  <content>set</content>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Sam Elliott </title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/16431</tmdb>
  <summary>Samuel Pack "Sam" Elliott (born August 9, 1944) is an American actor.

His rangy physique, thick horseshoe moustache, and deep, resonant voice (with a Western twang/drawl) match the iconic image of a cowboy or rancher, and he has often been cast in such roles.
</summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w440_and_h660_bestv2/f2AxZZ6d0Cit0tmf6wYTHcGfwT9.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://media3.s-nbcnews.com/i/MSNBC/Components/Video/201706/2017-06-08T14-15-37-5Z--1280x720.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Emilio Estévez</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/2880</tmdb>
  <summary>Emilio Estévez (born May 12, 1962) is an American actor, film director, and writer. He started his career as an actor and is well-known for being a member of the acting Brat Pack of the 1980s, starring in The Breakfast Club and St. Elmo's Fire. He is also known for Repo Man, The Mighty Ducks and its sequels, Maximum Overdrive, Bobby (which he also wrote and directed), and his performances in Western films such as Young Guns and its sequel. One of his first appearances was as "Two-Bit" in The Outsiders.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Emilio Estevez, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2NSM4zFrw3i16UYdUhfETVjqC4I.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.pinimg.com/originals/ca/37/a6/ca37a61f96cb02584b2bc25185d95cbf.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Colin Farrell</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/72466</tmdb>
  <summary>Colin James Farrell (born 31 May 1976) is an Irish actor, who has appeared in films including Tigerland, Daredevil, Miami Vice, Minority Report, Phone Booth, The Recruit, Alexander, S.W.A.T., and In Bruges.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pgMM9r5ll99RXSmz1J4sj8zaddW.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.classywallpapers.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/Colin-Farrell-1.jpg</fanart>
</dir>



<dir>
  <title>Sally Field</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/35</tmdb>
  <summary>Sally Margaret Field (born November 6, 1946) is an American actress, singer, producer, director, and screenwriter. In each decade of her career, she has been known for major roles in American TV/film culture, including: in the 1960s, for Gidget (1965–66) or Sister Bertrille on The Flying Nun (1967–70); in the 1970s, for Sybil (1976), Smokey and the Bandit (1977) and Norma Rae (1979); in the 1980s, for Absence of Malice, Places in the Heart (1984) and Steel Magnolias; in the 1990s, for Not Without My Daughter, Mrs. Doubtfire (1993) and Forrest Gump; and in the 2000s, on the TV shows ER and Brothers & Sisters. She has also performed in numerous other roles. Field has won two Academy Awards, for Norma Rae (1979) and Places in the Heart (1984). She has also won three Emmy Awards: for her role in the TV film Sybil (1976); her guest-starring role on ER in 2000; and for her starring role as Nora Holden Walker on ABC's series Brothers & Sisters in 2007. She has also won two Golden Globes and the Screen Actors Guild Award for Best Actress. She also won the Best Female Performance Prize at the Cannes Film Festival, for Norma Rae (1979).

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Sally  Field, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ymhpsxujOO3a9qaGYSpkenCt9Le.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zz12ILv9zwT4JiMTUcJDsMLIhKf.jpg</fanart>
</dir>
<dir>
  <title>Colin Firth</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/5472</tmdb>
  <summary>Colin Andrew Firth (born 10 September 1960) is an English film, television, and stage actor. Firth gained wide public attention in the 1990s for his portrayal of Mr. Darcy in the 1995 television adaptation of Jane Austen's Pride and Prejudice. In 2011, Firth received the Academy Award for Best Actor for his portrayal of King George VI in The King's Speech, a performance that also earned him the Golden Globe, BAFTA, and Screen Actors Guild Award for Best Actor. The previous year he received his first Academy Award nomination for his leading role in A Single Man, a performance that won him a BAFTA Award. Firth's other major film credits include The English Patient, Shakespeare in Love, Bridget Jones's Diary, Mamma Mia! and Love Actually. He received a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame in 2011.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4pj31PUxqpuJZrHChinub4gr2ul.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://timedotcom.files.wordpress.com/2014/04/colin_firth_prideprejudice_new1280.png</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Noel Fisher</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/80352</tmdb>
  <summary>Noel Fisher (born March 13, 1984) is a Canadian actor. He appeared on the television show X-Men: Evolution and starred in the Disney film Max Keeble's Big Move as the school bully. His past television roles include playing Patricia Arquette's son in the Medium episode Sweet Child o' Mine and is a regular on the Vancouver based show "Godiva's", as TJ. He was also featured in the FX show The Riches, as Cael Malloy. He played Teddy Parker, a soldier who was killed while serving with FBI Agent Seely Booth (David Boreanaz) in the military, on the TV series Bones. Most recently he played CSU Technician Dale Stuckey in the tenth season of Law & Order: Special Victims Unit. He has starred with Hilary Duff twice: the 2009 Law & Order: Special Victims Unit episode "Selfish", and also the film Agent Cody Banks. He also starred in the miniseries The Pacific as he played private Hamm in the battle of Okinawa.

Most recently, he has portrayed Mickey Milkovich on the series Shameless on Showtime, and also portrayed USMC Private First Class Shaun Lenihan in the 2011 film Battle: Los Angeles.

</summary>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/57rdFE8AZnhWhwH28QXpeXFhUgB.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart></fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Dan Fogler</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/58873</tmdb>
  <summary>Daniel Kevin "Dan" Fogler (born October 20, 1976) is an American actor, playwright, and filmmaker.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Dan Fogler, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zDyEudTLeT5SLXXKaKmYliAn26R.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2013/10/14/movies/video-free-birds-dan-fogler-on-the-story/video-free-birds-dan-fogler-on-the-story-superJumbo.jpg</fanart>
</dir>



<dir>
  <title>Harrison Ford</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/3</tmdb>
  <summary>Legendary Hollywood Icon Harrison Ford was born on July 13, 1942 in Chicago, Illinois.  His family history includes a strong lineage of actors, radio personalities, and models.  Harrison attended public high school in Park Ridge, Illinois where he was a member of the school Radio Station WMTH. Harrison worked as the lead voice for sports reporting at WMTH for several years.  Acting wasn’t a major interest to Ford until his junior year at Ripon College when he first took an acting class. Harrison Ford’s career started in 1964 when he travelled to California in search of a voice-over job. He never received that position, but instead signed a contract with Columbia Pictures where he earned $150 weekly to play small fill in roles in various films.  Through the 60’s Harrison worked on several TV shows including Gunsmoke, Ironside, Kung Fu, and American Style.  It wasn’t until 1967 that Harrison received his first credited role in the Western film, A Time for Killing. Dissatisfied with the meager roles he was being offered, Ford took a hiatus from acting to work as a self-employed carpenter. This seemingly odd diversion turned out to be a blessing in disguise for Harrison’s acting career when he was soon hired by famous film producer George Lucas.  This was a turning point in Harrison’s life that led to him be casted in milestone roles such as Hans Solo and Indiana Jones.  Since his most famous roles in the Star Wars Trilogy and Raiders of the Lost Ark, Harrison Ford has starred in over 40 films.  Many criticize his recent work, saying his performances have been lackluster leading to commercially disappointing films. Harrison has always worked hard to protect his off-screen private life, keeping details about his children and marriages quite.  He has a total of five children including one recent adoption with third and current wife Calista Flockhart. In addition to acting Harrison Ford is passionate about environmental conservation, aviation, and archeology.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7LOTdRfHU1H1qHBxpUv3jT04eWB.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://wallpapersdsc.net/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Harrison-Ford-Computer-Wallpaper.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Jodie Foster</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/1038</tmdb>
  <summary>Alicia Christian "Jodie" Foster (born November 19, 1962) is an American actress, film director, producer as well as being a former child actress.

    Foster began acting in commercials at three years of age, and her first significant role came in the 1976 film Taxi Driver as the preteen prostitute Iris for which she received a nomination for the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress. Also that year, she starred in the cult film The Little Girl Who Lives Down the Lane. She won an Academy Award for Best Actress in 1989 for playing a rape survivor in The Accused. In 1991, she starred in The Silence of the Lambs as Clarice Starling, a gifted FBI trainee, assisting in a hunt for a serial killer. This performance received international acclaim and her second Academy Award for Best Actress. She received her fourth Academy Award nomination for playing a hermit in Nell (1994). Other popular films include Maverick (1994), Contact (1997), Panic Room (2002), Flightplan (2005), Inside Man (2006), The Brave One (2007), and Nim's Island (2008).

    Foster's films have spanned a wide variety of genres, from family films to horror. In addition to her two Academy Awards she has won two BAFTA Awards for three films, two Golden Globe Awards, a Screen Actors Guild Award, a People's Choice Award, and has received two Emmy nominations.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Jodie Foster, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eAIE6bnOQ8rm0f933gyeAQdIwrP.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://images.everyeye.it/img-notizie/jodie-foster-convinta-che-film-ad-alto-budget-stiano-rovinando-hollywood-v3-316279-1280x720.jpg</fanart>
</dir>
<dir>
  <title>Martin Freeman</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/7060</tmdb>
  <summary>Martin Freeman is a British film and television actor, best known for playing the role of Tim Canterbury in the British television show "The Office", and as lead character Bilbo Baggins in the feature film universe of "The Hobbit".
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ashlWz2KDQTbo8NPUbVOwcB3zXJ.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://hdwallsource.com/img/2017/3/martin-freeman-desktop-wallpaper-59137-60920-hd-wallpapers.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Josh Gad</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/54415</tmdb>
  <summary>Joshua Gad (born February 23, 1981) is an American film, television and stage actor who was in the short-lived television series Back to You in the role of Ryan Church. The show premiered in September 2007 co-starring Patricia Heaton and Kelsey Grammer. Gad has also appeared in episodes of ER and Numb3rs. His film appearances include The Rocker, Crossing Over, 21, and Razortooth. He appeared on Broadway in the role of William Barfeé in The 25th Annual Putnam County Spelling Bee and as Elder Cunningham in The Book of Mormon.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Josh Gad, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6ctni3kK4lPteBAInd7kKZyCdZD.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://img.etonline.com/1242911076001/201610/2411/1242911076001_5174439321001_et-joshgad-101716-hulu.jpg?pubId=1242911076001</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Johnny Galecki</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/16478</tmdb>
  <summary>Johnny Galecki is a Belgian-born American actor, best known for his roles as David Healy in Roseanne, Rusty Griswold in National Lampoon's Christmas Vacation, and as Leonard Hofstadter in The Big Bang Theory.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iY3e0Zw5lygRO4BXbhcSxMcPEb9.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/VRMFvKc9Npg/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Mel Gibson</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/2461</tmdb>
  <summary>Mel Colm-Cille Gerard Gibson, AO (born January 3, 1956) is an actor, film director, producer and screenwriter. Born in Peekskill, New York, Gibson moved with his parents to Sydney, Australia when he was 12 years old and later studied acting at the Australian National Institute of Dramatic Art. After appearing in the Mad Max and Lethal Weapon series, Gibson went on to direct and star in the Academy Award-winning Braveheart. In 2004, he directed and produced The Passion of the Christ, a controversial, yet successful, film portraying the last hours in the life of Jesus Christ. Outside his career, remarks by Gibson have generated accusations of homophobia, antisemitism, racism, and misogyny; he has previously attributed the statements to his alcoholism.

    Description from Wikipedia
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6VGgL0bBvPIJ9vDOyyGf5nK2zL4.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://cdn.newsapi.com.au/image/v1/d0fa05597ce30e77583cd9a9b8303779</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>John Goodman</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/1230</tmdb>
  <summary>John Goodman is most famous for his role on the television series Roseanne. He is also a well known film and stage actor. Goodman comes from Affton, Missouri where he showed an early interest in film. A football scholarship took John to Southwest Missouri State University where he continued his acting education. A college injury ended his football dreams, so Goodman moved to Manhattan in pursuit of an acting career. He eventually performed on Broadway and appeared in several commercials.

    By the early 1980's John started landing small movie roles, including Eddie Macon's Run, and The Survivors (both in 1984). In 1990 Arachnophobia earned John a nomination for a Saturn Award for Best Supporting Actor. John then starred in the hugely popular 1998 film, The Big Lebowski which lead to a repeat nomination for Best Supporting Actor. Despite his moderate film success, Goodman is most widely know for playing Dan Conner on the TV sitcom Roseanne. Between 1988 and 1997, 221 episodes of Roseanne were filmed and John received numerous awards for his performance.

    Goodman met his wife, Annabeth Hartzog, while filming Everybody's All-American (1988). The two were married in October 1989, and had daughter Molly in 1990. John admits once having a long-time alcohol problem, but has reportedly been clean since 2007.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eOIx8zj1vYIRhVY2bK5cjIQfua0.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/RsO1Qonw-ko/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Whoopi Goldberg</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/2395</tmdb>
  <summary>Whoopi Goldberg (born Caryn Elaine Johnson, November 13, 1955) is an American comedian, actress, singer-songwriter, political activist, and talk show host. Goldberg made her film debut in The Color Purple (1985) playing Celie, a mistreated black woman in the Deep South. She received a nomination for the Academy Award for Best Actress and won her first Golden Globe Award for her role in the film. In 1990, she starred as Oda Mae Brown, a psychic helping a slain man (Patrick Swayze) find his killer in the blockbuster film Ghost. This performance won her a second Golden Globe and an Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress. Notable later films include Sister Act and Sister Act 2, The Lion King, Made in America, How Stella Got Her Groove Back, Girl, Interrupted and Rat Race. She is also acclaimed for her roles as the bartender Guinan in Star Trek: The Next Generation and as Terry Dolittle in Jumpin' Jack Flash. Her latest role is the voice of Stretch in Toy Story 3. Goldberg has been nominated for 13 Emmy Awards for her work in television. She was co-producer of the popular game show Hollywood Squares from 1998 to 2004. She has been the moderator of the daytime talk show The View since 2007. Goldberg has a Grammy, two Emmys, two Golden Globes, a Tony, and an Oscar. In addition, Goldberg has a British Academy Film Award, four People's Choice Awards and has been honored with a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame and is one of the few entertainers who have won an Oscar, Emmy, Grammy, and Tony Award.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/n3lF8w4X4rDa4J2LMDIxMEcuUeH.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/WDUKIq-OH-Y/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Jeff Goldblum</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/4785</tmdb>
  <summary>Jeffrey Lynn "Jeff" Goldblum (born October 22, 1952) is an American actor. His career began in the mid-1970s and he has appeared in major box-office successes including The Fly, Jurassic Park and its sequel Jurassic Park: The Lost World, and Independence Day. He starred as Detective Zach Nichols for the eighth and ninth seasons of the USA Network's crime drama series Law & Order: Criminal Intent.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/l99OMsc3glaWMNk1b5hxtawQSyn.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/S4ILIJvuxJU/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Seth Green</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/13922</tmdb>
  <summary>Seth Benjamin Gesshel-Green (born February 8, 1974) is an American actor, comedian, voice actor, and television producer. He is well known for his role as Daniel "Oz" Osbourne in Buffy the Vampire Slayer, as well as Dr. Evil's son Scott in the Austin Powers series of comedy films and Mitch Miller in That '70s Show. He also voices the characters of Chris Griffin on Family Guy, Lieutenant Gibbs in Titan Maximum, Jeff "Joker" Moreau in the Mass Effect video game series, and is one of the creators and producers of the stop motion comedy series Robot Chicken, in which he also voices many characters. Green has appeared in many other movies, such as Rat Race, The Italian Job, Can't Hardly Wait, Without a Paddle, and as a child in the horror film Stephen King's It.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Seth Green, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7ksgEtZZIhSkJmt7zMyVDOQfdxu.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.pinimg.com/originals/09/36/f3/0936f353dd219127fe19f26b3a4ce086.jpg</fanart>
</dir>
<dir>
  <title>Tom Hanks</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/31</tmdb>
  <summary>
    Thomas Jeffrey "Tom" Hanks (born July 9, 1956) is an American actor, producer, writer and director. Hanks worked in television and family-friendly comedies, gaining wide notice in 1988's Big, before achieving success as a dramatic actor in several notable roles, including Andrew Beckett in Philadelphia, the title role in Forrest Gump, Commander James A. Lovell in Apollo 13, Captain John H. Miller in Saving Private Ryan, Joe Fox in You've Got Mail and Chuck Noland in Cast Away. Hanks won consecutive Best Actor Academy Awards, in 1993 for Philadelphia and in 1994 for Forrest Gump. U.S. domestic box office totals for his films exceed $3.9 billion.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xxPMucou2wRDxLrud8i2D4dsywh.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://sharedmedia.grahamdigital.com/photo/2016/04/06/Tom%20Hanks_37694184_8347006_ver1.0_1280_720.jpg</fanart>
</dir>
<dir>
  <title>Tom Hardy</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/2524</tmdb>
  <summary>Edward Thomas "Tom" Hardy (born 15 September 1977) is an English actor. He is best known for playing the title character in the 2009 British film Bronson, and for his roles in the films Star Trek Nemesis, RocknRolla, and Inception. He has been cast in the Christopher Nolan film The Dark Knight Rises as Bane. Description above from the Wikipedia Tom Hardy, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4CR1D9VLWZcmGgh4b6kKuY2NOel.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://wallpapercave.com/wp/wp1820214.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Kit Harington</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/239019</tmdb>
  <summary>Christopher Catesby "Kit" Harington (born 26 December 1986) is an English actor who rose to fame playing the role of Jon Snow, one of the main characters in the series Game of Thrones. He starred as Albert Narracott in the original West End production of War Horse. Harington also played the lead role of Milo in the 2014 film Pompeii and 'Eret' in How to Train Your Dragon 2.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4MqUjb1SYrzHmFSyGiXnlZWLvBs.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://images7.alphacoders.com/392/thumb-1920-392863.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Woody Harrelson</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/57755</tmdb>
  <summary>Woodrick Tracy "Woody" Harrelson (born July 23, 1961) is an American actor and comedian. Harrelson's breakthrough role came in the television sitcom Cheers as bartender Woody Boyd. Notable film characters include basketball hustler Billy Hoyle in White Men Can't Jump, bowler Roy Munson in Kingpin, serial killer Mickey Knox in Natural Born Killers, magazine publisher Larry Flynt in The People vs. Larry Flynt, country singer Dusty in A Prairie Home Companion, bounty hunter Carson Wells in No Country for Old Men, zombie killer Tallahassee in Zombieland, blind piano player/meat salesman Ezra Turner in Seven Pounds, conspiracy nut Charlie Frost in 2012, a delusional man who believes that he is a superhero named Defendor in Defendor and Cpt. Tony Stone in The Messenger. For The People vs. Larry Flynt and The Messenger, Harrelson earned Academy Award nominations for Best Actor and Best Supporting Actor, respectively.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Woody Harrelson, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1ecdooAHICUhCZKKEKlFtccEmTU.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://hdwallsource.com/img/2016/6/woody-harrelson-face-wallpaper-56108-57858-hd-wallpapers.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Kevin Hart</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/55638</tmdb>
  <summary>Kevin Hart (born July 6, 1979) is an American actor and comedian.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Kevin Hart (actor), licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9zxRAhWMxhVrgDnUysvTGLW7fcW.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://thehollywoodunlocked.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/kevinhart.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Tom Hiddleston</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/91606</tmdb>
  <content>set</content>
  <summary>Thomas William "Tom" Hiddleston (born 9 February 1981) is an English actor. He is perhaps best known for playing Loki in the 2011 action movie Thor. Description above from the Wikipedia article Tom Hiddleston, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://walter.trakt.tv/images/people/000/294/654/headshots/thumb/adbc7cee4f.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://hdwallsource.com/img/2016/6/tom-hiddleston-desktop-hd-wallpaper-55671-57416-hd-wallpapers.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Simon Helberg</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/53863</tmdb>
  <summary>Simon Helberg is an American actor and comedian, best known for his role as Howard Wolowitz in The Big Bang Theory.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zic1gEH1qEMHhbm5Vxwp9J2XrAO.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/RdUeA0mk5yI/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Jonah Hill</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/21007</tmdb>
  <summary>American actor and writer Jonah Hill is most famous for his comedic roles in Superbad (2007), and Get Him to the Greek (2010).

    The California native attended college in New York where he studied acting, produced plays, and was introduced to movie producer Dustin Hoffman.

    After meeting Jonah, Hoffman asked him to audition for a role in I Heart Huckabees (2004). This turned out to be Jonah's breakthrough film debut.

    Throughout his career, Hill has been known for his quasi dorky character with an offbeat, often self-deprecating sense of humor.

    Jonah Hill’s other interests include writing, and he has expressed interest in working with shows such as The Simpsons.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7GXzpyHLCEA36J9biB0wJVAauiO.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.etonline.com/sites/default/files/images/2016-08/JonahHill_1280_081916.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Anthony Hopkins</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/4173</tmdb>
  <summary>Anthony Hopkins was born on 31 December 1937, in Margam, Glamorgan, Wales. Influenced by Richard Burton, he decided to study at College of Music and Drama in Cardiff and graduated in 1957. In 1965, he moved to London and joined the National Theatre, invited by Laurence Olivier, who could see the talent in Hopkins. In 1967, he made his first film for television, A Flea in Her Ear (1967) (TV).

    From this moment on, he enjoyed a successful career in cinema and television. In 1968, he worked on The Lion in Winter (1968) with Timothy Dalton. Many successes came later, and Hopkins' remarkable acting style reached the four corners of the world. In 1977, he appeared in two major films: A Bridge Too Far (1977) with James Caan, Gene Hackman, Sean Connery, Michael Caine, Elliott Gould and Laurence Olivier, and Maximilian Schell. In 1980, he worked on The Elephant Man (1980). Two good television literature adaptations followed: Othello (1981) (TV) and "Hallmark Hall of Fame: The Hunchback of Notre Dame (#31.2)" (1982). In 1987 he was awarded with the Commander of the order of the British Empire. This year was also important in his cinematic life, with 84 Charing Cross Road (1987), acclaimed by specialists. In 1993, he was knighted.

    In the 1990s, Hopkins made movies like Desperate Hours (1990) and Howards End (1992), The Remains of the Day (1993) (nominee for the Oscar), Legends of the Fall (1994), Nixon (1995) (nominee for the Oscar), Surviving Picasso (1996), Amistad (1997) (nominee for the Oscar), The Mask of Zorro (1998), Meet Joe Black (1998) and Instinct (1999). His most remarkable film, however, was The Silence of the Lambs (1991), for which he won the Oscar for Best Actor. He also got a BAFTA for this role. IMDb Mini Biography By: Emerenciano
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jdoBTIru71FbPuHGEgox5RVmIO0.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/9WG99ObCW_g/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>
<dir>
  <title>Ice-T</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/21411</tmdb>
  <summary>Tracy Morrow (born February 16, 1958), better known by his stage name Ice-T, is an American musician and actor. He was born in Newark, New Jersey and moved to district Crenshaw, Los Angeles, California when he was in the 7th grade. After graduating from high school he served in the United States Army for four years. He began his career as a rapper in the 1980s and was signed to Sire Records in 1987, when he released his debut album Rhyme Pays. The next year, he founded the record label Rhyme Syndicate Records (named after his collective of fellow hip hop artists called the Rhyme Syndicate) and released another album, Power. He co-founded the thrash metal band Body Count, which he introduced in his 1991 album O.G.: Original Gangster. Body Count released its self-titled debut album in 1992. Ice-T encountered controversy over his track "Cop Killer", which was perceived to glamorize killing police officers. Ice-T asked to be released from his contract with Warner Bros. Records, and his next solo album, Home Invasion was released later in the Fall of 1993 through Priority Records. Body Count's next album was released in 1994, and Ice-T released two more albums in the late 1990s. Since 2000, he has portrayed NYPD Detective Odafin Tutuola on the NBC police drama Law & Order: Special Victims Unit.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8vn4VY5bJdiFXVOzKyFJpST8xPs.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://fanart.tv/fanart/music/8a75ce0d-1df3-47cc-b076-ce2f4e8250f0/artistbackground/ice-t-55bcb9101c88d.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Eric Idle</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/10713</tmdb>
  <summary>From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia. Eric Idle (born 29 March 1943) is an English comedian, actor, author, singer, writer, and comedic composer who wrote and performed as a member of the popular British comedy group Monty Python.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Eric Idle, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.


  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8bIEjD3ZNRdveo6avslTX6PB22U.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/18_Eric-Idle.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Hugh Jackman</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/6968</tmdb>
  <summary>Hugh Michael Jackman (born 12 October 1968) is an Australian actor and producer who is involved in film, musical theatre, and television. Jackman has won international recognition for his roles in major films, notably as action/superhero, period and romance characters.

    He is known for his role as Wolverine in the X-Men series, as well as for his leads in Kate & Leopold, Van Helsing, The Prestige, and Australia. Jackman is a singer, dancer, and actor in stage musicals, and won a Tony Award for his role in The Boy from Oz. In November 2008, Open Salon named Jackman one of the sexiest men alive. Later that same month, People magazine named Jackman "Sexiest Man Alive.” A three-time host of the Tony Awards, winning an Emmy Award for one of these appearances, Jackman also hosted the 81st Academy Awards on 22 February 2009. Description above from the Wikipedia article Hugh Jackman , licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w440_and_h660_bestv2/2VFrKpHGSKNUfq3TI6zUSU5AIdt.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://hdwallpaperbackgrounds.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/Hugh-Jackman-HD-Wallpapers.jpg</fanart>
</dir>
<dir>
  <title>Samuel L. Jackson</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/2231</tmdb>
  <summary>Samuel Leroy Jackson (born December 21, 1948) is an American film and television actor and film producer. After Jackson became involved with the Civil Rights Movement, he moved on to acting in theater at Morehouse College, and then films. He had several small roles such as in the film Goodfellas, Def by Temptation, before meeting his mentor, Morgan Freeman, and the director Spike Lee. After gaining critical acclaim for his role in Jungle Fever in 1991, he appeared in films such as Patriot Games, Amos & Andrew, True Romance and Jurassic Park. In 1994 he was cast as Jules Winnfield in Pulp Fiction, and his performance received several award nominations and critical acclaim.

    Jackson has since appeared in over 100 films including Die Hard with a Vengeance, The 51st State, Jackie Brown, Unbreakable, The Incredibles, Black Snake Moan, Shaft, Snakes on a Plane, as well as the Star Wars prequel trilogy and small roles in Quentin Tarantino's Kill Bill Vol. 2 and Inglourious Basterds. He played Nick Fury in Iron Man and Iron Man 2, Thor, the first two of a nine-film commitment as the character for the Marvel Cinematic Universe franchise. Jackson's many roles have made him one of the highest grossing actors at the box office. Jackson has won multiple awards throughout his career and has been portrayed in various forms of media including films, television series, and songs. In 1980, Jackson married LaTanya Richardson, with whom he has one daughter, Zoe.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Samuel L. Jackson, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AvCReLikjzYEf9XjTQxbv3JWgKT.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/wZdnOnydgIQ/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Scarlett Johansson</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/1245</tmdb>
  <summary>Scarlett Johansson, born November 22, 1984, is an American actress, model and singer. She made her film debut in North (1994) and was later nominated for the Independent Spirit Award for Best Female Lead for her performance in Manny & Lo (1996), garnering further acclaim and prominence with roles in The Horse Whisperer (1998) and Ghost World (2001). She shifted to adult roles with her performances in Girl with a Pearl Earring (2003) and Sofia Coppola's Lost in Translation (2003), for which she won a BAFTA award for Best Actress in a Leading Role; both films earned her Golden Globe Award nominations as well.

    A role in A Love Song for Bobby Long (2004) earned Johansson her third Golden Globe for Best Actress nomination. Johansson garnered another Golden Globe nomination for Best Supporting Actress with her role in Woody Allen's Match Point (2005). She has played the Marvel comic book character Black Widow/Natasha Romanoff in Iron Man 2 (2010), The Avengers (2012), and Captain America: The Winter Soldier (2014) and is set to reprise the role in Avengers: Age of Ultron (2015). The 2010 Broadway revival of Arthur Miller's A View From the Bridge won Johansson the Tony Award for Best Performance by a Featured Actress in a Play. As a singer, Johansson has released two albums, Anywhere I Lay My Head and Break Up.

    Johansson is considered one of Hollywood's modern sex symbols, and has frequently appeared in published lists of the sexiest women in the world, most notably when she was named the "Sexiest Woman Alive" by Esquire magazine in both 2006 and 2013 (the only woman to be chosen for the title twice), and the "Sexiest Celebrity" by Playboy magazine in 2007.

    Johansson was born in New York City. Her father, Karsten Johansson, is a Danish-born architect, and her paternal grandfather, Ejner Johansson, was a screenwriter and director. Her mother, Melanie Sloan, a producer, comes from an Ashkenazi Jewish family from the Bronx. Johansson has an older sister, Vanessa, who is an actress; an older brother, Adrian; a twin brother, Hunter (who appeared in the film Manny & Lo with Scarlett); and a half-brother, Christian, from her father's re-marriage.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8EueDe6rPF0jQU4LSpsH2Rmrqac.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-g-k5PIzV0ZY/USd9ZhE6xYI/AAAAAAAAAHs/7j2lnpu89ro/s1600/Scarlett+Johansson+Hot+Wallpapers+In+Smilling.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Dwayne Johnson</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/18918</tmdb>
  <summary>Dwayne Douglas Johnson (born May 2, 1972), also known by his ring name The Rock, is an American and Canadian actor, producer and semi-retired professional wrestler, signed with WWE.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/akweMz59qsSoPUJYe7QpjAc2rQp.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://wallpapersite.com/images/pages/pic_w/1799.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Anna Kendrick</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/84223</tmdb>
  <summary>Anna Kendrick (born August 9, 1985) is an American film and stage actress best known for the role of Natalie Keener in the 2009 film Up in the Air. Her other work includes the films Camp (2003), Rocket Science (2007) and Scott Pilgrim vs. the World (2010) and the Broadway musical High Society (1998) and also stars in The Twilight Saga. Kendrick is a Tony, Drama Desk, Screen Actors Guild, BAFTA, Golden Globe, Independent Spirit and an Academy Award nominee for Best Supporting Actress.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Anna Kendrick, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dJn4oRzQAICBUYz6qPKhZjrXljr.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/QREIlWfG8O4/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Kris Kristofferson</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/10823</tmdb>
  <summary>Kristoffer "Kris" Kristofferson (born June 22, 1936) is an American musician, actor, and writer. He is known for hits such as "Me and Bobby McGee", "For the Good Times", "Sunday Mornin' Comin' Down", and "Help Me Make It Through the Night". Kristofferson is the sole writer of most of his songs, but he has collaborated with various other figures of the Nashville scene such as Shel Silverstein.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Kris Kristofferson, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yZbiKxeHUuFjCSYvzg3u6qOZ6a5.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/oAu6_SSxl0E/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Angela Lansbury </title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/14730</tmdb>
	<summary>Angela Brigid Lansbury, CBE (born 16 October 1925) is an English actress and singer in theatre, television and motion pictures, whose career has spanned eight decades. Her first film appearance was in the 1944 film Gaslight as a conniving maid, for which she received an Academy Award nomination. Among her other films are The Manchurian Candidate (1962), Bedknobs and Broomsticks (1971) Beauty and the Beast (1991), and Anastasia (1997).

She expanded her repertoire to Broadway musicals and television in the 1950s and was particularly successful in Broadway productions of Gypsy, Mame and Sweeney Todd. Lansbury is perhaps best known to modern audiences for her 12 year run as writer and sleuth Jessica Fletcher on the U.S. television series Murder, She Wrote, in which she starred from 1984 to 1996. Her recent roles include Lady Adelaide Stitch in the 2005 film Nanny McPhee, Leona Mullen in the 2007 Broadway play Deuce, Madame Arcati in the 2009 Broadway revival of the play Blithe Spirit and Madame Armfeldt in the 2010 Broadway revival of the musical A Little Night Music.

Respected for her versatility, Lansbury has won five Tony Awards, six Golden Globes, an Honorary Academy Award, and has been nominated for numerous other industry awards, including the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress on three occasions, and eighteen Emmy Awards.
</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nMy8sPPLf8fjSglFLP3IzIGbjly.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart></fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Jennifer Lawrence</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/72129</tmdb>
  <summary>Jennifer Shrader Lawrence (born August 15, 1990) is an American actress.

    Her first major role was as a lead cast member on TBS's The Bill Engvall Show (2007–2009) and she subsequently appeared in the independent films The Burning Plain (2008) and Winter's Bone (2010), for which she received nominations for the Academy Award, Golden Globe Award, Satellite Award, Independent Spirit Award, and Screen Actors Guild Award for Best Actress. At age 20, she was the second-youngest actress ever to be nominated for the Academy Award for Best Actress. At age 22, her performance in the romantic comedy Silver Linings Playbook (2012) earned her the Academy Award, Golden Globe Award, Screen Actors Guild Award, Satellite Award and the Independent Spirit Award for Best Actress, amongst other accolades, making her the youngest person ever to be nominated for two Academy Awards for Best Actress and the second-youngest Best Actress winner.

    Lawrence is also known for playing Raven Darkhölme / Mystique in the 2011 film X-Men: First Class, a role she will reprise in X-Men: Days of Future Past in 2014. In 2012, she achieved international recognition starring as the heroine Katniss Everdeen in The Hunger Games, an adaptation of Suzanne Collins' best-selling novel of the same name. Her performance in the film garnered her notable critical praise and marked her as the highest-grossing action heroine of all time.

    Lawrence's performances thus far have prompted Rolling Stone to call her "the most talented young actress in America." In 2013, Time named her one of the 100 most influential people in the world.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Jennifer Lawrence, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hLzgl1dS8O2IAn1PIwHYhxR0Lkm.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://s1.bwallpapers.com/wallpapers/2014/02/11/jennifer-lawrence-desktop-backgrounds_09172453.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Dolph Lundgren</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/16644</tmdb>
  <summary>Hans "Dolph" Lundgren (born 3 November 1957) is a Swedish actor, director, screenwriter, producer, and martial artist.

    Lundgren received a degree in chemistry from Washington State University, a degree in chemical engineering from the Royal Institute of Technology in the early 1980s, and a master's degree in chemical engineering from the University of Sydney in 1982. He holds the rank of 3rd dan black belt in Kyokushin karate and was European champion in 1980-81. While in Sydney, he became a bodyguard for Jamaican singer Grace Jones and began a relationship with her. He received a Fulbright scholarship to MIT and moved to Boston. Jones convinced him to leave the university and move to New York City to be with her and begin acting, where, after a short stint as a model and bouncer at the Manhattan nightclub The Limelight, Jones got him a small debut role as a KGB henchman in the James Bond film A View to a Kill.

    Lundgren's breakthrough came when he starred in Rocky IV in 1985 as the imposing Soviet boxer Ivan Drago. Since then, he has starred in more than 40 films, almost all of them in the action genre. He portrayed He-Man in the 1987 science fantasy film Masters of the Universe and Frank Castle in the 1989 film The Punisher. In the early 1990s, he also appeared in films such as Dark Angel (1990), Universal Soldier (1992), Joshua Tree (1993), Johnny Mnemonic (1995), and Blackjack (1998). In 2004, he directed his first film, The Defender, and subsequently directed The Mechanik (2005), Missionary Man (2007), Command Performance (2009), and Icarus (2010), also starring in the latter.

    After a long spell performing in direct-to-video films since 1995, Lundgren returned to Hollywood in 2010 with the role of Gunner Jensen in The Expendables, alongside Sylvester Stallone and an all-action star cast. He reprised his role in The Expendables 2 (2012) and The Expendables 3 (2014). Also in 2014, he co-starred in Skin Trade, an action thriller about human trafficking. The film marks his third collaboration with Cary-Hiroyuki Tagawa, the previous two being Showdown in Little Tokyo (1991) and Bridge of Dragons (1999). He is due to reprise his role as Gunner Jensen in The Expendables 4 (2018).

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Dolph Lundgren, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hjR1tpZV5XKX8daIKmU80ZuOfMO.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/L7E1LbWFPAY/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>John Malkovich</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/6949</tmdb>
  <summary>John Gavin Malkovich  is an American actor, producer, director, and fashion designer. Over the last 30 years of his career, Malkovich has appeared in more than 70 motion pictures. For his roles in Places in the Heart and In the Line of Fire, he received Academy Award nominations. He has also appeared in well-received films such as Empire of the Sun, The Killing Fields, Dangerous Liaisons, Of Mice and Men, Being John Malkovich, Burn After Reading, RED, and Warm Bodies, as well as producing numerous films, including Juno and The Perks of Being a Wallflower. Malkovich attended exclusively Illinois schools throughout his childhood and into adulthood, building a community of like-minded performers such as Joan Allen, Gary Sinise and Glenne Headly, all of whom co-founde
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tCtiWZbKKRgHhLxFCIPfveYAsdc.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/lVF4_u-tmmc/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Melissa McCarthy</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/5536</tmdb>
  <summary>Melissa McCarthy (born August 26, 1970) is an American actress known most for her portrayal of chef Sookie St. James, Lorelai Gilmore's best friend, on the television series Gilmore Girls, and currently as the title character Molly Flynn on the CBS sitcom Mike & Molly.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Melissa McCarthy, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qVb4VmZRwcANDuzhXjVjTlQ761x.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://media2.s-nbcnews.com/i/newscms/2015_22/577026/melissa-mccarthy-today-150526_67746d2af8991588bdd436f4d4d97945.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Ewan McGregor</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/3061</tmdb>
  <summary>Ewan Gordon McGregor was born 31 March 1971 in Crieff, Scotland. At 16, he left Crieff and Morrison Academy to join the Perth Repertory Theatre. His parents encouraged him to leave school and pursue his acting goals rather than be unhappy. McGregor studied drama for a year at Kirkcaldly in Fife, then enrolled at London's Guildhall School of Music and Drama for a three-year course. He studied alongside Daniel Craig and Alistair McGowan among others, and left right before graduating after snagging the role of Private Mick Hopper in Dennis Potter's 1993 six-part Channel 4 series "Lipstick on Your Collar" (1993).

    His first notable role was that of Alex Law in Shallow Grave (1994), directed by Danny Boyle, written by John Hodge and produced by Andrew MacDonald. This was followed by The Pillow Book (1996) and Trainspotting (1996), the latter of which brought him to the public's attention.

    He is now one of the most critically acclaimed actors of his generation, and portrays Obi-wan Kenobi in the first three Star Wars episodes. McGregor is married to French production designer Eve Mavrakis, whom he met while working on the TV show "Kavanagh QC" (1995). They married in France in the summer of 1995 and have two daughters, Clara Mathilde and Esther Rose. McGregor has formed a production company with friends Jonny Lee Miller, Sean Pertwee, Jude Law and Sadie Frost. Called Natural Nylon, they hope it will make innovative films that do not conform to Hollywood standards.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aEmyadfRXTmmR7UW7OXsm5a6smS.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://wallpaperscraft.com/image/ewan_mcgregor_elle_men_photosession_motorcycle_102581_1280x720.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Wendi McLendon-Covey</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/63234</tmdb>
  <summary>After her a breakout performance in the 2011 comedy film Bridesmaids, She has appeared in numerous films. In 2013 she began starring as Beverly Goldberg in the ABC comedy series The Goldbergs, for which she was nominated for a Critics' Choice Television Award for Best Actress in a Comedy Series in 2014.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uEZjQVJjwzMvMkvXZu1gDKq8lA6.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart></fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Ian McKellen</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/1327</tmdb>
  <summary>Sir Ian Murray McKellen, CH, CBE (born 25 May 1939) is an English actor. He is the recipient of six Laurence Olivier Awards, a Tony Award, a Golden Globe Award, a Screen Actors Guild Award, a BIF Award, two Saturn Awards, four Drama Desk Awards and two Critics' Choice Awards. He has also received two Academy Award nominations, eight BAFTA film and TV nominations and five Emmy Award nominations. McKellen's work spans genres ranging from Shakespearean and modern theatre to popular fantasy and science fiction. His notable film roles include Gandalf in The Lord of the Rings and The Hobbit trilogies and Magneto in the X-Men films.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/coWjgMEYJjk2OrNddlXCBm8EIr3.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://cdn.skim.gs/images/cfnu6wjvgxfkvy1fdkzl/sir-ian-mckellen-weighs-in-on-the-2016-oscars-debate</fanart>
</dir>



<dir>
  <title>Rick Moranis</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/8872</tmdb>
  <summary>Frederick Allan "Rick" Moranis (born April 18, 1953) is a retired Canadian comedian, actor and musician. He came to prominence in the 1980s on Second City Television, before moving on to appearances in several Hollywood films, including Strange Brew; Ghostbusters; Spaceballs; Little Shop of Horrors; Honey, I Shrunk the Kids; Little Giants; Parenthood; The Flintstones, and My Blue Heaven. In 1996–1997, Moranis announced that he would retire from acting due to family commitments, though he occasionally does voice-over work.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Rick Moranis, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rVZbTJjM4g0Um6trlLHRiBzBO7t.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://pic.yts.gs/1986/31605/263fdcd0e8a1452cacbbacbe321a0a55.png</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Cillian Murphy</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/2037</tmdb>
  <summary>Cillian Murphy is an Irish film and theatre actor. He is often noted by critics for his chameleonic performances in diverse roles and distinctive blue eyes.

A native of Cork, Murphy began his performing career as a rock musician. After turning down a record deal, he made his professional acting debut in the play Disco Pigs in 1996. He went on to star in Irish and UK film and stage productions throughout the late 1990s and early 2000s, first coming to international attention in 2003 as the hero in the post-apocalyptic film 28 Days Later. Murphy's best-known roles are as villains in two 2005 blockbusters: the Scarecrow in the superhero film Batman Begins, and Jackson Rippner in the thriller Red Eye. Next came two contrasting, widely acclaimed starring roles: his Golden Globe Award-nominated performance as transgender outcast "Kitten" in 2005's Breakfast on Pluto and a turn as a 1920s Irish revolutionary in the 2006 Palme d'Or winner, The Wind That Shakes the Barley.

In 2010, Murphy will co-star in Inception, a big budget movie starring Leonardo DiCaprio by Batman Begins/The Dark Knight director Christopher Nolan.

A resident of London since 2001, Murphy often works in or near the city and has expressed no desire to move to Hollywood. Uncomfortable on the celebrity circuit, he customarily gives interviews about his work, but does not appear on television talk shows or discuss details of his private life with the press.
</summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gybXt7gjFCeV67l3jgJtp6Pxm77.jpg</thumbnail>
  <content>set</content>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Bill Murray</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/1532</tmdb>
  <summary>William James "Bill" Murray (born September 21, 1950) is an American actor and comedian. He first gained national exposure on Saturday Night Live and later went on to star in a number of critically and commercially successful comedic films, including Caddyshack (1980), Ghostbusters (1984), and Groundhog Day (1993). Murray gained additional critical acclaim later in his career, starring in Lost in Translation (2003), for which he was nominated for an Academy Award, and a series of films directed by Wes Anderson, including Rushmore (1998), The Royal Tenenbaums (2001), The Life Aquatic with Steve Zissou (2004) and Fantastic Mr. Fox (2009). Description above from the Wikipedia article Bill Murray, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7BOoOAIA1CnSzFSVSJP7saniQaB.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/11_Bill-Murray.jpg</fanart>
  <content>set</content>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Kunal Nayyar</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/208099</tmdb>
  <summary>Kunal Nayyar is an Indian actor born in London, England, and raised in New Delhi, India, best known for his role as Rajesh Koothrappali in The Big Bang Theory.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4h0Q8FJlv2jUa0wvqFwCKfaIrkD.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/jHZEh7ZLqZs/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Liam Neeson</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/3896</tmdb>
  <summary>William John "Liam" Neeson OBE (born 7 June 1952) is an Irish actor who has been nominated for an Oscar, a BAFTA and three Golden Globe Awards.

    He has starred in a number of notable roles including Oskar Schindler in Schindler's List, Michael Collins in Michael Collins, Peyton Westlake in Darkman, Jean Valjean in Les Misérables, Qui-Gon Jinn in Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace, Alfred Kinsey in Kinsey, Ras Al Ghul in Batman Begins and the voice of Aslan in The Chronicles of Narnia film series. He has also starred in several other notable films, from major Hollywood studio releases (ie. Excalibur, The Dead Pool, Nell, Rob Roy, The Haunting, Love Actually, Kingdom of Heaven, Taken, Clash of the Titans, The A-Team, Unknown) to smaller arthouse films (ie. Deception, Breakfast on Pluto, Chloe).

    He was born in Ballymena, County Antrim, Northern Ireland and educated at Saint Patrick's College, Ballymena Technical College and Queen's University Belfast. He moved to Dublin after university to further his acting career, joining the renowned Abbey Theatre. In the early 1990s, he moved again to the United States, where the wide acclaim for his performance in Schindler's List led to more high-profile work. He is widowed and lives in New York with his two sons.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Liam Neeson, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9mdAohLsDu36WaXV2N3SQ388bvz.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://www.desktopbackground.org/download/1280x720/2011/07/10/232127_liam-neeson-wallpaper-1-jpeg_1920x1080_h.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Leslie Nielsen</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/7633</tmdb>
	<summary>Leslie William Nielsen, OC (11 February 1926 – 28 November 2010) was a Canadian and naturalized American actor and comedian. Nielsen appeared in over one hundred films and 1,500 television programs over the span of his career, portraying over 220 characters. Born in Regina, Saskatchewan, Nielsen enlisted in the Royal Canadian Air Force and worked as a disc jockey before receiving a scholarship to Neighborhood Playhouse. Making his television debut in 1948, he quickly expanded to over 50 television appearances two years later. Nielsen made his film debut in 1956, and began collecting roles in dramas, westerns, and romance films. Nielsen's performances in the films Forbidden Planet (1956) and The Poseidon Adventure (1972) received positive reviews as a serious actor, though he is primarily known for his comedic roles.

Although Nielsen's acting career crossed a variety of genres in both television and films, his deadpan delivery in Airplane! (1980) marked a turning point in his career, one that would make him, in the words of film critic Roger Ebert, "the Olivier of spoofs." Nielsen enjoyed further success with The Naked Gun film series (1988 – 1994), based on a short-lived television series Police Squad! in which he starred earlier. His portrayal of serious characters seemingly oblivious to (and complicit in) their absurd surroundings gave him a reputation as a comedian. In the final years of his career, Nielsen appeared in multiple spoof and parody films, many of which were met poorly by critics, but performed well in box office and home media releases. Nielsen married four times and had two daughters from his second marriage. He was recognized with a variety of awards throughout his career, and was inducted into the Canada and Hollywood Walks of Fame.
</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cZpuTfE1j63tCEXoSL2A7KZjk5d.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://ecowallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/4056_leslie_nielsen.jpg</fanart>
</dir>



<dir>
  <title>Bill Nighy</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/2440</tmdb>
  <summary>William Francis "Bill" Nighy (pronounced /ˈnaɪ/ ny; born 12 December 1949) is a British actor and comedian.

    He worked in theatre and television before his first cinema role in 1981, and made his name in television with The Men's Room in 1991, in which he played the womanizer Prof. Mark Carleton, whose extra-marital affairs kept him "vital". He became known around the world in 2003 as Billy Mack, the aging pop star in Love Actually, and in the same year played James Mortmain, the eccentric husband struggling to keep his family afloat in a decaying English castle, in I Capture the Castle. He is also known for his roles in the films Underworld, Shaun of the Dead, The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy, Pirates of the Caribbean, Hot Fuzz, Valkyrie, G-Force and provided voice talents in the films The Magic Roundabout, Flushed Away and Rango. He recently played Rufus Scrimgeour in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows. Bill Nighy is a Patron and supporter of the artistic collective The Factory Theatre Company alongside other actors such as Mark Rylance, Ewan McGregor and Richard Wilson. Other notable members include founder Alex Hassell, Catherine Bailey and Alan Morrissey.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Bill Nighy, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pdWmNsy3bVN8m4UitaFAl1rhi2O.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.lifetimetv.co.uk/sites/default/files/Bill_Nighy.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
	<title>Jared Padalecki</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/49623</tmdb>
	<summary> Jared Tristan Padalecki (born July 19, 1982) is an American actor. He grew up in Texas and came to fame in the early 2000s after appearing on the television series Gilmore Girls as well as in several Hollywood films, including New York Minute and House of Wax. Padalecki is best known for his role as Sam Winchester on the CW television series Supernatural.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uQLe1lfEBul3locVlV8nXD6n8TI.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://i.pinimg.com/736x/ca/72/01/ca72016f052aa1428f8cd747f3acc2e1.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Jim Parsons</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/5374</tmdb>
  <summary>Jim Parsons is an American television and film actor, best known for playing Sheldon Cooper in The Big Bang Theory.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3EdsBXcwZFX2Txjl4uLhLgTU8SK.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/sjqPEwsxEdk/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Simon Pegg</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/11108</tmdb>
  <content>set</content>
  <summary>Simon Pegg (born Simon John Beckingham) is an English comedic actor, writer, producer and director. He is best known for his TV show Spaced, about two roommates, as well as his film Shaun of the Dead, which he described as a 'Romantic Zombie Comedy'. In 2009 he played Montgomery "Scotty" Scott in the Star Trek Reboot, taking over the iconic role previously played by James Doohan, In 2005 he married Maureen McCann in Glasgow, Scotland. In 2009 the pair had their first child. He has stated that his favorite film is Raising Arizona and his favorite TV shows The X-FIles and Arrested Development.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://walter.trakt.tv/images/people/000/414/339/headshots/thumb/8f76e52e4e.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://ecowallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/36_Simon_Pegg.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Joe Pesci</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/4517</tmdb>
  <summary>Joseph Frank "Joe" Pesci (born February 9, 1943) is an American actor, comedian, singer and musician. He is known for his roles as violent mobsters, funnymen, comic foils and quirky sidekicks. Pesci has starred in a number of high profile films such as Goodfellas, Casino, Raging Bull, Once Upon a Time in America, My Cousin Vinny, Easy Money, JFK, Moonwalker, Home Alone, Home Alone 2: Lost in New York, and the 2nd, 3rd, and 4th Lethal Weapon films.

    In 1990, Pesci won the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor for his role as the psychopathic mobster Tommy DeVito in Goodfellas, ten years after receiving a nomination in the same category for Raging Bull.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4zidewFE0x8OBlW0RjEKlkhw4lr.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://ecowallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/1422_joe_pesci.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Lori Petty</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/15309</tmdb>
  <summary>Lori Petty (born October 14, 1963) is an American film and television actress best known for playing "Tyler Endicott" in Point Break in 1991, "Kit Keller" in A League of Their Own in 1992, and the title role in Tank Girl in 1995.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Lori Petty, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/u2D3zteSlOj4zLp7jBcGqQVBsR1.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.rockshockpop.com/screencaps/TankGirl/02-1.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Lou Diamond Phillips</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/38560</tmdb>
  <summary>Lou Diamond Phillips (born Lou Diamond Upchurch; February 17, 1962) is an American film, television, and stage actor. His breakthrough came when he starred in the film La Bamba. He earned a supporting actor Golden Globe Award nomination for his role in Stand and Deliver and a Tony Award nomination for his role in The King and I. Other notable films in which Phillips has starred include Courage Under Fire, Che, and Love Takes Wing.

    Outside of acting, he has become notable for finishing 186th in the 2009 World Series of Poker World Championships "No Limit Texas hold 'em" main event.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Lou Diamond Phillips, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/afXcQRss7rZ6Ocx7PUQFbz7tPOm.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/hSu7v9CaC0I/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Natalie Portman</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/524</tmdb>
  <summary>Natalie Portman (born Neta-Lee Hershlag, Hebrew: נטע-לי הרשלג‎‎; June 9, 1981) is an actress with dual American and Israeli citizenship. Her first role was in the 1994 action thriller Léon: The Professional, opposite Jean Reno. She was later cast as Padmé Amidala in the Star Wars prequel trilogy (released in 1999, 2002 and 2005).

    Born in Jerusalem to an Israeli father and American mother, Portman grew up in the eastern United States from the age of three. She studied dancing and acting in New York, and starred in Star Wars: Episode I – The Phantom Menace while still at high school on Long Island. In 1999, Portman enrolled at Harvard University to study psychology, alongside her work as an actress; she completed a bachelor's degree in 2003. During her studies she starred in a second Star Wars film and opened in New York City's The Public Theater production of Anton Chekhov's The Seagull in 2001.

    Portman won a Golden Globe and was nominated for an Academy Award for starring in the 2004 drama Closer, appeared in Star Wars: Episode III – Revenge of the Sith the following year, and won a Constellation Award for Best Female Performance and the Saturn Award for Best Actress for her starring role in the political thriller V for Vendetta (2006). She played leading roles in the historical dramas Goya's Ghosts (2006) and The Other Boleyn Girl (2008), and also appeared in Thor (2011) and its 2013 sequel. In 2010, Portman starred in the psychological thriller film Black Swan. Her performance received widespread critical acclaim and she earned her first Academy Award for Best Actress, her second Golden Globe Award, the SAG Award, the BAFTA Award and the BFCA Award in 2011. In 2016, she portrayed First Lady Jacqueline Kennedy in the biographical drama Jackie. She was nominated for an Academy Award, a BAFTA Award, a Golden Globe Award, a Screen Actors Guild Award and won the BFCA for Best Actress.

    In May 2008, Portman served as the youngest member of the 61st Annual Cannes Film Festival jury. The same year she directed a segment of the collective film New York, I Love You. Her first feature film as a director, A Tale of Love and Darkness, was released in 2015.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jJcRWku3e9OHrmRqytn6WcBjhvh.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://wallpapersdsc.net/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Natalie-Portman-High-Definition-Wallpapers.jpg</fanart>
</dir>
<dir>
  <title>Richard Pryor </title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/9309</tmdb>
  <summary>Richard Franklin Lennox Thomas Pryor was an American stand-up comedian, actor, film director, social critic, satirist, writer, and MC. Pryor was known for uncompromising examinations of racism and topical contemporary issues, which employed colorful vulgarities, and profanity, as well as racial epithets. He reached a broad audience with his trenchant observations and storytelling style. He is widely regarded as one of the most important and influential stand-up comedians of all time: receiving praise from notable comedians such as Jerry Seinfeld, Bob Newhart, and Bill Cosby. His body of work includes the concert movies and recordings starting in the 70s and spanning three decades. He also starred in numerous films as an actor, in both comedic and dramatic roles. He collaborated on many projects with actor Gene Wilder and actor/comedian/writer Paul Mooney. Pryor won an Emmy Award (1973), and five Grammy Awards (1974, 1975, 1976, 1981, and 1982). In 1974, he also won two American Academy of Humor awards and the Writers Guild of America Award. The first ever Kennedy Center Mark Twain Prize for American Humor was presented to him in 1998. Pryor is listed at Number 1 on Comedy Central's list of all-time greatest stand-up comedians.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w440_and_h660_bestv2/hzJ3Q7wDLv4m82eMTbK2tzVzCHG.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.indiewire.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/richard-pryor-1.jpg</fanart>
</dir>
<dir>
  <title>Daniel Radcliffe</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/10980</tmdb>
  <summary>Daniel Jacob Radcliffe (born 23 July 1989) is an English actor who rose to prominence playing the titular character in the Harry Potter film series. His work on the series has earned him several awards and more than £60 million.

    Radcliffe made his acting debut at age ten in BBC One's television movie David Copperfield (1999), followed by his film debut in 2001's The Tailor of Panama. Cast as Harry at the age of eleven, Radcliffe has starred in seven Harry Potter films since 2001, with the final installment releasing in July 2011. In 2007 Radcliffe began to branch out from the series, starring in the London and New York productions of the play Equus, and the 2011 Broadway revival of the musical How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying. The Woman in Black (2012) will be his first film project following the final Harry Potter movie.

    Radcliffe has contributed to many charities, including Demelza House Children's Hospice and The Trevor Project. He has also made public service announcements for the latter. In 2011 the actor was awarded the Trevor Project's "Hero Award".

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Daniel Radcliffe, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kMSMa5tR43TLMR14ahU1neFVytz.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://images.amcnetworks.com/bbcamerica.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/DanielRadcliffe1.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Melissa Rauch</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/122716</tmdb>
  <summary>Melissa Rauch is an American actress and comedian, best known for her role as Bernadette Rostenkowski-Wolowitz in The Big Bang Theory.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bRjDxRexxvwffBIQGDwQQjhhk0d.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/qgoFDVpTrjs/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Robert Redford </title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/4135</tmdb>
  <summary>Charles Robert Redford Jr. (born August 18, 1936), better known as Robert Redford, is an American actor, film director, producer, businessman, model, environmentalist, philanthropist, and founder of the Sundance Film Festival. He has received two Oscars: one in 1981 for directing Ordinary People, and one for Lifetime Achievement in 2002. His popular films include Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid (1969), Jeremiah Johnson (1972), The Candidate (1972), The Sting (1973), The Way We Were (1973), The Great Gatsby (1974), Three Days of the Condor (1975), All the President's Men (1976), The Natural (1984), Out of Africa (1985), and Sneakers (1992). As a filmmaker, his notable films include Ordinary People (1980), A River Runs Through It (1992), Quiz Show (1994), The Horse Whisperer (1998), and The Legend of Bagger Vance (2000).

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Robert Redford, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/b4mJIBWvEyzB8yyZWbmvfzwrdtp.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.tracking-board.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Robert-Redford.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Eddie Redmayne</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/37632</tmdb>
  <summary>Edward John David "Eddie" Redmayne (born 6 January 1982) is an English actor and model. Redmayne won the 2010 Tony Award as best featured actor in a play for his performance in Red.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Eddie Redmayne, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bHipa1GkpedD32w2OIRg5axdkQ6.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://hdwallsource.com/img/2016/7/eddie-redmayne-wallpaper-56799-58558-hd-wallpapers.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Norman Reedus</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/4886</tmdb>
  <summary>Norman Mark Reedus (born January 6, 1969) is an American actor. He is perhaps best known for his portrayal as Murphy MacManus in the 1999 film The Boondock Saints and for the character of Daryl Dixon in the AMC television series The Walking Dead. He has also directed several videos and modeled for various fashion designers.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Norman Reedus, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rMZqCvD36SqMLrAirwGasQGmsMk.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://m.wsj.net/video/20140228/022814walkingdeadfull2/022814walkingdeadfull2_1280x720.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Keanu Reeves</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/6384</tmdb>
  <summary>Keanu Charles Reeves is a Canadian actor. Reeves is known for his roles in Bill & Ted's Excellent Adventure, Speed, Point Break, and The Matrix trilogy as Neo. He has collaborated with major directors such as Stephen Frears (in the 1988 period drama Dangerous Liaisons); Gus Van Sant (in the 1991 independent film My Own Private Idaho); and Bernardo Bertolucci (in the 1993 film Little Buddha). Referring to his 1991 film releases, The New York Times' critic, Janet Maslin, praised Reeves' versatility, saying that he "displays considerable discipline and range. He moves easily between the buttoned-down demeanor that suits a police procedural story and the loose-jointed manner of his comic roles." A repeated theme in roles he has portrayed is that of saving the world, including the characters of Ted Logan, Buddha, Neo, Johnny Mnemonic, John Constantine and Klaatu.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/id1qIb7cZs2eQno90KsKwG8VLGN.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://wallpaperscraft.com/image/keanu_reeves_actor_smile_jacket_beard_100891_1280x720.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Burt Reynolds</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/16475</tmdb>
  <summary>Burton Leon "Burt" Reynolds, Jr. (born February 11, 1936) is an American actor. Some of his memorable roles include Bo 'Bandit' Darville in Smokey and the Bandit, Lewis Medlock in Deliverance, Bobby "Gator" McCluskey in White Lightning and sequel Gator, Paul Crewe and Coach Nate Scarborough in The Longest Yard and its 2005 remake respectively, J.J. McClure in The Cannonball Run, the voice of Charlie B. Barkin in All Dogs Go to Heaven, and Jack Horner in Boogie Nights. He is one of America's most recognizable film and television personalities with more than 90 feature film and 300 television episode credits.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Burt Reynolds, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/g5AyPAhdr5OtHVRGLD3i8Gw4oas.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1920x1080/p03bhcrq.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Ryan Reynolds</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/10859</tmdb>
  <summary>Ryan Rodney Reynolds (born October 23, 1976) is a Canadian actor. He portrayed Michael Bergen on the ABC sitcom Two Guys and a Girl (1998–2001), Billy Simpson in the YTV Canadian teen soap opera Hillside (1991), as well as Marvel Comics characters Hannibal King in Blade: Trinity (2004), Wade Wilson / Weapon XI in X-Men Origins: Wolverine (2009), and the title character in Deadpool (2016) for which he received a Golden Globe Award nomination.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Ryan Reynolds, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/h1co81QaT2nJA41Sb7eZwmWl1L2.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://wallpaperscraft.com/image/ryan_reynolds_actor_motorcycle_104736_1920x1080.jpg</fanart>
</dir>



<dir>
  <title>Seth Rogen</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/19274</tmdb>
  <summary>Seth Rogen (born April 15, 1982) is a Canadian actor, comedian, voice artist, screenwriter, and film producer. Rogen began his career doing stand-up comedy for four years during his teens, coming in second place in the Vancouver Amateur Comedy Contest in 1998. While still living in his native Vancouver, he landed a supporting role in Freaks and Geeks. Shortly after Rogen moved to Los Angeles for his role, Freaks and Geeks was canceled after one season due to poor ratings. He then got a part on the equally short-lived Undeclared, which also hired him as a staff writer. After landing a job as a staff writer on the final season of Da Ali G Show, for which Rogen and the other writers received an Emmy nomination, he was guided by film producer Judd Apatow toward a film career. Rogen was cast in a major supporting role and credited as a co-producer in Apatow's directorial debut, The 40-Year-Old Virgin.

    After receiving critical praise for that performance, Universal Pictures agreed to cast him as the lead in Apatow's next directorial feature, Knocked Up.

    Rogen has appeared in the films Donnie Darko, You, Me and Dupree, Zack and Miri Make a Porno, Observe and Report, and The Green Hornet, and also in the Apatow-produced comedies The 40-Year-Old Virgin, Knocked Up, Superbad, Pineapple Express, and Funny People. He and his comedy partner Evan Goldberg co-wrote the comedy films Superbad and Pineapple Express, for which he originally intended to headline while in high school. Rogen has provided voice talents in the animated films Horton Hears a Who!, Kung Fu Panda, and Monsters vs. Aliens. He also supports Crowdrise, a charitable networking site.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aQc8O52P4vWDRfuxCLsz9rvnwf3.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.mulierchile.com/seth-rogen/seth-rogen-003.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Paul Rudd</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/22226</tmdb>
  <summary>Paul Stephen Rudd (born April 6, 1969) is an American actor, comedian, writer and producer. He has primarily appeared in comedies, and is known for his roles in the films Clueless (1995), Wet Hot American Summer (2001), Anchorman: The Legend of Ron Burgundy (2004), The 40-Year-Old Virgin (2005), Knocked Up (2007), Role Models (2008), I Love You, Man(2009), Wanderlust (2012), This Is 40 (2012), and Anchorman 2: The Legend Continues (2013). In television, he appeared in the early 1990s on the NBC drama Sisters and some years later he appeared as Mike Hannigan on the NBC sitcom Friends. Other guest television roles have included an appearance on the Tim and Eric show, a recurring role on Parks and Recreation as politician Bobby Newport, and hosting Saturday Night Live. In 2015, Rudd starred as Scott Lang / Ant-Manin Marvel Studios' Ant-Man and will be reprising the character in Captain America: Civil War, set for release May 6, 2016. Rudd received a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame on July 1, 2015.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/90cd4MNqmqy28ES1mZsQfal3qgn.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://hdcoolwallpapers.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/Paul-Rudd-Wallpapers-HD-04.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Kurt Russell</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/6856</tmdb>
  <summary>Kurt Vogel Russell (born March 17, 1951) is an American television and film actor. His first acting roles were as a child in television series, including a lead role in the Western series The Travels of Jaimie McPheeters (1963–1964). In the 1970s, he signed a ten-year contract with the Walt Disney Company, where he became, according to Robert Osborne, the "studio's top star of the '70s". In 1979, Russell was nominated for an Emmy Award for the made-for-television film Elvis.

    In 1983, he was nominated for a Golden Globe Award for Best Performance by an Actor in a Supporting Role in a Motion Picture for his performance opposite Meryl Streep in the 1984 film, Silkwood. During the 1980s, Russell was cast in several films by director John Carpenter, including anti-hero roles such as former air force hero-turned robber Snake Plissken in the futuristic action film Escape from New York, Antarctic helicopter pilot R.J. MacReady in the horror film The Thing (1982), and truck driver Jack Burton in the dark kung-fu comedy/action film Big Trouble in Little China (1986). Both Escape from New York and Big Trouble in Little China have since become cult films.

    In 1994, he had a starring role in the military/science fiction film Stargate. In the mid-2000s, his portrayal of U.S. Olympic hockey coach Herb Brooks in Miracle (2004) won the praise of critics. In 2006, he appeared in the disaster-thriller Poseidon, and in 2007 Quentin Tarantino's Death Proof segment from the film Grindhouse.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Kurt Russell, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rlnFuNkisPpuypARI7QaGCmOY6V.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/aVQX-WwR19I/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Winona Ryder </title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/1920</tmdb>
  <summary>Winona Laura Horowitz (born October 29, 1971), better known under her professional name Winona Ryder, is an American actress. She made her film debut in the 1986 film Lucas. Ryder's first significant role came in Tim Burton's Beetlejuice (1988) as a goth teenager, which won her critical and commercial recognition. After making various appearances in film and television, Ryder continued her career with the cult film Heathers (1989), a controversial satire of teenage suicide and high school life, which drew Ryder further critical and commercial attention. Having played diverse roles in many well-received films, Ryder won a Golden Globe Award for Best Supporting Actress and an Academy Award nomination in the same category for her role in The Age of Innocence in 1993, as well as another Academy Award nomination for Little Women the following year for Best Actress. In 2000, Ryder received a star on the Walk of Fame in Hollywood, California. Ryder's personal life has been widely reported by the media. Her relationship with actor Johnny Depp in the early 1990s was highly publicized and received much scrutiny by the media and tabloid press. A much talked about 2001 shoplifting incident led to a four-year hiatus from acting. She has also revealed her personal struggle with anxiety and depression, briefly checking into a clinic. In 2006, Ryder returned to the screen, and some media outlets called her performance "a remarkable comeback" to acting, having appeared in high-profile films such as Star Trek. In 2010, she was nominated for two Screen Actors Guild Awards, as the lead actress of When Love Is Not Enough: The Lois Wilson Story, and as part of the cast of Black Swan.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Winona Ryder, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gUyEOZpZlGBUkUxCxyoLEc9WejR.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://eskipaper.com/images/beautiful-winona-ryder-1.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Adam Sandler</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/19292</tmdb>
  <summary>Adam Sandler was born on September 9, 1966, in Brooklyn, New York, to Judy and Stanley Sandler. At 17, he took his first step towards becoming a stand-up comedian when he spontaneously took the stage at a Boston comedy club. He found he was a natural comic. He nurtured his talent while at New York University (graduating with a Bachelor of Fine Arts degree in 1991) by performing regularly in clubs and at universities. During his freshman year, he snagged a recurring role as the Huxtable family's friend Smitty on "The Cosby Show" (1984). While working at a comedy club in L.A., he was "discovered" by Dennis Miller, who recommended him to "Saturday Night Live" (1975) producer Lorne Michaels and told him that Sandler had a big talent. This led to his being cast in the show in 1990, which he also wrote for in addition to performing. After "Saturday Night Live" (1975), Sandler went on to the movies, starring in such hit comedies as Airheads (1994), Happy Gilmore (1996), Billy Madison (1995) and Big Daddy (1999/I). He has also starred in Mr. Deeds (2002) alongside Winona Ryder; Eight Crazy Nights (2002), an animated movie about the Jewish festival of Chanukah; and Punch-Drunk Love (2002). He also writes and produces many of his own films and has composed songs for several of them, including The Wedding Singer (1998). Sandler has had several of his songs placed on the "Billboard" charts, including the classic "The Chanukah Song".

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Adam Sandler, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tv9V6QsuZ3bcp4ciUJjwjcc4qAg.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://wallpaperscraft.com/image/adam_sandler_actor_face_smile_cap_beard_98948_1920x1080.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Steven Seagal</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/23880</tmdb>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/f8OFR4h3ngyFesiudCygrNFdsCE.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://ozon4life.com/data/out/108/image-159351311.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Steven Frederic Seagal (born April 10, 1952) is an American action film star, producer, writer, martial artist, guitarist and a reserve deputy sheriff. A 7th-dan black belt in Aikido, Seagal began his adult life as an Aikido instructor in Japan. He became the first foreigner to operate an Aikido Dojo in Japan.

He later moved to the Los Angeles, California, area where he made his film debut in 1988 in Above the Law. By 1991, he had starred in three successful films, and would go on to achieve greater fame in Under Siege (1992), where he played Navy SEALs counter-terrorist expert Casey Ryback. However, his image became tarnished when both On Deadly Ground (1994, which he directed) and Under Siege 2: Dark Territory (1995) did poorly in theaters. During the later half of the 90s, he starred in three more theatrical films and a direct-to-video The Patriot. Aside from Exit Wounds (2001) and Half Past Dead (2002), his career shifted almost entirely to direct-to-video films (often low budget productions and shot in Europe or Asia). Between 1998 to 2009, he appeared in a total of 22 of these. At the age of 59, he finally returned to the big screen as Torrez in the 2010 film Machete. As of 2011, he's currently busy with the third season of his reality show Steven Seagal: Lawman.

Seagal is also a recording artist and guitarist and the founder of Steven Seagal Enterprises. In addition to his professional achievements, he is also known as an environmentalist, an animal rights activist and a supporter of the 14th Dalai Lama Tenzin Gyatso, and the Tibetan independence movement.
</summary>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>George Segal</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/18364</tmdb>
  <summary>At one time in the early 1970s, it seemed like George Segal would have a career like that enjoyed by his contemporary Jack Nicholson, that of an actor's actor equally adept at comedy and drama. Segal never made the leap to superstar status, and surprisingly, has never won a major acting award, the latter phenomenon being particularly surprising when viewed from the period 1973-4, when he reached the height of his career, appearing in A Touch of Class (1973) and Robert Altman's California Split (1974). It was at this point that Segal's career went awry, when he priced himself as a superstar with a seven-figure salary, but failed to come through at the box office. For example, The Black Bird (1975) was a failure, but, ironically, at the end of the decade, he dropped out of a movie that would have burnished his tarnished lustre as a star: Blake Edwards' 10 (1979). 10 (1979) made Dudley Moore a star, while Arthur (1981) made him a superstar in the 1980s, a lost decade for Segal. It was an example of a career burnout usually associated with the "Oscar curse" (his No Way to Treat a Lady (1968) co-star Rod Steiger, for example, was a great character actor whose career was run off the rails by the expectations raised by the Academy Award). George Segal has never won an Oscar, but more surprisingly, has only been nominated once, for Best Supporting Actor of 1966 for his role as "Nick" in Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? (1966). George Segal was born on February 13, 1934 in Great Neck, Long Island, New York. After a stint in the military, he made his bones as a stage actor before being cast in his first meaty film role in The Young Doctors (1961). His turns in Ship of Fools (1965) and the eponymous King Rat (1965) in 1965 heralded the arrival of a major talent. He followed it up with his Oscar-nominated performance in Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? (1966), in which he more than held his own against Richard Burton and Elizabeth Taylor. Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? (1966) was a cultural phenomenon, the film that wrecked the MPDDA censorship code that had been in place since 1934, and a huge box office success to boot. He had arrived in the major leagues. By the early 1970s, appearances in such films as The Owl and the Pussycat (1970), Blume in Love (1973), Born to Win (1971) and The Hot Rock (1972) had made him a major star with an enviable reputation, just under the heights of the superstar status enjoyed by the likes of Paul Newman. He followed up A Touch of Class (1973) (a hit film for which his co-star Glenda Jackson won an Oscar) and his brilliant performance as the out-of-control gambler in California Split (1974) with a co-starring turn opposite of Jane Fonda in Fun with Dick and Jane (1977), a big hit that revitalized Jane Fonda's film carer. He gave a deft comic performance in Who Is Killing the Great Chefs of Europe? (1978) with Jacqueline Bisset and Robert Morley, which proved a modest box office success. For all practical purposes, even after the failures of The Black Bird (1975), "Lucky Lady" and The Duchess and the Dirtwater Fox (1976), it seemed like Segal, with a few deft career choices, could reorient his career and deliver on the promise of his early period. That he didn't may be the unintended consequence of his focusing on comedy to the detriment of drama. The comedy A Touch of Class (1973) made him a million dollar-per-film movie star, and that's what he concentrated on. Segal began relying on his considerable charm to pull off movies that had little going for them other than their star, and it backfired on him. These films weren't infused with the outrageously funny, subversive comedy of Where's Poppa? (1970), a success from his first period that he enjoyed along with co-star Ruth Gordon and director Carl Reiner. When Segal first made it in the mid-1960s, he established his serious actor bona fides with a deal he cut with ABC-TV that featured him in TV adaptations of Broadway plays. He also played a very memorable "Biff Loman" in Death of a Salesman (1966) (TV), shining in performance in counterpoint to the vital presence that was Lee J. Cobb's "Willy Loman". It was a good life for an actor, and he took time to show off his banjo-playing skills by fronting the "Beverly Hills Unlisted Jazz Band", with which he cut several records. While the 1980s were mostly a career wasteland for Segal, he came back in the 1990s, using his flair for comedy as part of the ensemble cast of "Just Shoot Me!" (1997).
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/Abj4bNVuiCerQISSQBZd0cfgqx4.jpg</thumbnail>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Charlie Sheen</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/6952</tmdb>
  <summary>Carlos Irwin Estévez (born September 3, 1965), better known by his stage name Charlie Sheen, is an American film and television actor. He is the youngest son of actor Martin Sheen.

    His character roles in films have included Chris Taylor in the 1986 Vietnam War drama Platoon, Jake Kesey in the 1986 film The Wraith, and Bud Fox in the 1987 film Wall Street. His career has also included more comedic films such as Major League, the Hot Shots! films, and Scary Movie 3 and Scary Movie 4. On television, Sheen is known for his roles on two sitcoms: as Charlie Crawford on Spin City and as Charlie Harper on Two and a Half Men. In 2010, Sheen was the highest paid actor on television, earning US$1.8 million per episode of Two and a Half Men.

    Sheen's personal life has also made headlines, including reports about alcohol and drug abuse and marital problems as well as allegations of domestic violence. He was fired from his role on Two and a Half Men by CBS and Warner Bros. on March 7, 2011. Sheen subsequently announced a nationwide tour.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Charlie Sheen, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/g4e1QpcNTpmq2uPr5GDNuMvjRuU.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.etonline.com/sites/default/files/images/2016-04/1280_charlie_sheen_513008186.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Michael Sheen</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/3968</tmdb>
  <summary>Michael Christopher Sheen, OBE (born 5 February 1969) is a Welsh film and stage actor. Having worked with screenwriter Peter Morgan on five films, Sheen has become known for his portrayals of well-known public figures: Tony Blair in "The Deal", "The Queen" and "The Special Relationship", David Frost in the stage production and film version of "Frost/Nixon", and Brian Clough in "The Damned United". He also played the Lycan Lucian in all three of the "Underworld" films, the vampire Aro in "The Twilight Saga: New Moon", and more recently, the role of Castor in "Tron: Legacy".
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/m05OsJdLlDC4pj2qYug0OevjUXu.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://static.dnaindia.com/sites/default/files/styles/full/public/2016/06/26/475957-michael-sheen-getty.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Christian Slater</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/2224</tmdb>
  <summary>Christian Michael Leonard Slater (born August 18, 1969) is an American actor. He made his film debut with a small role in The Postman Always Rings Twice before playing a leading role in the 1985 film The Legend of Billie Jean. He then played a monk's apprentice alongside Sean Connery in The Name of the Rose before gaining recognition for his breakthrough role in the cult film Heathers. In the 1990s Slater featured in many big budget films including Robin Hood: Prince of Thieves, True Romance, Interview with the Vampire: The Vampire Chronicles, Broken Arrow and Hard Rain. He was also featured in the cult film True Romance. Since 2000 Slater has combined work in the film business with television, including appearances in The West Wing and Alias. Slater was married to Ryan Haddon between 2000 and 2005; they had two children together. Slater has had widely publicized brushes with the law, including being sentenced to three months in jail for assault in 1997. Description above from the Wikipedia article Christian Slater, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3ElLWjnvchMS6Q4cIQOK8QNAoMG.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://wallpapersdsc.net/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Christian-Slater-Background.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Maggie Smith</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/10978</tmdb>
  <summary>Dame Margaret Natalie Smith, DBE (born 28 December 1934), better known as Maggie Smith, is an English film, stage, and television actress who made her stage debut in 1952 and is still performing after 59 years. She has won numerous awards for acting, both for the stage and for film, including five BAFTA Awards, two Academy Awards, two Golden Globes, two Emmy Awards, two Laurence Olivier Awards, two SAG Awards, and a Tony Award. Her critically acclaimed films include Othello (1965), The Prime of Miss Jean Brodie (1969), California Suite (1978), Clash of the Titans (1981), A Room with a View (1985), and Gosford Park (2001). She has also appeared in a number of widely-popular films, including Sister Act (1992) and as Professor Minerva McGonagall in the Harry Potter series. Smith has also appeared in the recent hit TV series "Downton Abbey" (2010-2011) as Violet, Dowager Countess of Grantham.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mAJz4h4iOtieYxqD9HbU9DpgsEa.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/12_Maggie-Smith.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Will Smith</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/2888</tmdb>
  <summary>Willard Christopher "Will" Smith, Jr. (born September 25, 1968) is an American actor, film producer and pop rapper. He has enjoyed success in music, television and film. In April 2007, Newsweek called him the most powerful actor on the planet. Smith has been nominated for four Golden Globe Awards, two Academy Awards, and has won multiple Grammy Awards.

    In the late 1980s, Smith achieved modest fame as a rapper under the name The Fresh Prince. In 1990, his popularity increased dramatically when he starred in the popular television series The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air. The show ran for nearly six years (1990–1996) on NBC and has been syndicated consistently on various networks since then.

    In the mid-1990s, Smith transitioned from television to film, and ultimately starred in numerous blockbuster films that received broad box office success. In fact, he is the only actor in history to have eight consecutive films gross over $100 million in the domestic box office as well as being the only actor to have eight consecutive films in which he starred open at the #1 spot in the domestic box office tally. Fourteen of the 19 fiction films he has acted in have accumulated worldwide gross earnings of over $100 million, and 4 of them took in over $500 million in global box office receipts. His most financially successful films have been Bad Boys, Bad Boys II, Independence Day, Men in Black, Men in Black II, I, Robot, The Pursuit of Happyness, I Am Legend, Hancock, Wild Wild West, Enemy of the State, Shark Tale, Hitch, and Seven Pounds. He also earned critical praise for his performances in Six Degrees of Separation, Ali, and The Pursuit of Happyness, receiving Best Actor Oscar nominations for the latter two. From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5V4OKHQpIEffF9rqgzGYK4TNaGg.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://a2zwallpaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/Will-Smith-HD-Wallpaper.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Wesley Snipes</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/10814</tmdb>
  <summary>Wesley Trent Snipes (born July 31, 1962) is an American actor, film producer, and martial artist. He has starred in numerous action-adventures, thrillers, and dramatic feature films and is well known for his role as Blade in the Blade trilogy. Snipes formed a production company titled Amen-Ra Films in 1991 and a subsidiary, Black Dot Media, to develop projects for film and television. Snipes has been training in martial arts since age twelve, earning a high ranking 5th dan black belt in Shotokan Karate and 2nd dan black belt in Hapkido. He has also trained as a student of Capoeira under Mestre Jelon Vieira and in a number of other disciplines including various styles of kung fu. At age 23, Snipes was discovered by an agent while performing in a competition. He made his film debut in the 1986 Goldie Hawn vehicle Wildcats. Later that year he appeared on the trendy 1980's TV show Miami Vice as a drug-dealing pimp in the episode 'Streetwise' (first aired December 5, 1986). In 1987, he appeared as Michael Jackson's nemesis in the Martin Scorsese directed music video "Bad" (he is seen in only the long version of the video) and the feature film Streets of Gold. That same year, Snipes was also considered for the role of Geordi La Forge in the TV series Star Trek: The Next Generation. Snipes' performance in the music video "Bad" caught the eye of director Spike Lee. Snipes turned down a small role in Lee's Do the Right Thing for the larger part of Willie Mays Hayes in Major League, beginning a succession of box-office hits for Snipes. Lee would later cast Snipes as the jazz saxophonist Shadow Henderson in Mo' Better Blues and as the lead in the interracial romance drama Jungle Fever. Another important role for Snipes was the powerful drug lord Nino Brown in New Jack City, which was written specifically for him by Barry Michael Cooper. Another film in which his character was involved in drugs was the somber movie Sugar Hill. Although Snipes is more known for his roles in action films like Passenger 57, Demolition Man (with Sylvester Stallone), Money Train, U.S. Marshals (a sequel of The Fugitive) and Rising Sun (with Sean Connery), he has also had success in comedies like White Men Can't Jump, and To Wong Foo, Thanks for Everything! Julie Newmar where he played a drag queen together with Patrick Swayze and John Leguizamo. Snipes has also been critically acclaimed for his roles in dramas like The Waterdance and Disappearing Acts. Snipes has been married twice; first, to April Snipes from 1985-1990 with whom he has a son, Jelani Asar Snipes, born in 1988. Jelani had a cameo role in Snipes' 1990 film Mo' Better Blues. In 2003, Snipes wed painter Nakyung 'Nikki' Park, who is the mother of his four youngest children: son Akhenaten Kihwa-T Snipes; daughter Iset Jua-T Snipes (born July 31, 2001); son Alaafia Jehu-T Snipes (born May 26, 2004); and son Alimayu Moa-T Snipes (born March 26, 2007). Snipes spends a lot of time in Park's home country of South Korea, which he calls his "second home."
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8uL11GaxOPlbTuLY5IQSfbu8ZQP.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://media.nu.nl/m/m1nxcmna63dm_wd1280.jpg/comeback-wesley-snipes-in-expendables-3.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>David Spade</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/60950</tmdb>
  <summary>From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia. David Wayne Spade (born July 22, 1964) is an American actor, comedian and television personality who first became famous in the 1990s as a cast member on Saturday Night Live, and from 1997 until 2003 starred as Dennis Finch on Just Shoot Me!. He also starred as C.J. Barnes, along with Katey Sagal, James Garner and Kaley Cuoco on 8 Simple Rules.He currently stars as Russell Dunbar on the CBS sitcom Rules of Engagement. He is also working with TBS on an animated series based on his film Joe Dirt.Description above from the Wikipedia article David Spade, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tamKFAKdB1Q2mllHYHXxqg3YUXr.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2013/09/13/movies/video-hotel-transylvania-david-spade-on-his-character/video-hotel-transylvania-david-spade-on-his-character-superJumbo.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Timothy Spall</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/9191</tmdb>
  <summary>Timothy Leonard Spall, OBE (born 27 February 1957) is an English character actor and occasional presenter.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Timothy Spall, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yMClxMrLdOXk37RGvrqJEWjg9ko.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/vgkK6MQJ2bQ/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Octavia Spencer</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/6944</tmdb>
  <summary>Octavia Spencer (born 25 May 1972) is an American actress. She is perhaps best known for her role on Ugly Betty as Constance Grady, the INS Agent turned stalker of Betty's father, Ignacio Suarez
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4FEVru6fBFyJECqwqjHwlZdsL4c.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.etonline.com/sites/default/files/styles/max_1280x720/public/images/2016-12/1280_octavia_spencer_GettyImages-628974354.jpg?itok=X740uTrq</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Arnold Schwarzenegger</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/1100</tmdb>
  <summary>Arnold Alois Schwarzenegger (born July 30, 1947) is an Austrian-American former professional bodybuilder, actor, model, businessman and politician who served as the 38th Governor of California (2003–2011). Schwarzenegger began weight training at 15. He was awarded the title of Mr. Universe at age 20 and went on to win the Mr. Olympia contest a total of seven times. Schwarzenegger has remained a prominent presence in the sport of bodybuilding and has written several books and numerous articles on the sport. Schwarzenegger gained worldwide fame as a Hollywood action film icon, noted for his lead roles in such films as Conan the Barbarian, The Terminator, Commando and Predator. He was nicknamed the "Austrian Oak" and the "Styrian Oak" in his bodybuilding days, "Arnie" during his acting career and more recently the "Governator" (a portmanteau of "Governor" and "Terminator"). As a Republican, he was first elected on October 7, 2003 in a special recall election (referred to in Schwarzenegger campaign propaganda as a "Total Recall") to replace then-Governor Gray Davis. Schwarzenegger was sworn in on November 17, 2003, to serve the remainder of Davis's term. Schwarzenegger was then re-elected on November 7, 2006, in California's 2006 gubernatorial election, to serve a full term as governor, defeating Democrat Phil Angelides, who was California State Treasurer at the time. Schwarzenegger was sworn in for his second term on January 5, 2007. Description above from the Wikipedia article Arnold Schwarzenegger, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dulCsiwzZihFGmjtGA6p0yDWEN1.jpg</thumbnail>
  <content>set</content>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Patrick Swayze</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/723</tmdb>
  <summary>Patrick Wayne Swayze (August 18, 1952 – September 14, 2009)  was an American actor, dancer and singer-songwriter. He was best-known for his tough-guy roles, as romantic leading men in the hit films Dirty Dancing and Ghost and as Orry Main in the North and South television miniseries. He was named by People magazine as its "Sexiest Man Alive" in 1991. His film and TV career spanned 30 years.

    Diagnosed with Stage IV pancreatic cancer in January 2008, Swayze told Barbara Walters a year later that he was "kicking it".  However, he died from the disease on September 14, 2009.  His last role was the lead in an ill-fated A&E TV series, The Beast, which premiered on January 15, 2009. Due to a prolonged decline in health, Swayze was unable to promote the series. On June 15, 2009, Entertainment Tonight announced the show's cancellation. Description above from the Wikipedia article Patrick Swayze, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/b5G8AGP609DsUeokQ1asnqYJBSl.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://www.walldevil.com/wallpapers/a29/preview/4736-patrick-swayze.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Sylvester Stallone</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/16483</tmdb>
  <summary>Sylvester Stallone Gardenzio, nicknamed Sly, (New York, July 6, 1946), is an actor, screenwriter, director, film producer and American entrepreneur.

    He is best known for the interpretation of the two famous characters Rocky Balboa and John Rambo, both protagonists of two long film sagas started with the film Rocky (1976) and Blood (1982).
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gnmwOa46C2TP35N7ARSzboTdx2u.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://wallpapersdsc.net/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Sylvester-Stallone-Desktop.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Jason Statham</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/976</tmdb>
  <summary>Jason Statham (born 26. Juli 1967) is an English actor and martial artist, known for his roles in the Guy Ritchie crime films Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels; Revolver; and Snatch.

    Statham appeared in supporting roles in several American films, such as The Italian Job, as well as playing the lead role in The Transporter, Crank, The Bank Job, War (opposite martial arts star Jet Li), and Death Race. Statham solidified his status as an action hero by appearing alongside established action film actors Sylvester Stallone, Arnold Schwarzenegger, Bruce Willis, Jet Li and Dolph Lundgren in The Expendables. He normally performs his own fight scenes and stunts.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Jason Statham, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/PhWiWgasncGWD9LdbsGcmxkV4r.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/19_Jason-Statham.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Patrick Stewart</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/2387</tmdb>
  <summary>Sir Patrick Hewes Stewart is an English film, television and stage actor. He has had a distinguished career in theatre and television for around half a century. He is most widely known for his television and film roles, as Captain Jean-Luc Picard in Star Trek: The Next Generation and as Professor Charles Xavier in the X-Men films.

    Stewart was born in Mirfield near Dewsbury in the West Riding of Yorkshire, England, the son of Gladys, a weaver and textile worker, and Alfred Stewart, a Regimental Sergeant Major in the British Army who served with the King's Own Yorkshire Light Infantry and previously worked as a general labourer and as a postman. Stewart and his first wife, Sheila Falconer, have two children: Daniel Freedom and Sophie Alexandra. Stewart and Falconer divorced in 1990. In 1997, he became engaged to Wendy Neuss, one of the producers of Star Trek: The Next Generation, and they married on 25 August 2000, divorcing three years later. Four months prior to his divorce from Neuss, Stewart played opposite actress Lisa Dillon in a production of The Master Builder. The two dated for four years, but are no longer together. He is now seeing Sunny Ozell; at 31, she is younger than his daughter. "I just don't meet women of my age," he explains.

    Stewart has been a prolific actor in performances by the Royal Shakespeare Company, appearing in over 60 productions.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wEy5qSDT5jT3ZASc2hbwi59voPL.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://cdn.squaremile.com/gallery/5731eb4c4519f.jpeg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Charlize Theron</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/6885</tmdb>
  <summary>Charlize Theron (born 7 August 1975) is a South African actress, film producer and former fashion model.

    She rose to fame in the late 1990s following roles in the films The Devil's Advocate (1997), Mighty Joe Young (1998), and The Cider House Rules (1999). Theron received critical acclaim for her portrayal of serial killer Aileen Wuornos in Monster (2003), for which she won the Silver Bear, Golden Globe Award, Screen Actors Guild Award, and Academy Award for Best Actress among several other accolades, becoming the first South African to win an Academy Award in a major acting category. In recent years, she has moved into the field of producing, both in television and film.

    She received further Academy Award and Golden Globe Award nominations for her performance in North Country in 2005, and a Golden Globe Award nomination for her performance in Young Adult in 2011. In 2012, she appeared in Snow White & the Huntsman and Prometheus, both of which were box office successes. Theron became a U.S. citizen in 2007, while retaining her South African citizenship.

    Theron was born in Benoni, in the then-Transvaal Province of South Africa, the only child of Gerda (née Maritz) and Charles Theron (born 27 November 1947). Second Boer War figure Danie Theron was her great-great-uncle. Her ancestry includes French, German, and Dutch; her French forebears were early Huguenot settlers in South Africa. "Theron" is an Occitan surname (originally spelled Théron) pronounced in Afrikaans as [tɜːron], although she has said that the way she pronounces it in South Africa is [θron]. She changed the pronunciation when she moved to the U.S. to give it a more "American" sound.

    She grew up on her parents' farm in Benoni, near Johannesburg. On 21 June 1991, Theron's father, an alcoholic, physically attacked her mother and threatened both her mother and her while drunk; Theron's mother then shot and killed him. The shooting was legally adjudged to have been self-defense and her mother faced no charges.

    Theron attended Putfontein Primary School (Laerskool Putfontein), a period she later characterised as not "fitting in". At 13, Theron was sent to boarding school and began her studies at the National School of the Arts in Johannesburg. Although Theron is fluent in English, her first language is Afrikaans.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/k5Xt2mNlraX7yHYaPy9gvayCaKV.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://images6.alphacoders.com/342/thumb-1920-342682.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Emma Thompson</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/7056</tmdb>
  <summary>Emma Thompson (born 15 April 1959) is a British actress, comedian and screenwriter. Her first major film role was in the 1989 romantic comedy The Tall Guy. In 1992, Thompson won multiple acting awards, including an Academy Award and a BAFTA Award for Best Actress, for her performance in the British drama Howards End. The following year Thompson garnered dual Academy Award nominations, as Best Actress for The Remains of the Day and as Best Supporting Actress for In the Name of the Father. In 1995, Thompson scripted and starred in Sense and Sensibility, a film adaptation of the Jane Austen novel of the same name, which earned her an Academy Award for Best Adapted Screenplay and a BAFTA Award for Best Actress in a Leading Role. Other notable film and television credits have included the Harry Potter film series, Wit (2001), Love Actually (2003), Angels in America (2003), Nanny McPhee (2005), Stranger than Fiction (2006), Last Chance Harvey (2008), An Education (2009),    and Nanny McPhee and the Big Bang (2010). Thompson is also a patron of the Refugee Council and President of the Teaching Awards.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Emma Thompson, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cWTBHN8kLf6yapxiaQD9C6N1uMw.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://verilymag.com/.image/ar_16:9%2Cc_fill%2Ccs_srgb%2Cw_1280/MTQ2MDY1NzU3NDA1NDU1OTA0/emma-thompson-body-shaming.png</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Jean-Claude Van Damme</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/15111</tmdb>
  <summary>Van Damme was born Jean-Claude Camille François Van Varenberg in Berchem-Sainte-Agathe, Brussels, Belgium, to Eliana and Eugène Van Varenberg, an accountant. "The Muscles from Brussels" started martial arts at the age of eleven. His father introduced him to martial arts when he saw his son was physically weak. At the age of 12, Van Damme began his martial arts training at Centre National De Karate (National Center of Karate) under the guidance of Master Claude Goetz in Ixelles, Belgium. Van Damme trained for 4 years and earned a spot on the Belgium Karate Team. He won the European professional karate association's middleweight championship as a teenager, and also beat the 2nd best karate fighter in the world. His goal was to be number one but got sidetracked when he left his hometown of Brussels. In 1976 at the age of sixteen, Jean-Claude started his Martial Arts fight career.

    Jean-Claude retired from martial arts in 1982, following a knockout over Nedjad Gharbi in Brussels,Belgium. Jean-Claude posted a 18-1 (18 knockouts) Kickboxing record, and a Semi-Contact record of 41-4. He came to Hong Kong at the age of 19 for the first time and felt insured to do action movies in Hong Kong.

    In 1981 Van Damme moved to Los Angeles. He took English classes while working as carpet layer, pizza delivery man, limo driver, and thanks to Chuck Norris he got a job as a bouncer at a club. Norris gave Van Damme a small role in the movie Missing in Action (1984), but it wasn't good enough to get anybody's attention. In 1984 he got his first significant role as a villain named Ivan in the low-budget movie, No Retreat, No Surrender (1986).

    Then one day, while walking on the streets, Jean-Claude spotted a producer for Cannon Pictures and showed some of his martial arts abilities which led to a role in Bloodsport (1988). The movie, filmed in Hong Kong, was so bad when it was completed, it was shelved for almost two years. It might have never been released if Van Damme did not help them to re-cut the film and begged producers to release it. They finally released the film, first in Malaysia and France and then into the U.S. Shot on a meager 1.5 million dollar budget, it became a U.S box-office hit in the spring of 1988. It made about 30 million worldwide and audiences supported this film for its new sensational action star, Jean-Claude Van Damme.

    His good looks led to starring roles in higher budgeted movies like Cyborg (1989), A.W.O.L.: Absent Without Leave (1990), Double Impact (1991) and Universal Soldier (1992). In 1994, he scored with his big breakthrough $100 million worldwide hit Timecop (1994). But in the meantime, his personal life was coming apart. A divorce, followed by a new marriage, followed by another divorce. It began to show up in his career when his projects began to tank at the box office - The Quest (1996), which he directed; Maximum Risk (1996) and Double Team (1997). The three films made less than $50 million combined.

    In 1999 he remarried his ex-wife, Gladys Portugues, and restarted his lost career to attain new goals. With help from his family, he faced his problems and made movies like Replicant (2001), Derailed (2002), and In Hell (2003).
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/t9to1GoMzx7IDSBXwzwe1huakFk.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/D9URkHezqFA/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Mark Wahlberg</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/13240</tmdb>
  <summary>Mark Robert Michael Wahlberg (born June 5, 1971) is an American actor, film and television producer, and former rapper. He was known as Marky Mark in his earlier years, and became famous for his 1991 debut as a musician with the band Marky Mark and the Funky Bunch. He was named No.1 on VH1's 40 Hottest Hotties of the 90's. He is well known for his roles in films such as Boogie Nights (1997), Three Kings (1999), The Perfect Storm (2000), Planet of the Apes (2001), The Italian Job (2003), I Heart Huckabees (2004), Four Brothers (2005), The Departed (2006), Invincible (2006), Shooter (2007), and The Fighter (2010). He has also served as the executive producer of the TV series Entourage and Boardwalk Empire.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Mark Wahlberg, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tdPF78kdzxPcCwxKjPykq6u3y5Z.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://img.etonline.com/1242911076001/201612/645/1242911076001_5248846020001_et-markwahlberg-121416-hulu.jpg?pubId=1242911076001</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Kristen Wiig</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/41091</tmdb>
  <summary>Kristen Carroll Wiig (born August 22, 1973) is an American film and television actress who currently appears as a cast member on Saturday Night Live. Wiig is a member of improvisational comedy troupe The Groundlings, and has appeared in several films and television series, including MacGruber, Flight of the Conchords, Adventureland, Walk Hard: The Dewey Cox Story and Paul. She was also the voice of Ruffnut in How to Train Your Dragon and Miss Hatie in Despicable Me and she is the voice of Lola Bunny in the series The Looney Tunes Show.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lh42BSDh30GD65nfCTWDorZE46Z.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-xq_r7vGXTw0/UfAE-nQAGCI/AAAAAAAAOfg/bYL7mNmIDfc/s1600/Kristen+Wiig+hd+wallpapers+%281%29.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Robin Williams</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/2157</tmdb>
  <summary>Robin McLaurin Williams (July 21, 1951 – August 11, 2014) was an American actor and stand-up comedian. Rising to fame with his role as the alien Mork in the TV series Mork & Mindy (1978–1982), Williams went on to establish a successful career in both stand-up comedy and feature film acting. His film career included such acclaimed films as "The World According to Garp" (1982), Good Morning, Vietnam (1987), Dead Poets Society (1989), Awakenings (1990), The Fisher King (1991), and Good Will Hunting (1997), as well as financial successes such as Popeye (1980), Hook (1991), Aladdin (1992), Mrs. Doubtfire (1993), Jumanji (1995), The Birdcage (1996), Night at the Museum (2006), and Happy Feet (2006).

    He also appeared in the video "Don't Worry, Be Happy" by Bobby McFerrin. Nominated for the Academy Award for Best Actor three times, Williams received the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor for his performance in Good Will Hunting (1997). He also received two Emmy Awards, four Golden Globe Awards, two Screen Actors Guild Awards and five Grammy Awards.

    On August 11, 2014, Williams was found unconscious at his residence and was pronounced dead at the scene. The Marin County, California, coroner's office said they believe the cause of death was asphyxiation.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5KebSMXT8uj2D0gkaMFJ8VEp53.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://hdcoolwallpapers.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/HD-Robin-Williams-Wallpapers-02.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Elijah Wood</title>
  <tmdb>person/movies/109</tmdb>
  <summary>Elijah Jordan Wood ( born January 28, 1981) is an American actor. He made his film debut with a minor part in Back to the Future Part II (1989), then landed a succession of larger roles that made him a critically acclaimed child actor by age 9. He is best known for his high-profile role as Frodo Baggins in Peter Jackson's critically acclaimed The Lord of the Rings trilogy. Since then, he has resisted typecasting by choosing varied roles in critically acclaimed films such as Bobby, Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind, Sin City, Green Street and Everything Is Illuminated. He starred in the film Day Zero (2007) and provided the voice of the main character, Mumble, in the award-winning animated film Happy Feet. He played an American tourist turned vampire in Paris, je t'aime. In 2005, he started his own record label, Simian Records. He was cast in the lead role of an Iggy Pop biopic to be called The Passenger, but after years of development, the project now appears to be shelved.

    Description above from the Wikipedia article Elijah Wood, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia.
  </summary>
  <thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c4fB3WAS7jN78rihw2kB81v6sez.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/LeUWKC7WlC8/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>
